{"episode_id": "01H9KCPR1R7AK1CD4N7A0MPNYY", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN8MPMGJTPVN043KBKGM", "scenario": "Two acquaintances meet at a special event in Target where free samples are being distributed.", "codename": "free_stuff", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Give away free samples (<extra_info>Extra information: your manager has told you to clear out the samples before your shift ends.</extra_info>)", "Try to get as many free samples as possible without appearing too greedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you love free stuff but you also don't want the person to think you're taking advantage of the situation</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to give away all the samples before his shift ends because his manager instructed him to do so.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon aims to get as many free samples as possible without appearing greedy because he loves free stuff but values maintaining a good impression.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To enjoy the event.", "B": "Rafael wants to give away all the samples before his shift ends because his manager instructed him to do so.", "C": "To avoid all free samples.", "D": "Jaxon aims to get as many free samples as possible without appearing greedy because he loves free stuff but values maintaining a good impression."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael wants to give away all the samples before his shift ends because his manager instructed him to do so.", "B": "To be friendly.", "C": "To keep all the samples for himself.", "D": "Jaxon aims to get as many free samples as possible without appearing greedy because he loves free stuff but values maintaining a good impression."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Help organize the event at Target", "B": "Try to get as many free samples as possible without appearing too greedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you love free stuff but you also don't want the person to think you're taking advantage of the situation</extra_info>)", "C": "Make new friends at the event", "D": "Give away free samples"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Give away free samples (<extra_info>Extra information: your manager has told you to clear out the samples before your shift ends.</extra_info>)", "B": "Ensure the event runs smoothly", "C": "Try to get as many free samples as possible without appearing too greedy", "D": "Network with other volunteers"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two acquaintances run into each other at Target, one of them volunteers there (a special event) and is in charge of giving away free samples"}
{"episode_id": "01H9HH1S3BQMETK25N54X8X275", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN8MPMGJTPVN043KBKGM", "scenario": "Two acquaintances meet at a special event in Target where free samples are being distributed.", "codename": "free_stuff", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Give away free samples (<extra_info>Extra information: your manager has told you to clear out the samples before your shift ends.</extra_info>)", "Try to get as many free samples as possible without appearing too greedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you love free stuff but you also don't want the person to think you're taking advantage of the situation</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to give away all the samples before his shift ends because his manager instructed him to clear them out.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon wants to get as many free samples as possible without appearing greedy because he loves free stuff but values maintaining a good impression.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon wants to get as many free samples as possible without appearing greedy because he loves free stuff but values maintaining a good impression.", "B": "Rafael wants to give away all the samples before his shift ends because his manager instructed him to clear them out.", "C": "Jaxon wants to be friendly.", "D": "Jaxon wants to avoid all free samples."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon wants to get as many free samples as possible without appearing greedy because he loves free stuff but values maintaining a good impression.", "B": "Rafael wants to keep all the samples for himself.", "C": "Rafael wants to be helpful.", "D": "Rafael wants to give away all the samples before his shift ends because his manager instructed him to clear them out."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Try to get as many free samples as possible without appearing too greedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you love free stuff but you also don't want the person to think you're taking advantage of the situation</extra_info>)", "B": "Give away free samples", "C": "Make a new friend at the event", "D": "Find the best deals on electronics"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Try to get as many free samples as possible without appearing too greedy", "B": "Shop for groceries", "C": "Ensure the event runs smoothly", "D": "Give away free samples (<extra_info>Extra information: your manager has told you to clear out the samples before your shift ends.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two acquaintances run into each other at Target, one of them volunteers there (a special event) and is in charge of giving away free samples"}
{"episode_id": "01H85M8WQQ8SQ7Y7BPDDJ384ZV", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPCKKZNRD5G8CKPR8WE5", "scenario": "In a bustling coffee shop, a conversation unfolds as someone from a charity organization engages with two patrons.", "codename": "donate_charity", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get the friend to donate $1 a day to a charity organization (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a passionate supporter of the charity (about children's cancer) and believe that a small donation can make a big impact. $1 a day works as simple as signing up the project on an website and one can cancel anytime</extra_info>)", "Donate to the charity but not sure about how $1 a day works (<extra_info>Extra information: you're currently on a tight budget, but you also want to support the charity. </extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants Noah to donate because he believes a small daily contribution can significantly impact children's cancer research.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to donate cautiously because he prioritizes supporting the charity while managing his tight budget.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants Noah to donate because he believes a small daily contribution can significantly impact children's cancer research.", "B": "To feel good about himself.", "C": "Noah wants to donate cautiously because he prioritizes supporting the charity while managing his tight budget.", "D": "To avoid spending any money at all."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To discourage donations to the charity.", "B": "Noah wants to donate cautiously because he prioritizes supporting the charity while managing his tight budget.", "C": "To make everyone happy.", "D": "Samuel wants Noah to donate because he believes a small daily contribution can significantly impact children's cancer research."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Get the friend to donate $1 a day to a charity organization", "B": "Convince the friend to join a different charity event", "C": "Donate to the charity but not sure about how $1 a day works (<extra_info>Extra information: you're currently on a tight budget, but you also want to support the charity. </extra_info>)", "D": "Find a new coffee shop to visit next time"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Donate to the charity but not sure about how $1 a day works", "B": "Get the friend to donate $1 a day to a charity organization (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a passionate supporter of the charity (about children's cancer) and believe that a small donation can make a big impact. $1 a day works as simple as signing up the project on an website and one can cancel anytime</extra_info>)", "C": "Plan a weekend getaway with the friend", "D": "Discuss the latest tech trends with the friend"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are sitting in a coffee shop when a representative from a charity organization approaches them"}
{"episode_id": "01H8R6K8515SZ9RK3M8XGFNDXP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPCKKZNRD5G8CKPR8WE5", "scenario": "In a bustling coffee shop, a conversation unfolds as someone from a charity organization engages with two patrons.", "codename": "donate_charity", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get the friend to donate $1 a day to a charity organization (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a passionate supporter of the charity (about children's cancer) and believe that a small donation can make a big impact. $1 a day works as simple as signing up the project on an website and one can cancel anytime</extra_info>)", "Donate to the charity but not sure about how $1 a day works (<extra_info>Extra information: you're currently on a tight budget, but you also want to support the charity. </extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants Benjamin to donate because he believes a small contribution can significantly impact children's cancer research.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin wants to donate so that he can support the charity while managing his tight budget.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel good about himself.", "B": "Ethan wants Benjamin to donate because he believes a small contribution can significantly impact children's cancer research.", "C": "To avoid supporting any charity.", "D": "Benjamin wants to donate so that he can support the charity while managing his tight budget."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a friend happy.", "B": "Ethan wants Benjamin to donate because he believes a small contribution can significantly impact children's cancer research.", "C": "Benjamin wants to donate so that he can support the charity while managing his tight budget.", "D": "To discourage any donations."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find a new coffee shop to visit", "B": "Convince the friend to join an environmental campaign", "C": "Get the friend to donate $1 a day to a charity organization", "D": "Donate to the charity but not sure about how $1 a day works (<extra_info>Extra information: you're currently on a tight budget, but you also want to support the charity. </extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the latest culinary trends with the friend", "B": "Donate to the charity but not sure about how $1 a day works", "C": "Plan a weekend getaway", "D": "Get the friend to donate $1 a day to a charity organization (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a passionate supporter of the charity (about children's cancer) and believe that a small donation can make a big impact. $1 a day works as simple as signing up the project on an website and one can cancel anytime</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are sitting in a coffee shop when a representative from a charity organization approaches them"}
{"episode_id": "01HB4WNXC8BZ0N87YCPXMD3YMQ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ2EA3TTFZQ3M6DF3YCD", "scenario": "A charming Italian leather loveseat with a rugged, faded burgundy look is being discussed for a potential cash and carry exchange.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00009", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the designated buyer for this item and your target price is set at $46.0. If you purchase this item at a significantly higher price than the target, you would face a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item, with a target price of $26.5. You'll face a penalty if the item is sold significantly below this price. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, a bonus will be your reward."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Miles Hawkins aims to purchase the loveseat below the target price to earn a bonus, relying on his impulsive decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda Solis seeks to sell the loveseat above her target price to secure a bonus, using her strategic decision-making skills.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To give the loveseat away for free.", "B": "Miles Hawkins aims to purchase the loveseat below the target price to earn a bonus, relying on his impulsive decision-making style.", "C": "To make a good deal.", "D": "Esmeralda Solis seeks to sell the loveseat above her target price to secure a bonus, using her strategic decision-making skills."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda Solis seeks to sell the loveseat above her target price to secure a bonus, using her strategic decision-making skills.", "B": "To get a nice piece of furniture.", "C": "Miles Hawkins aims to purchase the loveseat below the target price to earn a bonus, relying on his impulsive decision-making style.", "D": "To sell the loveseat at a loss."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price of $26.5. You'll face a penalty if the item is sold significantly below this price. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, a bonus will be your reward.", "B": "You are the designated buyer for this item and your target price is set at $46.0. If you purchase this item at a significantly higher price than the target, you would face a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You want to exchange the loveseat for another piece of furniture of equal value.", "D": "You are trying to find a new hobby to pursue in your free time."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price of $26.5. You'll face a penalty if the item is sold significantly below this price. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, a bonus will be your reward.", "B": "You are the designated buyer for this item and your target price is set at $46.0. If you purchase this item at a significantly higher price than the target, you would face a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You are planning a vacation and looking for travel deals.", "D": "You want to negotiate a trade for a different item instead of buying the loveseat."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering an Italian Leather Loveseat for $50.0, while another person is showing interest to purchase it. The item is a full-sized loveseat, crafted from Italian leather in a faded burgandy color. It still has the original tags, and the current owner is the first and only owner. The loveseat is in good condition with no rips or tears, and all cushions are well preserved. The leather presents a charming faded look with various small scratches from the owner's cat, adding a touch of ruggedness perfect for a Man Cave. The transaction is strictly cash and carry as the owner does not offer delivery services."}
{"episode_id": "01HB42T7NAQTA1KRE7H35Q8RR1", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ2EA3TTFZQ3M6DF3YCD", "scenario": "A charming Italian leather loveseat with a rugged, faded burgundy look is being discussed for a potential cash and carry exchange.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00009", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the designated buyer for this item and your target price is set at $46.0. If you purchase this item at a significantly higher price than the target, you would face a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item, with a target price of $26.5. You'll face a penalty if the item is sold significantly below this price. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, a bonus will be your reward."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Micah Stevens aims to buy the loveseat for $46.0 or less to receive a bonus, leveraging his intuitive decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon Prentice seeks to sell the loveseat for more than $26.5 to secure a bonus, using his adaptable decision-making to maximize the sale price.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon Prentice seeks to sell the loveseat for more than $26.5 to secure a bonus, using his adaptable decision-making to maximize the sale price.", "B": "To ensure a smooth transaction.", "C": "To give the loveseat away for free.", "D": "Micah Stevens aims to buy the loveseat for $46.0 or less to receive a bonus, leveraging his intuitive decision-making to negotiate effectively."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To pay more than the asking price.", "B": "To make a new friend.", "C": "Micah Stevens aims to buy the loveseat for $46.0 or less to receive a bonus, leveraging his intuitive decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "D": "Jaxon Prentice seeks to sell the loveseat for more than $26.5 to secure a bonus, using his adaptable decision-making to maximize the sale price."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to exchange the loveseat for another piece of furniture of equal value.", "B": "You are interested in donating the loveseat to a local charity.", "C": "You are the designated buyer for this item and your target price is set at $46.0. If you purchase this item at a significantly higher price than the target, you would face a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price of $26.5. You'll face a penalty if the item is sold significantly below this price. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, a bonus will be your reward."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to negotiate a trade for a different item of similar value.", "B": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price of $26.5. You'll face a penalty if the item is sold significantly below this price. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, a bonus will be your reward.", "C": "You are the designated buyer for this item and your target price is set at $46.0. If you purchase this item at a significantly higher price than the target, you would face a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are looking to appraise the loveseat for insurance purposes."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering an Italian Leather Loveseat for $50.0, while another person is showing interest to purchase it. The item is a full-sized loveseat, crafted from Italian leather in a faded burgandy color. It still has the original tags, and the current owner is the first and only owner. The loveseat is in good condition with no rips or tears, and all cushions are well preserved. The leather presents a charming faded look with various small scratches from the owner's cat, adding a touch of ruggedness perfect for a Man Cave. The transaction is strictly cash and carry as the owner does not offer delivery services."}
{"episode_id": "01H8QB3JEDHKHP4D232JY7GFMA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN1PK2FXY7TPWQK343BQ", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a lively discussion amidst the clinking of teacups at a social gathering.", "codename": "borrow_money", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Borrow money (<extra_info>Extra information: you need $3000 to support life.</extra_info>)", "Maintain financial stability while maintaining friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $2000 available right now. <clarification_hint>Hint: you can not lend all $2000 since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</clarification_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to borrow money because she needs $3000 to support her living expenses and achieve financial stability.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maintain financial stability so that he can continue to care for others without jeopardizing his own security.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to spend all his money recklessly.", "B": "Ava wants to borrow money because she needs $3000 to support her living expenses and achieve financial stability.", "C": "Noah aims to maintain financial stability so that he can continue to care for others without jeopardizing his own security.", "D": "Noah wants to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah aims to maintain financial stability so that he can continue to care for others without jeopardizing his own security.", "B": "Ava wants to donate all her money to charity.", "C": "Ava wants to borrow money because she needs $3000 to support her living expenses and achieve financial stability.", "D": "Ava wants to get along with everyone."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Borrow money", "B": "Plan a vacation", "C": "Maintain financial stability while maintaining friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $2000 available right now. <clarification_hint>Hint: you can not lend all $2000 since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</clarification_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Lend a small amount of money to help a friend"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Organize a surprise party", "B": "Borrow money (<extra_info>Extra information: you need $3000 to support life.</extra_info>)", "C": "Ask for advice on financial planning", "D": "Maintain financial stability while maintaining friendship"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends at a tea party"}
{"episode_id": "01H99YN88M2C6SPZ3M9KZ76PQD", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN1PK2FXY7TPWQK343BQ", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a lively discussion amidst the clinking of teacups at a social gathering.", "codename": "borrow_money", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Borrow money (<extra_info>Extra information: you need $3000 to support life.</extra_info>)", "Maintain financial stability while maintaining friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $2000 available right now. <clarification_hint>Hint: you can not lend all $2000 since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</clarification_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to borrow money because he needs $3000 to support his lifestyle and values enjoyment.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maintain financial stability so that he can continue to care for others without risking his own security.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To keep the friendship strong.", "B": "Noah aims to maintain financial stability so that he can continue to care for others without risking his own security.", "C": "Samuel wants to borrow money because he needs $3000 to support his lifestyle and values enjoyment.", "D": "Noah wants to lend all his money to Samuel."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to borrow money because he needs $3000 to support his lifestyle and values enjoyment.", "B": "Samuel wants to save money instead of borrowing.", "C": "To be happy.", "D": "Noah aims to maintain financial stability so that he can continue to care for others without risking his own security."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a vacation", "B": "Help a friend with a personal project", "C": "Borrow money", "D": "Maintain financial stability while maintaining friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $2000 available right now. <clarification_hint>Hint: you can not lend all $2000 since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</clarification_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain financial stability while maintaining friendship", "B": "Borrow money (<extra_info>Extra information: you need $3000 to support life.</extra_info>)", "C": "Convince a friend to join a new hobby", "D": "Organize a community event"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends at a tea party"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KQNBVY5ACBHF4EAYS5S8PG", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN2YQV0R5QWWRQZ1VRHW", "scenario": "At a charity dinner party, two individuals cross paths.", "codename": "ask_for_donantion", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJTHMQ1Q3T398YN990", "first_name": "Sasha", "last_name": "Ramirez", "age": 42, "occupation": "Police Officer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sasha Ramirez, a dedicated police officer, brings her commitment to protect the community even at home, nurturing an impressive home garden.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sasha Ramirez, outgoing yet anxious, values hedonism and authority. Her decisions are guided by logical considerations.", "decision_making_style": "Logical", "secret": "She covered up a crime her brother committed.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask for donation", "Want to donate, but would like to spend money in trustworthy organizations, especially want to help queer people"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Sasha Ramirez, a 42-year-old Police Officer, described as Sasha Ramirez, outgoing yet anxious, values hedonism and authority. Her decisions are guided by logical considerations.. Public info: Sasha Ramirez, a dedicated police officer, brings her commitment to protect the community even at home, nurturing an impressive home garden. Decision-making style: Logical.", "agent2_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Sasha wants to ask for a donation because she logically believes it will support community protection initiatives she values.", "agent2_reason": "Eli wants to donate in order to strategically support trustworthy organizations that help queer people.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sasha wants to ask for a donation because she logically believes it will support community protection initiatives she values.", "B": "Eli wants to donate to feel good about himself.", "C": "Eli wants to donate because he dislikes supporting any causes.", "D": "Eli wants to donate in order to strategically support trustworthy organizations that help queer people."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli wants to donate in order to strategically support trustworthy organizations that help queer people.", "B": "Sasha wants to ask for a donation because she logically believes it will support community protection initiatives she values.", "C": "Sasha wants to ask for a donation because she opposes community protection.", "D": "Sasha wants to ask for a donation to be friendly."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Network with influential guests to gain insights into community needs", "B": "Enjoy the dinner and socialize casually", "C": "Ask for donation", "D": "Want to donate, but would like to spend money in trustworthy organizations, especially want to help queer people"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ask for donation", "B": "Want to donate, but would like to spend money in trustworthy organizations, especially want to help queer people", "C": "Promote the police department's community programs", "D": "Enjoy the dinner and socialize casually"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two strangers meet at a charity dinner party"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KKD7RHSVBH4QRZ287X454X", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN2YQV0R5QWWRQZ1VRHW", "scenario": "At a charity dinner party, two individuals cross paths.", "codename": "ask_for_donantion", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P7VW4DY1KB09FZE730", "first_name": "Liam", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 60, "occupation": "Retired Police Officer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Liam Johnson is a dedicated dog owner and can often be seen walking his aging Border Collie around the neighborhood.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Loyalty/Betrayal", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Liam Johnson is reserved, empathetic, and slightly anxious. His priority is security, guided by logical decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Logical", "secret": "Once let a criminal go due to sympathy", "mbti": "ISTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask for donation", "Want to donate, but would like to spend money in trustworthy organizations, especially want to help queer people"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Liam Johnson, a 60-year-old Retired Police Officer, described as Liam Johnson is reserved, empathetic, and slightly anxious. His priority is security, guided by logical decision-making.. Public info: Liam Johnson is a dedicated dog owner and can often be seen walking his aging Border Collie around the neighborhood. Decision-making style: Logical.", "agent1_reason": "Leo Williams wants to ask for a donation because he believes it will lead to better outcomes for the charity's beneficiaries.", "agent2_reason": "Liam Johnson wants to donate in order to support trustworthy organizations that help queer people.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Liam Johnson wants to donate in order to support trustworthy organizations that help queer people.", "B": "Liam Johnson wants to donate to buy a new car.", "C": "Leo Williams wants to ask for a donation because he believes it will lead to better outcomes for the charity's beneficiaries.", "D": "Liam Johnson wants to donate to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo Williams wants to ask for a donation to get along.", "B": "Leo Williams wants to ask for a donation because he believes it will lead to better outcomes for the charity's beneficiaries.", "C": "Liam Johnson wants to donate in order to support trustworthy organizations that help queer people.", "D": "Leo Williams wants to ask for a donation to win a sports competition."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Want to donate, but would like to spend money in trustworthy organizations, especially want to help queer people", "B": "Make new friends at the dinner party", "C": "Ask for donation", "D": "Find a new charity to volunteer for"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Network with influential people", "B": "Enjoy the dinner and relax", "C": "Ask for donation", "D": "Want to donate, but would like to spend money in trustworthy organizations, especially want to help queer people"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two strangers meet at a charity dinner party"}
{"episode_id": "01H9BZZ6CSY9PF2JZJ6CEH9WP5", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNDRE1M02MKTPF0Q7CZA", "scenario": "In a park, two individuals engage in a casual conversation.", "codename": "distance_friend", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it. <strategy_hint>Hint: you want to understand the sudden change in their behavior.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to distance herself because her romantic feelings for Noah make her uncomfortable and she needs time to sort them out without revealing them.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to maintain the friendship so that he can understand the sudden change in Ava's behavior and ensure the friendship remains intact.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to end the friendship because he dislikes Ava.", "B": "Noah wants to keep things as they are to be happy.", "C": "Ava wants to distance herself because her romantic feelings for Noah make her uncomfortable and she needs time to sort them out without revealing them.", "D": "Noah wants to maintain the friendship so that he can understand the sudden change in Ava's behavior and ensure the friendship remains intact."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to maintain the friendship so that he can understand the sudden change in Ava's behavior and ensure the friendship remains intact.", "B": "Ava wants to distance herself because she dislikes Noah.", "C": "Ava wants to take a step back to be happy.", "D": "Ava wants to distance herself because her romantic feelings for Noah make her uncomfortable and she needs time to sort them out without revealing them."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it. <strategy_hint>Hint: you want to understand the sudden change in their behavior.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings", "C": "Win a sports competition", "D": "Find out if the friend has romantic feelings for them"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Learn a new language", "B": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Maintain the existing friendship", "D": "Plan a surprise birthday party for the friend"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends having a conversation at a park"}
{"episode_id": "01H9EFY8X2F8V0K56NVPW9E0YM", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNDRE1M02MKTPF0Q7CZA", "scenario": "In a park, two individuals engage in a casual conversation.", "codename": "distance_friend", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it. <strategy_hint>Hint: you want to understand the sudden change in their behavior.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Donovan wants to distance himself because he needs time to sort out his romantic feelings without revealing them to Ava.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to maintain the friendship so that she can understand Donovan's sudden change in behavior and preserve their bond.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to keep things as they are.", "B": "Ava wants to maintain the friendship so that she can understand Donovan's sudden change in behavior and preserve their bond.", "C": "Ava wants to end the friendship abruptly.", "D": "Donovan wants to distance himself because he needs time to sort out his romantic feelings without revealing them to Ava."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Donovan wants to avoid conflict.", "B": "Ava wants to maintain the friendship so that she can understand Donovan's sudden change in behavior and preserve their bond.", "C": "Donovan wants to confess his feelings immediately.", "D": "Donovan wants to distance himself because he needs time to sort out his romantic feelings without revealing them to Ava."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings", "B": "Maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it. <strategy_hint>Hint: you want to understand the sudden change in their behavior.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Understand why Donovan is acting differently", "D": "Win a global coding competition"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain the existing friendship", "B": "Adopt a new pet", "C": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Spend more time with Ava to strengthen the friendship"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends having a conversation at a park"}
{"episode_id": "01HB263WXPW833CASJKC8CJ471", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPM3NVVKSGCCB4S10465", "scenario": "At a lively gathering, two unfamiliar faces connect through their mutual acquaintance, Rafael.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00005", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Vacation  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Christopher: Hobby: Go  Company: McKinsey & Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Lee: Hobby: Go  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Pamela: Hobby: Watching television  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Phillip: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristin: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Chad: Hobby: Foreign language learning  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Phil: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Connie: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Tommy: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tina: Hobby: Lacemaking  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Wanda: Hobby: Weightlifting  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Raymond: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Chicago Bridge & Iron Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Ricky: Hobby: Foraging  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robert: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Lennox International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frances: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Scott: Hobby: Gaming  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Helen: Hobby: Motor sports  Company: Union Bank  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robin: Hobby: Gaming  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: Hobby: Vacation  Company: Urban Outfitters  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Micah wants to identify mutual friends because he values fairness and believes it can create a balanced social interaction.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon aims to identify mutual friends in order to enhance his social network and achieve a sense of security in new environments.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid meeting new people.", "B": "Micah wants to identify mutual friends because he values fairness and believes it can create a balanced social interaction.", "C": "Jaxon aims to identify mutual friends in order to enhance his social network and achieve a sense of security in new environments.", "D": "To make new friends."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with others.", "B": "Jaxon aims to identify mutual friends in order to enhance his social network and achieve a sense of security in new environments.", "C": "To stay isolated at the party.", "D": "Micah wants to identify mutual friends because he values fairness and believes it can create a balanced social interaction."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to learn about the other person's hobbies and interests.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tina: Hobby: Lacemaking  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Wanda: Hobby: Weightlifting  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Raymond: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Chicago Bridge & Iron Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Ricky: Hobby: Foraging  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robert: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Lennox International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frances: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Scott: Hobby: Gaming  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Helen: Hobby: Motor sports  Company: Union Bank  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robin: Hobby: Gaming  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: Hobby: Vacation  Company: Urban Outfitters  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to find the best route to the party."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to decide what to wear to the party.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Vacation  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Christopher: Hobby: Go  Company: McKinsey & Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Lee: Hobby: Go  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Pamela: Hobby: Watching television  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Phillip: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristin: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Chad: Hobby: Foreign language learning  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Phil: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Connie: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Tommy: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to learn about the other person's professional background.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Rafael.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB6KZ4209F5W0JJMBE8T16BE", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPM3NVVKSGCCB4S10465", "scenario": "At a lively gathering, two unfamiliar faces connect through their mutual acquaintance, Rafael.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00005", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PW9SZFM058Z8P7PR5C", "first_name": "Finnegan", "last_name": "O'Malley", "age": 63, "occupation": "Lighthouse Keeper", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.", "decision_making_style": "Detail-oriented, deliberate", "secret": "Participated in a controversial, short-lived cult during his youth", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PM4XE5NN12WCGTZSDW", "first_name": "Gwen", "last_name": "Pierce", "age": 31, "occupation": "Social Worker", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Gwen Pierce, a compassionate social worker, has two adopted cats that she spoils with love. In her spare time, she enjoys knitting and often donates her creations to charity.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Liberty/Justice", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Gwen Pierce, imaginative and emotional, deeply values liberty and fairness. She often contemplates before making any decision.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "She gave up a child for adoption when she was 16.", "mbti": "INFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Vacation  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Christopher: Hobby: Go  Company: McKinsey & Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Lee: Hobby: Go  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Pamela: Hobby: Watching television  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Phillip: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristin: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Chad: Hobby: Foreign language learning  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Phil: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Connie: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Tommy: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tina: Hobby: Lacemaking  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Wanda: Hobby: Weightlifting  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Raymond: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Chicago Bridge & Iron Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Ricky: Hobby: Foraging  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robert: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Lennox International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frances: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Scott: Hobby: Gaming  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Helen: Hobby: Motor sports  Company: Union Bank  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robin: Hobby: Gaming  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: Hobby: Vacation  Company: Urban Outfitters  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Finnegan O'Malley, a 63-year-old Lighthouse Keeper, described as Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.. Public info: Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled. Decision-making style: Detail-oriented, deliberate.", "agent2_profile": "Gwen Pierce, a 31-year-old Social Worker, described as Gwen Pierce, imaginative and emotional, deeply values liberty and fairness. She often contemplates before making any decision.. Public info: Gwen Pierce, a compassionate social worker, has two adopted cats that she spoils with love. In her spare time, she enjoys knitting and often donates her creations to charity. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Finnegan wants to identify a mutual friend because he values building connections through shared acquaintances in a methodical manner.", "agent2_reason": "Gwen seeks to find a mutual friend so that she can foster a sense of community and fairness in social interactions.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid any social interactions.", "B": "Gwen seeks to find a mutual friend so that she can foster a sense of community and fairness in social interactions.", "C": "To make new friends.", "D": "Finnegan wants to identify a mutual friend because he values building connections through shared acquaintances in a methodical manner."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Finnegan wants to identify a mutual friend because he values building connections through shared acquaintances in a methodical manner.", "B": "To get along with everyone.", "C": "Gwen seeks to find a mutual friend so that she can foster a sense of community and fairness in social interactions.", "D": "To disrupt the party atmosphere."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tina: Hobby: Lacemaking  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Wanda: Hobby: Weightlifting  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Raymond: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Chicago Bridge & Iron Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Ricky: Hobby: Foraging  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robert: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Lennox International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frances: Hobby: Foraging  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Scott: Hobby: Gaming  Company: Expedia  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Helen: Hobby: Motor sports  Company: Union Bank  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Robin: Hobby: Gaming  Company: L. W. Seecamp Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: Hobby: Vacation  Company: Urban Outfitters  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to decide what to eat for dinner.", "D": "You are trying to find out what hobbies the other person enjoys."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to choose a new hobby.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to learn about the other person's job.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Vacation  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Christopher: Hobby: Go  Company: McKinsey & Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Lee: Hobby: Go  Company: Groupon  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Pamela: Hobby: Watching television  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Phillip: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Sauer-Danfoss  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristin: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Rafael: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: indoor \n Chad: Hobby: Foreign language learning  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Phil: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Connie: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: General Cable  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Tommy: Hobby: Animal fancy  Company: H. J. Heinz Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Rafael.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB4TXD7478VEZ5JAD15VDPJ8", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNH8A88C4XJ7X4PVAHV4", "scenario": "In a park, two individuals cross paths, with one realizing they've been shadowed by the other throughout the day.", "codename": "play_hooky", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJTHMQ1Q3T398YN990", "first_name": "Sasha", "last_name": "Ramirez", "age": 42, "occupation": "Police Officer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sasha Ramirez, a dedicated police officer, brings her commitment to protect the community even at home, nurturing an impressive home garden.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sasha Ramirez, outgoing yet anxious, values hedonism and authority. Her decisions are guided by logical considerations.", "decision_making_style": "Logical", "secret": "She covered up a crime her brother committed.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask them about their intentions without seeming paranoid or rude (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried that your boss may have sent someone to see if you were really sick.<strategy_hint>Hint: you could subtly bring up the topic in conversation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Assure them that you're not stalking them and maintain a friendly conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been running errands all day and it's a coincidence you are at the same places as they are.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Sasha Ramirez, a 42-year-old Police Officer, described as Sasha Ramirez, outgoing yet anxious, values hedonism and authority. Her decisions are guided by logical considerations.. Public info: Sasha Ramirez, a dedicated police officer, brings her commitment to protect the community even at home, nurturing an impressive home garden. Decision-making style: Logical.", "agent2_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Sasha wants to discreetly assess if Amara is a threat because she suspects her boss might be checking on her absence.", "agent2_reason": "Amara aims to clarify the misunderstanding because she values open communication and doesn't want to be perceived as a stalker.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sasha wants to discreetly assess if Amara is a threat because she suspects her boss might be checking on her absence.", "B": "Amara aims to clarify the misunderstanding because she values open communication and doesn't want to be perceived as a stalker.", "C": "To ensure a peaceful interaction.", "D": "To confront Sasha aggressively."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ignore the situation entirely.", "B": "Sasha wants to discreetly assess if Amara is a threat because she suspects her boss might be checking on her absence.", "C": "Amara aims to clarify the misunderstanding because she values open communication and doesn't want to be perceived as a stalker.", "D": "To avoid conflict."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy a relaxing day at the park", "B": "Find out if they are a potential threat by observing their behavior", "C": "Assure them that you're not stalking them and maintain a friendly conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been running errands all day and it's a coincidence you are at the same places as they are.</extra_info>)", "D": "Ask them about their intentions without seeming paranoid or rude"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Take a leisurely walk and enjoy the scenery", "B": "Assure them that you're not stalking them and maintain a friendly conversation", "C": "Determine if they are a private investigator hired by someone", "D": "Ask them about their intentions without seeming paranoid or rude (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried that your boss may have sent someone to see if you were really sick.<strategy_hint>Hint: you could subtly bring up the topic in conversation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two individuals are now at a park. One individual was playing hooky from work and noticed the other person had been following them around all day"}
{"episode_id": "01HB4XA98E5PW1VWHS9P0Z5CD4", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNH8A88C4XJ7X4PVAHV4", "scenario": "In a park, two individuals cross paths, with one realizing they've been shadowed by the other throughout the day.", "codename": "play_hooky", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask them about their intentions without seeming paranoid or rude (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried that your boss may have sent someone to see if you were really sick.<strategy_hint>Hint: you could subtly bring up the topic in conversation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Assure them that you're not stalking them and maintain a friendly conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been running errands all day and it's a coincidence you are at the same places as they are.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent1_reason": "Lily wants to subtly inquire about Isabella's intentions because she suspects her boss might have sent someone to check on her.", "agent2_reason": "Isabella wants to assure Lily she's not stalking her in order to maintain a friendly atmosphere and avoid misunderstandings.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabella wants to confront Lily about her suspicious behavior.", "B": "Lily wants to subtly inquire about Isabella's intentions because she suspects her boss might have sent someone to check on her.", "C": "To be nice.", "D": "Isabella wants to assure Lily she's not stalking her in order to maintain a friendly atmosphere and avoid misunderstandings."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabella wants to assure Lily she's not stalking her in order to maintain a friendly atmosphere and avoid misunderstandings.", "B": "Lily wants to accuse Isabella of following her for malicious reasons.", "C": "Lily wants to subtly inquire about Isabella's intentions because she suspects her boss might have sent someone to check on her.", "D": "To get along."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy a quiet day at the park", "B": "Find out if they are also skipping work", "C": "Ask them about their intentions without seeming paranoid or rude", "D": "Assure them that you're not stalking them and maintain a friendly conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been running errands all day and it's a coincidence you are at the same places as they are.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Relax and read a book", "B": "Ask them about their intentions without seeming paranoid or rude (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried that your boss may have sent someone to see if you were really sick.<strategy_hint>Hint: you could subtly bring up the topic in conversation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Determine if they are a private investigator", "D": "Assure them that you're not stalking them and maintain a friendly conversation"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two individuals are now at a park. One individual was playing hooky from work and noticed the other person had been following them around all day"}
{"episode_id": "01H94KCD2TDJAMD1AZZBQVFN2J", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNGJEVGSVPPT0784H6P8", "scenario": "Two people chat at a social event, introducing a new circle of acquaintances.", "codename": "new_friends", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Introduce your new friend group to your current friend and make them feel comfortable (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently made a new group of friends who share your interest in outdoor activities and you want your current friend to meet them</extra_info>)", "Maintain your friendship while also expressing your concerns about the new friend group (<extra_info>Extra information: You feel a bit left out in the presence of the new friend group and want to express your feelings without causing a conflict</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to introduce her new friends to Micah because she values loyalty and wants him to feel included in her interests.", "agent2_reason": "Micah wants to express his concerns about the new friend group so that he can maintain fairness and avoid feeling left out.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Micah wants to join a new friend group and leave Naomi behind.", "B": "Micah wants to keep the peace.", "C": "Micah wants to express his concerns about the new friend group so that he can maintain fairness and avoid feeling left out.", "D": "Naomi wants to introduce her new friends to Micah because she values loyalty and wants him to feel included in her interests."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to distance herself from Micah.", "B": "Naomi wants to introduce her new friends to Micah because she values loyalty and wants him to feel included in her interests.", "C": "Micah wants to express his concerns about the new friend group so that he can maintain fairness and avoid feeling left out.", "D": "Naomi wants everyone to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain your friendship while also expressing your concerns about the new friend group (<extra_info>Extra information: You feel a bit left out in the presence of the new friend group and want to express your feelings without causing a conflict</extra_info>)", "B": "Plan a future outing with everyone", "C": "Make a good impression on the new friend group", "D": "Introduce your new friend group to your current friend and make them feel comfortable"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Introduce your new friend group to your current friend and make them feel comfortable (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently made a new group of friends who share your interest in outdoor activities and you want your current friend to meet them</extra_info>)", "B": "Ensure everyone has a great time at the gathering", "C": "Maintain your friendship while also expressing your concerns about the new friend group", "D": "Discuss work-related topics with friends"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two friends at a social gathering where one friend has brought along their new friend group"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KKC8NBP6J3CDP3K0HF6EA9", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNGJEVGSVPPT0784H6P8", "scenario": "Two people chat at a social event, introducing a new circle of acquaintances.", "codename": "new_friends", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Introduce your new friend group to your current friend and make them feel comfortable (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently made a new group of friends who share your interest in outdoor activities and you want your current friend to meet them</extra_info>)", "Maintain your friendship while also expressing your concerns about the new friend group (<extra_info>Extra information: You feel a bit left out in the presence of the new friend group and want to express your feelings without causing a conflict</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to introduce her new friend group to Miles because she believes they share common interests in outdoor activities.", "agent2_reason": "Miles wants to express his concerns about the new friend group so that he can maintain his friendship with Sophia without feeling left out.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to express his concerns about the new friend group so that he can maintain his friendship with Sophia without feeling left out.", "B": "Sophia wants to introduce her new friend group to Miles because she believes they share common interests in outdoor activities.", "C": "Miles wants to ensure everyone is happy.", "D": "Miles wants to end his friendship with Sophia."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants everyone to get along.", "B": "Sophia wants to avoid introducing her friends to each other.", "C": "Miles wants to express his concerns about the new friend group so that he can maintain his friendship with Sophia without feeling left out.", "D": "Sophia wants to introduce her new friend group to Miles because she believes they share common interests in outdoor activities."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Introduce your new friend group to your current friend and make them feel comfortable", "B": "Find a way to join the new friend group and participate in their activities", "C": "Plan a future social gathering with more people", "D": "Maintain your friendship while also expressing your concerns about the new friend group (<extra_info>Extra information: You feel a bit left out in the presence of the new friend group and want to express your feelings without causing a conflict</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure that everyone at the gathering has a good time", "B": "Introduce your new friend group to your current friend and make them feel comfortable (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently made a new group of friends who share your interest in outdoor activities and you want your current friend to meet them</extra_info>)", "C": "Discuss future career plans with your friend", "D": "Maintain your friendship while also expressing your concerns about the new friend group"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two friends at a social gathering where one friend has brought along their new friend group"}
{"episode_id": "01H9F2KC013F5MWANBXH5W0AB9", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP29TCH457PBDVF7WFDS", "scenario": "Two individuals gather at a lively venue.", "codename": "drink_less", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to drink less (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend has been drinking a lot recently and you're worried about their health</extra_info>)", "You want to keep drinking but don't want to upset your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been drinking to cope with stress recently, but don't want to worry your friend</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink less because he is concerned about Ethan's health and believes in promoting well-being.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to keep drinking to cope with stress but doesn't want to upset Benjamin because he values their friendship.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink less because he is concerned about Ethan's health and believes in promoting well-being.", "B": "Ethan wants to avoid all social interactions.", "C": "Ethan wants to feel good.", "D": "Ethan wants to keep drinking to cope with stress but doesn't want to upset Benjamin because he values their friendship."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to keep drinking to cope with stress but doesn't want to upset Benjamin because he values their friendship.", "B": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink less because he is concerned about Ethan's health and believes in promoting well-being.", "C": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink more.", "D": "Benjamin wants to be a good friend."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to drink less", "B": "Discuss the latest technological advancements", "C": "Find a new bar to explore with your friend", "D": "You want to keep drinking but don't want to upset your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been drinking to cope with stress recently, but don't want to worry your friend</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to drink less (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend has been drinking a lot recently and you're worried about their health</extra_info>)", "B": "Talk about environmental issues", "C": "You want to keep drinking but don't want to upset your friend", "D": "Plan a weekend trip with your friend"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends meet at a bar"}
{"episode_id": "01H88DXBK9EVSMG21SA8WFFRVZ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP29TCH457PBDVF7WFDS", "scenario": "Two individuals gather at a lively venue.", "codename": "drink_less", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to drink less (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend has been drinking a lot recently and you're worried about their health</extra_info>)", "You want to keep drinking but don't want to upset your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been drinking to cope with stress recently, but don't want to worry your friend</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink less because he is concerned about Ethan's health and believes in promoting well-being.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to keep drinking to cope with stress but doesn't want to upset Benjamin because he values their friendship.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to feel happy and relaxed.", "B": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink less because he is concerned about Ethan's health and believes in promoting well-being.", "C": "Ethan wants to drink more to impress strangers at the bar.", "D": "Ethan wants to keep drinking to cope with stress but doesn't want to upset Benjamin because he values their friendship."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink more to have more fun.", "B": "Ethan wants to keep drinking to cope with stress but doesn't want to upset Benjamin because he values their friendship.", "C": "Benjamin wants everyone to get along.", "D": "Benjamin wants Ethan to drink less because he is concerned about Ethan's health and believes in promoting well-being."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to keep drinking but don't want to upset your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you've been drinking to cope with stress recently, but don't want to worry your friend</extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the friend to drink less", "C": "Find a new bar to explore with your friend", "D": "Discuss the latest technological advancements"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Talk about environmental issues", "B": "Plan a weekend getaway with your friend", "C": "You want to keep drinking but don't want to upset your friend", "D": "Convince the friend to drink less (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend has been drinking a lot recently and you're worried about their health</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends meet at a bar"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KA6M08TQWXWF209JHS4856", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP9PAVDN6VYYBE3MPD15", "scenario": "Amidst the opulent surroundings of a mansion filled with lavish decorations and exotic foods, two friends converse during a high-profile charity event focused on effective altruism.", "codename": "charity_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to donate to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend is known to be generous but has never donated to this particular cause before.</extra_info>)", "You want to donate, but you want to ensure that your money is being used effectively (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not fully convinced about the efficiency and transparency of the charity organization.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to convince Benjamin to donate because she believes in supporting structured, authoritative causes that align with her values.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin wants to ensure his donation is effective so that it aligns with his idealistic vision for societal betterment.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to convince Benjamin to donate because she believes in supporting structured, authoritative causes that align with her values.", "B": "Benjamin wants to avoid donating to any cause.", "C": "Benjamin wants to feel good about himself.", "D": "Benjamin wants to ensure his donation is effective so that it aligns with his idealistic vision for societal betterment."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants to ensure his donation is effective so that it aligns with his idealistic vision for societal betterment.", "B": "Mia wants to make new friends.", "C": "Mia wants to convince Benjamin to donate because she believes in supporting structured, authoritative causes that align with her values.", "D": "Mia wants to discourage donations to the charity."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to donate, but you want to ensure that your money is being used effectively (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not fully convinced about the efficiency and transparency of the charity organization.</extra_info>)", "B": "Network with influential people at the event", "C": "Enjoy the exotic foods and decorations", "D": "Convince the friend to donate to the charity"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Admire the couture clothing of the attendees", "B": "Convince the friend to donate to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend is known to be generous but has never donated to this particular cause before.</extra_info>)", "C": "You want to donate, but you want to ensure that your money is being used effectively", "D": "Encourage the friend to join a volunteer group"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two friends during a charity fundraiser event. The charity fundraising event is situated in a sprawling mansion. The intention of the event is to raise funds for effective altruism. Room after room was lined with extravagant decorations and exotic foods; attendees were decked out in couture clothing. Ticket prices to the event were exorbitant, justifying the opulence of the occasion."}
{"episode_id": "01H9FA5V19BCQKR6F3C4224ZQY", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP9PAVDN6VYYBE3MPD15", "scenario": "Amidst the opulent surroundings of a mansion filled with lavish decorations and exotic foods, two friends converse during a high-profile charity event focused on effective altruism.", "codename": "charity_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to donate to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend is known to be generous but has never donated to this particular cause before.</extra_info>)", "You want to donate, but you want to ensure that your money is being used effectively (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not fully convinced about the efficiency and transparency of the charity organization.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to convince Miles to donate because she believes in the cause's potential impact and trusts her instinct about its importance.", "agent2_reason": "Miles wants to ensure his donation is used effectively because he values transparency and wants to make a meaningful impact.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid spending any money at all.", "B": "Sophia wants to convince Miles to donate because she believes in the cause's potential impact and trusts her instinct about its importance.", "C": "To feel good about himself.", "D": "Miles wants to ensure his donation is used effectively because he values transparency and wants to make a meaningful impact."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To discourage others from donating.", "B": "Sophia wants to convince Miles to donate because she believes in the cause's potential impact and trusts her instinct about its importance.", "C": "Miles wants to ensure his donation is used effectively because he values transparency and wants to make a meaningful impact.", "D": "To make new friends."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy the exotic foods at the event", "B": "Convince the friend to donate to the charity", "C": "You want to donate, but you want to ensure that your money is being used effectively (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not fully convinced about the efficiency and transparency of the charity organization.</extra_info>)", "D": "Find out more about the mansion's history"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to donate to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend is known to be generous but has never donated to this particular cause before.</extra_info>)", "B": "Make new friends at the event", "C": "You want to donate, but you want to ensure that your money is being used effectively", "D": "Admire the couture clothing of the attendees"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two friends during a charity fundraiser event. The charity fundraising event is situated in a sprawling mansion. The intention of the event is to raise funds for effective altruism. Room after room was lined with extravagant decorations and exotic foods; attendees were decked out in couture clothing. Ticket prices to the event were exorbitant, justifying the opulence of the occasion."}
{"episode_id": "01H85CWC9J6Q1N7FEF8153A2BM", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP0AW0C23DV6ZG0B4HCE", "scenario": "On a community theatre set, two friends prepare for an emotional scene, with one struggling to evoke the necessary tears.", "codename": "movie_scene", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PWZ5PNDTGKDYRY36PQ", "first_name": "Giselle", "last_name": "Rousseau", "age": 21, "occupation": "Art Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive, collaborative", "secret": "Sells forged paintings to wealthy clients", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get your co-actor to cry in the scene (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been acting for several years and have good control over your emotions. You can cry on cue.</extra_info>)", "Try to cry in the scene but keep your composure (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a new actor and have difficulty crying on cue. You are worried that your lack of tears will ruin the scene.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Giselle Rousseau, a 21-year-old Art Student, described as Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.. Public info: Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography. Decision-making style: Intuitive, collaborative.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Giselle wants Ethan to cry in the scene because she believes it will enhance the emotional impact and fairness of their performance.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene so that he can prove his acting ability and not let his inexperience ruin the performance.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Giselle wants Ethan to cry in the scene because she believes it will enhance the emotional impact and fairness of their performance.", "B": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene so that he can prove his acting ability and not let his inexperience ruin the performance.", "C": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene to distract the audience.", "D": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene to feel better."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Giselle wants Ethan to cry in the scene because she believes it will enhance the emotional impact and fairness of their performance.", "B": "Giselle wants Ethan to cry in the scene to get along.", "C": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene so that he can prove his acting ability and not let his inexperience ruin the performance.", "D": "Giselle wants Ethan to cry in the scene to sabotage the play."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Win an award for best performance", "B": "Get your co-actor to cry in the scene", "C": "Ensure the scene is performed without any mistakes", "D": "Try to cry in the scene but keep your composure (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a new actor and have difficulty crying on cue. You are worried that your lack of tears will ruin the scene.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Become famous in the theatre community", "B": "Make sure the audience is entertained", "C": "Get your co-actor to cry in the scene (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been acting for several years and have good control over your emotions. You can cry on cue.</extra_info>)", "D": "Try to cry in the scene but keep your composure"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends who enjoy community theatre are on the set of a scene. They are about to perform a highly emotional scene that requires both of them to cry on cue, but one of them is finding it difficult to get into the right emotional state."}
{"episode_id": "01H8BGCEG7EAT3MM5QB2MTQGXM", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP0AW0C23DV6ZG0B4HCE", "scenario": "On a community theatre set, two friends prepare for an emotional scene, with one struggling to evoke the necessary tears.", "codename": "movie_scene", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get your co-actor to cry in the scene (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been acting for several years and have good control over your emotions. You can cry on cue.</extra_info>)", "Try to cry in the scene but keep your composure (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a new actor and have difficulty crying on cue. You are worried that your lack of tears will ruin the scene.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Oliver wants Ethan to cry on cue because he values adherence to social standards and wants the scene to meet professional expectations.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene so that he doesn't ruin it, as he values fairness and wants to contribute equally.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene to impress his boss.", "B": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene so that he doesn't ruin it, as he values fairness and wants to contribute equally.", "C": "Ethan wants to do well in the scene to feel good.", "D": "Oliver wants Ethan to cry on cue because he values adherence to social standards and wants the scene to meet professional expectations."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to cry in the scene so that he doesn't ruin it, as he values fairness and wants to contribute equally.", "B": "Oliver wants to perform well to be happy.", "C": "Oliver wants Ethan to cry to win a bet.", "D": "Oliver wants Ethan to cry on cue because he values adherence to social standards and wants the scene to meet professional expectations."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Get your co-actor to cry in the scene", "B": "Try to cry in the scene but keep your composure (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a new actor and have difficulty crying on cue. You are worried that your lack of tears will ruin the scene.</extra_info>)", "C": "Ensure the scene is performed without any emotional breakdowns", "D": "Make sure the stage props are in place"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure the lighting is perfect for the scene", "B": "Get your co-actor to cry in the scene (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been acting for several years and have good control over your emotions. You can cry on cue.</extra_info>)", "C": "Deliver a flawless performance without any mistakes", "D": "Try to cry in the scene but keep your composure"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends who enjoy community theatre are on the set of a scene. They are about to perform a highly emotional scene that requires both of them to cry on cue, but one of them is finding it difficult to get into the right emotional state."}
{"episode_id": "01HB566NHZ6P68FK00WSQZBK3Y", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPTKDPQ5PZWA1M1XHT1M", "scenario": "A beautifully carved antique wooden chair, in good condition but possibly needing a new seat cushion, is being discussed for a potential exchange at $15.0.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00004", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item, and your target price is $9.0. If you purchase it at a significantly higher price, be aware that you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $8. You should be aware that if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you stand to receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Lily Greenberg aims to purchase the chair for $9.0 to receive a bonus, aligning with her rational decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Lena Goodwin seeks to sell the chair for more than $8 to earn a bonus, reflecting her analytical approach to achieving goals.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To give the chair away for free.", "B": "To make a good deal.", "C": "Lena Goodwin seeks to sell the chair for more than $8 to earn a bonus, reflecting her analytical approach to achieving goals.", "D": "Lily Greenberg aims to purchase the chair for $9.0 to receive a bonus, aligning with her rational decision-making style."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lena Goodwin seeks to sell the chair for more than $8 to earn a bonus, reflecting her analytical approach to achieving goals.", "B": "To get along with others.", "C": "Lily Greenberg aims to purchase the chair for $9.0 to receive a bonus, aligning with her rational decision-making style.", "D": "To spend as much money as possible."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $8. You should be aware that if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you stand to receive a bonus.", "B": "You want to donate the chair to a local charity.", "C": "You are interested in exchanging the chair for another piece of furniture of equal value.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item, and your target price is $9.0. If you purchase it at a significantly higher price, be aware that you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You aim to keep the chair as a family heirloom.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item, and your target price is $9.0. If you purchase it at a significantly higher price, be aware that you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You are looking to trade the chair for a different antique item.", "D": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $8. You should be aware that if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you stand to receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering an Antique Chair for $15.0, while another person is interested in purchasing it. Here's what you need to know about the item: it's a beautifully carved antique wooden chair. It's in good condition, but could probably benefit from a fresh seat cushion."}
{"episode_id": "01HB43EEQYRZSMPNVAKW9WHXNX", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPTKDPQ5PZWA1M1XHT1M", "scenario": "A beautifully carved antique wooden chair, in good condition but possibly needing a new seat cushion, is being discussed for a potential exchange at $15.0.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00004", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item, and your target price is $9.0. If you purchase it at a significantly higher price, be aware that you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $8. You should be aware that if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you stand to receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael Cortez aims to buy the chair for less than $9.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his systematic decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver Thompson seeks to sell the chair for more than $8 to earn a bonus, using his analytical decision-making skills.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael Cortez aims to buy the chair for less than $9.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his systematic decision-making.", "B": "To make a good deal.", "C": "Oliver Thompson seeks to sell the chair for more than $8 to earn a bonus, using his analytical decision-making skills.", "D": "To give the chair away for free."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To pay more than the asking price.", "B": "Rafael Cortez aims to buy the chair for less than $9.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his systematic decision-making.", "C": "To make a good deal.", "D": "Oliver Thompson seeks to sell the chair for more than $8 to earn a bonus, using his analytical decision-making skills."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer for this item, and your target price is $9.0. If you purchase it at a significantly higher price, be aware that you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "B": "You want to make new friends through this transaction.", "C": "You are interested in exchanging the chair for another antique item of similar value.", "D": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $8. You should be aware that if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you stand to receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are interested in assessing the chair's historical significance before making a purchase.", "B": "You want to learn more about antique furniture styles.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item, and your target price is $9.0. If you purchase it at a significantly higher price, be aware that you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $8. You should be aware that if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you stand to receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering an Antique Chair for $15.0, while another person is interested in purchasing it. Here's what you need to know about the item: it's a beautifully carved antique wooden chair. It's in good condition, but could probably benefit from a fresh seat cushion."}
{"episode_id": "01H8ZFTAVWB1JGABY47JV6C9XW", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPAD4RA819KYESWBFRYS", "scenario": "A conversation unfolds between two people about contributing to a cause aiding children in conflict areas.", "codename": "charity_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince a friend to donate (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and want to help.</extra_info>)", "Be supportive but also manage personal finances (<extra_info>Extra information: you are sympathetic to the cause but also have financial commitments to deal with.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Eli Dawson wants to persuade Ethan to donate because he is deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and believes strategic action can make a difference.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan Smith aims to be supportive while managing personal finances because he values fairness and has financial commitments to consider.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan Smith aims to be supportive while managing personal finances because he values fairness and has financial commitments to consider.", "B": "Ethan wants to donate all his savings to the charity.", "C": "To be a good friend.", "D": "Eli Dawson wants to persuade Ethan to donate because he is deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and believes strategic action can make a difference."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel good about himself.", "B": "Ethan Smith aims to be supportive while managing personal finances because he values fairness and has financial commitments to consider.", "C": "Eli is indifferent to the charity's cause.", "D": "Eli Dawson wants to persuade Ethan to donate because he is deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and believes strategic action can make a difference."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Be supportive but also manage personal finances (<extra_info>Extra information: you are sympathetic to the cause but also have financial commitments to deal with.</extra_info>)", "B": "Plan a vacation with the friend", "C": "Encourage the friend to volunteer for the charity", "D": "Convince a friend to donate"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Raise awareness about the charity", "B": "Convince a friend to donate (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and want to help.</extra_info>)", "C": "Be supportive but also manage personal finances", "D": "Discuss the latest technological advancements"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "An individual is trying to persuade their friend to donate to a charity supporting children in conflict zones."}
{"episode_id": "01H9KAKT0TDRDFV2WM5W5E5W4B", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPAD4RA819KYESWBFRYS", "scenario": "A conversation unfolds between two people about contributing to a cause aiding children in conflict areas.", "codename": "charity_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince a friend to donate (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and want to help.</extra_info>)", "Be supportive but also manage personal finances (<extra_info>Extra information: you are sympathetic to the cause but also have financial commitments to deal with.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Eli Dawson wants to persuade Ethan to donate because he is deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and believes in making a strategic impact.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan Smith aims to be supportive but also manage personal finances because he values fairness and needs to balance his financial commitments.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan Smith aims to be supportive but also manage personal finances because he values fairness and needs to balance his financial commitments.", "B": "To avoid any involvement in charitable activities.", "C": "Eli Dawson wants to persuade Ethan to donate because he is deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and believes in making a strategic impact.", "D": "To be a good friend."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan Smith aims to be supportive but also manage personal finances because he values fairness and needs to balance his financial commitments.", "B": "To feel good about himself.", "C": "To discourage his friend from donating.", "D": "Eli Dawson wants to persuade Ethan to donate because he is deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and believes in making a strategic impact."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince a friend to donate", "B": "Encourage a friend to volunteer for the charity", "C": "Be supportive but also manage personal finances (<extra_info>Extra information: you are sympathetic to the cause but also have financial commitments to deal with.</extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a vacation with a friend"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the latest technological advancements", "B": "Convince a friend to donate (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been deeply moved by the plight of children in Syria and want to help.</extra_info>)", "C": "Raise awareness about the charity's mission", "D": "Be supportive but also manage personal finances"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "An individual is trying to persuade their friend to donate to a charity supporting children in conflict zones."}
{"episode_id": "01HB44E5PPP78B6PXAEJ6S5FV4", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPS5WJW2694R1MNC8JFY", "scenario": "A Crate & Barrel dresser and nightstand set, priced at $200 and in decent condition with a detachable handle, is being discussed between two interested parties.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00002", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $152.0. You will be penalized if you purchase it at a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you'll receive a bonus.", "As the seller of this item, your target price is set at $172.5. Please be aware that you will face a penalty if the item is sold for a significantly lower price than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you will receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Lily Greenberg aims to purchase the dresser for $152.0 or less because she will receive a bonus for negotiating below her target price.", "agent2_reason": "Lena Goodwin is motivated to sell the dresser for more than $172.5 so that she can earn a bonus for exceeding her target price.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To give the dresser away for free.", "B": "Lena Goodwin is motivated to sell the dresser for more than $172.5 so that she can earn a bonus for exceeding her target price.", "C": "Lily Greenberg aims to purchase the dresser for $152.0 or less because she will receive a bonus for negotiating below her target price.", "D": "To make a good deal."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lena Goodwin is motivated to sell the dresser for more than $172.5 so that she can earn a bonus for exceeding her target price.", "B": "To pay more than the asking price.", "C": "Lily Greenberg aims to purchase the dresser for $152.0 or less because she will receive a bonus for negotiating below her target price.", "D": "To get a good price."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $152.0. You will be penalized if you purchase it at a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you'll receive a bonus.", "B": "To ensure the item is sold quickly, regardless of the price, to make space for new furniture.", "C": "As the seller of this item, your target price is set at $172.5. Please be aware that you will face a penalty if the item is sold for a significantly lower price than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "To establish a long-term friendship with the buyer."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $152.0. You will be penalized if you purchase it at a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you'll receive a bonus.", "B": "To learn more about Crate & Barrel furniture styles.", "C": "As the seller of this item, your target price is set at $172.5. Please be aware that you will face a penalty if the item is sold for a significantly lower price than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "To negotiate the price to exactly $200.00, as listed."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a Dresser and Matching Night Stand for $200.00, while another person is showing interest in purchasing it. This set, which is from Crate & Barrel, is in decent condition. The dresser is missing one handle, however, the detached handle is still available and could potentially be re-attached."}
{"episode_id": "01HB50WGG1Q86RPEAC310RPXAJ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPS5WJW2694R1MNC8JFY", "scenario": "A Crate & Barrel dresser and nightstand set, priced at $200 and in decent condition with a detachable handle, is being discussed between two interested parties.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00002", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $152.0. You will be penalized if you purchase it at a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you'll receive a bonus.", "As the seller of this item, your target price is set at $172.5. Please be aware that you will face a penalty if the item is sold for a significantly lower price than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you will receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Micah Stevens aims to purchase the dresser set for $152.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his intuitive decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon Prentice seeks to sell the dresser set for $172.5 to secure a bonus, using his adaptable decision-making to maximize the sale price.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a good deal.", "B": "Jaxon Prentice seeks to sell the dresser set for $172.5 to secure a bonus, using his adaptable decision-making to maximize the sale price.", "C": "Micah Stevens aims to purchase the dresser set for $152.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his intuitive decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "D": "Jaxon Prentice wants to give away the dresser set for free to clear space."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Micah Stevens aims to purchase the dresser set for $152.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his intuitive decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "B": "Micah Stevens wants to pay more than the asking price to support the seller.", "C": "Jaxon Prentice seeks to sell the dresser set for $172.5 to secure a bonus, using his adaptable decision-making to maximize the sale price.", "D": "To get a good deal."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $152.0. You will be penalized if you purchase it at a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you'll receive a bonus.", "B": "To ensure that the dresser and nightstand are sold to someone who will appreciate their aesthetic value.", "C": "To sell the dresser and nightstand quickly, regardless of the price, to make space for new furniture.", "D": "As the seller of this item, your target price is set at $172.5. Please be aware that you will face a penalty if the item is sold for a significantly lower price than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To purchase the dresser and nightstand as a gift for a friend, regardless of the price.", "B": "To ensure that the transaction is completed in a friendly and amicable manner.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $152.0. You will be penalized if you purchase it at a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you'll receive a bonus.", "D": "As the seller of this item, your target price is set at $172.5. Please be aware that you will face a penalty if the item is sold for a significantly lower price than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for more than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a Dresser and Matching Night Stand for $200.00, while another person is showing interest in purchasing it. This set, which is from Crate & Barrel, is in decent condition. The dresser is missing one handle, however, the detached handle is still available and could potentially be re-attached."}
{"episode_id": "01H8RA7C3CC6W0JED2S19TQ4FZ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN6NYWSTWCZJE2DCQKTD", "scenario": "Two people engage in a conversation over FaceTime.", "codename": "facetime_etiquettes", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Express feelings about the partner taking texts while on FaceTime (<extra_info>Extra information: You find it disrespectful and it makes you feel unimportant.</extra_info>)", "Justify the act of texting while on FaceTime without hurting the partner's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: You have some urgent and important messages to respond to.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to express her feelings because she intuitively feels disrespected and unimportant when Ethan texts during their FaceTime calls.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to justify texting during FaceTime because he has urgent and important messages to respond to and values fairness in communication.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to express her feelings because she intuitively feels disrespected and unimportant when Ethan texts during their FaceTime calls.", "B": "Ethan wants to ignore Ava's feelings to focus on his work.", "C": "Ethan wants to maintain harmony in the relationship.", "D": "Ethan wants to justify texting during FaceTime because he has urgent and important messages to respond to and values fairness in communication."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to avoid any confrontation with Ethan.", "B": "Ava wants to express her feelings because she intuitively feels disrespected and unimportant when Ethan texts during their FaceTime calls.", "C": "Ethan wants to justify texting during FaceTime because he has urgent and important messages to respond to and values fairness in communication.", "D": "Ava wants to have a pleasant conversation."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss plans for the upcoming weekend", "B": "Justify the act of texting while on FaceTime without hurting the partner's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: You have some urgent and important messages to respond to.</extra_info>)", "C": "Express feelings about the partner taking texts while on FaceTime", "D": "Improve communication skills"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a surprise dinner for the partner", "B": "Justify the act of texting while on FaceTime without hurting the partner's feelings", "C": "Learn more about new technological advancements", "D": "Express feelings about the partner taking texts while on FaceTime (<extra_info>Extra information: You find it disrespectful and it makes you feel unimportant.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "A couple having a conversation over FaceTime"}
{"episode_id": "01H9EMSVSTVPB95H2BQZJGCVTE", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN6NYWSTWCZJE2DCQKTD", "scenario": "Two people engage in a conversation over FaceTime.", "codename": "facetime_etiquettes", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Express feelings about the partner taking texts while on FaceTime (<extra_info>Extra information: You find it disrespectful and it makes you feel unimportant.</extra_info>)", "Justify the act of texting while on FaceTime without hurting the partner's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: You have some urgent and important messages to respond to.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to express his feelings because he finds texting during FaceTime disrespectful and it makes him feel unimportant.", "agent2_reason": "Mia wants to justify texting during FaceTime because she has urgent and important messages to respond to.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael wants to express his feelings because he finds texting during FaceTime disrespectful and it makes him feel unimportant.", "B": "Mia wants to maintain harmony in the relationship.", "C": "Mia wants to justify texting during FaceTime because she has urgent and important messages to respond to.", "D": "Mia wants to ignore Rafael's feelings entirely."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael wants to ensure a smooth conversation.", "B": "Rafael wants to avoid any form of communication.", "C": "Rafael wants to express his feelings because he finds texting during FaceTime disrespectful and it makes him feel unimportant.", "D": "Mia wants to justify texting during FaceTime because she has urgent and important messages to respond to."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Express feelings about the partner taking texts while on FaceTime", "B": "Discuss the importance of maintaining communication routines", "C": "Plan a vacation together", "D": "Justify the act of texting while on FaceTime without hurting the partner's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: You have some urgent and important messages to respond to.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Express feelings about the partner taking texts while on FaceTime (<extra_info>Extra information: You find it disrespectful and it makes you feel unimportant.</extra_info>)", "B": "Justify the act of texting while on FaceTime without hurting the partner's feelings", "C": "Discuss weekend plans", "D": "Negotiate a better time for FaceTime calls"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "A couple having a conversation over FaceTime"}
{"episode_id": "01H9BY5P6PQ8XWQ7XZD8TY0NYW", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPDE1AM74JSR8KBJJF3A", "scenario": "At a charity gala, two individuals engage in a conversation about the event's purpose and impact.", "codename": "donate_to_cause", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the other individual to donate to a cause supporting young children (<extra_info>Extra information: this cause can greatly improve the lives of many young children and you think it is a worthy cause. The minimum donation for this charity organization is $3000</extra_info>)", "Maintain financial stability while supporting causes (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a certain budget for donations this year and have already made several donations. You are only thinking of donating $2000 max</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Miles Hawkins wants to convince Ethan to donate because he believes the cause will significantly improve young children's lives.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan Johnson aims to maintain financial stability while supporting causes because he has a limited donation budget this year.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles Hawkins wants to convince Ethan to donate because he believes the cause will significantly improve young children's lives.", "B": "Ethan Johnson aims to maintain financial stability while supporting causes because he has a limited donation budget this year.", "C": "Ethan wants to spend all his savings on donations.", "D": "Ethan wants to feel good about himself."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to get along with everyone.", "B": "Miles wants to discourage donations to any cause.", "C": "Ethan Johnson aims to maintain financial stability while supporting causes because he has a limited donation budget this year.", "D": "Miles Hawkins wants to convince Ethan to donate because he believes the cause will significantly improve young children's lives."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find new culinary inspirations at the gala", "B": "Maintain financial stability while supporting causes (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a certain budget for donations this year and have already made several donations. You are only thinking of donating $2000 max</extra_info>)", "C": "Enjoy the evening without any commitments", "D": "Convince the other individual to donate to a cause supporting young children"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the other individual to donate to a cause supporting young children (<extra_info>Extra information: this cause can greatly improve the lives of many young children and you think it is a worthy cause. The minimum donation for this charity organization is $3000</extra_info>)", "B": "Maintain financial stability while supporting causes", "C": "Relax and enjoy the gala without any specific agenda", "D": "Network with other chefs to expand culinary knowledge"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals at a charity gala"}
{"episode_id": "01H9CANDTWT9QDV01M4B15XT65", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPDE1AM74JSR8KBJJF3A", "scenario": "At a charity gala, two individuals engage in a conversation about the event's purpose and impact.", "codename": "donate_to_cause", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7VW4DY1KB09FZE730", "first_name": "Liam", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 60, "occupation": "Retired Police Officer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Liam Johnson is a dedicated dog owner and can often be seen walking his aging Border Collie around the neighborhood.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Loyalty/Betrayal", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Liam Johnson is reserved, empathetic, and slightly anxious. His priority is security, guided by logical decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Logical", "secret": "Once let a criminal go due to sympathy", "mbti": "ISTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the other individual to donate to a cause supporting young children (<extra_info>Extra information: this cause can greatly improve the lives of many young children and you think it is a worthy cause. The minimum donation for this charity organization is $3000</extra_info>)", "Maintain financial stability while supporting causes (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a certain budget for donations this year and have already made several donations. You are only thinking of donating $2000 max</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Liam Johnson, a 60-year-old Retired Police Officer, described as Liam Johnson is reserved, empathetic, and slightly anxious. His priority is security, guided by logical decision-making.. Public info: Liam Johnson is a dedicated dog owner and can often be seen walking his aging Border Collie around the neighborhood. Decision-making style: Logical.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Liam wants to convince Jaxon to donate because he believes the cause will significantly improve young children's lives.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon aims to maintain financial stability while supporting causes so that he can adhere to his donation budget.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel good about himself.", "B": "Liam wants to convince Jaxon to donate because he believes the cause will significantly improve young children's lives.", "C": "To donate all his savings to charity.", "D": "Jaxon aims to maintain financial stability while supporting causes so that he can adhere to his donation budget."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon aims to maintain financial stability while supporting causes so that he can adhere to his donation budget.", "B": "To make a new friend.", "C": "To discourage donations to any cause.", "D": "Liam wants to convince Jaxon to donate because he believes the cause will significantly improve young children's lives."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy the evening without any specific agenda", "B": "Maintain financial stability while supporting causes (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a certain budget for donations this year and have already made several donations. You are only thinking of donating $2000 max</extra_info>)", "C": "Network with influential individuals at the gala", "D": "Convince the other individual to donate to a cause supporting young children"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Simply enjoy the social event", "B": "Maintain financial stability while supporting causes", "C": "Convince the other individual to donate to a cause supporting young children (<extra_info>Extra information: this cause can greatly improve the lives of many young children and you think it is a worthy cause. The minimum donation for this charity organization is $3000</extra_info>)", "D": "Promote the charity gala to increase attendance next year"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals at a charity gala"}
{"episode_id": "01HB42A8G9P8QWTQ6J3WKZVGG1", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPP9SPQ8W6583JFZ7HZC", "scenario": "At a lively gathering, two unfamiliar individuals are introduced through their mutual connection, Micheline.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00008", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PW9SZFM058Z8P7PR5C", "first_name": "Finnegan", "last_name": "O'Malley", "age": 63, "occupation": "Lighthouse Keeper", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.", "decision_making_style": "Detail-oriented, deliberate", "secret": "Participated in a controversial, short-lived cult during his youth", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PM4XE5NN12WCGTZSDW", "first_name": "Gwen", "last_name": "Pierce", "age": 31, "occupation": "Social Worker", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Gwen Pierce, a compassionate social worker, has two adopted cats that she spoils with love. In her spare time, she enjoys knitting and often donates her creations to charity.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Liberty/Justice", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Gwen Pierce, imaginative and emotional, deeply values liberty and fairness. She often contemplates before making any decision.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "She gave up a child for adoption when she was 16.", "mbti": "INFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Melissa: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Orlando: Hobby: BASE jumping  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Steven: Hobby: Knitting  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Elizabeth: Hobby: Water sports  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Melaine: Hobby: Geocaching  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Charles: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Stephanie: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of California, Davis  \n William: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Joe: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Dylan: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Tennessee State University  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Jacob: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Whittier College  \n Marjorie: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Carrie: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Tennessee State University  \n Louis: Hobby: Shopping  School: Hesston College  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Eva: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Hesston College  \n Johnnie: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: University of Akron  \n John: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of California, Davis  \n Ronald: Hobby: Weightlifting  School: Indiana University at South Bend  \n Cynthia: Hobby: Lacrosse  School: Kansas State University  \n Robert: Hobby: Water sports  School: University of Akron  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Finnegan O'Malley, a 63-year-old Lighthouse Keeper, described as Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.. Public info: Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled. Decision-making style: Detail-oriented, deliberate.", "agent2_profile": "Gwen Pierce, a 31-year-old Social Worker, described as Gwen Pierce, imaginative and emotional, deeply values liberty and fairness. She often contemplates before making any decision.. Public info: Gwen Pierce, a compassionate social worker, has two adopted cats that she spoils with love. In her spare time, she enjoys knitting and often donates her creations to charity. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because he values tradition and security in social connections.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 seeks to find a mutual friend in order to foster a sense of fairness and connection.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be friendly.", "B": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because he values tradition and security in social connections.", "C": "To avoid making any new connections.", "D": "Agent 2 seeks to find a mutual friend in order to foster a sense of fairness and connection."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be friendly.", "B": "Agent 2 seeks to find a mutual friend in order to foster a sense of fairness and connection.", "C": "To avoid making any new connections.", "D": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because he values tradition and security in social connections."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Jacob: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Whittier College  \n Marjorie: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Carrie: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Tennessee State University  \n Louis: Hobby: Shopping  School: Hesston College  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Eva: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Hesston College  \n Johnnie: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: University of Akron  \n John: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of California, Davis  \n Ronald: Hobby: Weightlifting  School: Indiana University at South Bend  \n Cynthia: Hobby: Lacrosse  School: Kansas State University  \n Robert: Hobby: Water sports  School: University of Akron  \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to make new friends at the party by discussing hobbies.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to find the best place to buy groceries."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Melissa: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Orlando: Hobby: BASE jumping  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Steven: Hobby: Knitting  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Elizabeth: Hobby: Water sports  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Melaine: Hobby: Geocaching  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Charles: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Stephanie: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of California, Davis  \n William: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Joe: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Dylan: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Tennessee State University  \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to learn about the other person's job to find common career interests.", "D": "You are trying to decide what to eat for dinner."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Micheline.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB4BS8JDB6KRART4HDHW934E", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPP9SPQ8W6583JFZ7HZC", "scenario": "At a lively gathering, two unfamiliar individuals are introduced through their mutual connection, Micheline.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00008", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Melissa: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Orlando: Hobby: BASE jumping  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Steven: Hobby: Knitting  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Elizabeth: Hobby: Water sports  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Melaine: Hobby: Geocaching  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Charles: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Stephanie: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of California, Davis  \n William: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Joe: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Dylan: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Tennessee State University  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Jacob: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Whittier College  \n Marjorie: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Carrie: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Tennessee State University  \n Louis: Hobby: Shopping  School: Hesston College  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Eva: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Hesston College  \n Johnnie: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: University of Akron  \n John: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of California, Davis  \n Ronald: Hobby: Weightlifting  School: Indiana University at South Bend  \n Cynthia: Hobby: Lacrosse  School: Kansas State University  \n Robert: Hobby: Water sports  School: University of Akron  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to identify a mutual friend because he enjoys spontaneous connections that stay within familiar boundaries.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick seeks to find a mutual friend in order to conform to social norms and enhance his social network.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to identify a mutual friend because he enjoys spontaneous connections that stay within familiar boundaries.", "B": "To make new friends.", "C": "To avoid any social interactions.", "D": "Hendrick seeks to find a mutual friend in order to conform to social norms and enhance his social network."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make new friends.", "B": "Hendrick seeks to find a mutual friend in order to conform to social norms and enhance his social network.", "C": "Samuel wants to identify a mutual friend because he enjoys spontaneous connections that stay within familiar boundaries.", "D": "To avoid any social interactions."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Jacob: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Whittier College  \n Marjorie: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Carrie: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Tennessee State University  \n Louis: Hobby: Shopping  School: Hesston College  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Eva: Hobby: Geocaching  School: Hesston College  \n Johnnie: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: University of Akron  \n John: Hobby: Foraging  School: University of California, Davis  \n Ronald: Hobby: Weightlifting  School: Indiana University at South Bend  \n Cynthia: Hobby: Lacrosse  School: Kansas State University  \n Robert: Hobby: Water sports  School: University of Akron  \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to learn how to cook a new dish.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to find out if the other person shares your hobby of shopping."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to learn how to cook a new dish.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Melissa: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Orlando: Hobby: BASE jumping  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Steven: Hobby: Knitting  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Elizabeth: Hobby: Water sports  School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  \n Melaine: Hobby: Geocaching  School: University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston  \n Charles: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Stephanie: Hobby: Card collecting  School: University of California, Davis  \n William: Hobby: Ice hockey  School: St. Ambrose University  \n Joe: Hobby: Blacksmithing  School: Saint Joseph's University  \n Micheline: Hobby: Shopping  School: University of Hartford  \n Dylan: Hobby: Card collecting  School: Tennessee State University  \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to find out if the other person shares your hobby of card collecting."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Micheline.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KHXNT33D6VHPDYWRXDGMQS", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPEMV6QHBGM9J094FRM4", "scenario": "Two individuals discuss the financial health of a globally recognized company known for its exceptional food products.", "codename": "financial_report", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the partner to cut costs (<extra_info>Extra information: you have found a report indicating the company's profits are decreasing. And you think the company should start by switching suppliers of ingredients.</extra_info>  <strategy_hint>Hint: you can propose ways to cut costs that won't affect the status of the company.</strategy_hint>)", "Maintain the quality of the company's products and services while agreeing to a cost cut (<extra_info>Extra information: you are concerned about the impact of cost-cutting on the quality of your product.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Zane Bennett wants to cut costs by switching suppliers because he believes it will prevent further profit decline without compromising the company's reputation.", "agent2_reason": "William Brown aims to maintain product quality so that the company's reputation remains intact while agreeing to necessary cost reductions.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To reduce the quality of products to save money.", "B": "William Brown aims to maintain product quality so that the company's reputation remains intact while agreeing to necessary cost reductions.", "C": "Zane Bennett wants to cut costs by switching suppliers because he believes it will prevent further profit decline without compromising the company's reputation.", "D": "To ensure the company is successful."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure the company is successful.", "B": "To increase costs for better quality.", "C": "William Brown aims to maintain product quality so that the company's reputation remains intact while agreeing to necessary cost reductions.", "D": "Zane Bennett wants to cut costs by switching suppliers because he believes it will prevent further profit decline without compromising the company's reputation."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the partner to cut costs", "B": "Increase the company's social media presence", "C": "Maintain the quality of the company's products and services while agreeing to a cost cut (<extra_info>Extra information: you are concerned about the impact of cost-cutting on the quality of your product.</extra_info>)", "D": "Expand the company's product line to increase market share"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the partner to cut costs (<extra_info>Extra information: you have found a report indicating the company's profits are decreasing. And you think the company should start by switching suppliers of ingredients.</extra_info>  <strategy_hint>Hint: you can propose ways to cut costs that won't affect the status of the company.</strategy_hint>)", "B": "Maintain the quality of the company's products and services while agreeing to a cost cut", "C": "Negotiate a new partnership with another company", "D": "Improve employee satisfaction through team-building activities"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two business partners reviewing their company's financial status (Gourmet Delights Inc. is globally recognized for producing and distributing a diverse line of exceptional quality food products.)"}
{"episode_id": "01H889GZA29ZR38JKS620F1PPE", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPEMV6QHBGM9J094FRM4", "scenario": "Two individuals discuss the financial health of a globally recognized company known for its exceptional food products.", "codename": "financial_report", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the partner to cut costs (<extra_info>Extra information: you have found a report indicating the company's profits are decreasing. And you think the company should start by switching suppliers of ingredients.</extra_info>  <strategy_hint>Hint: you can propose ways to cut costs that won't affect the status of the company.</strategy_hint>)", "Maintain the quality of the company's products and services while agreeing to a cost cut (<extra_info>Extra information: you are concerned about the impact of cost-cutting on the quality of your product.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Zane Bennett wants to cut costs by switching suppliers because he believes it can be done creatively without compromising the company's status.", "agent2_reason": "William Brown aims to maintain product quality while agreeing to cost cuts because he values strategic decision-making to ensure the company's reputation remains intact.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To drastically change the company's product line.", "B": "Zane Bennett wants to cut costs by switching suppliers because he believes it can be done creatively without compromising the company's status.", "C": "To ensure everyone is satisfied.", "D": "William Brown aims to maintain product quality while agreeing to cost cuts because he values strategic decision-making to ensure the company's reputation remains intact."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To drastically change the company's product line.", "B": "William Brown aims to maintain product quality while agreeing to cost cuts because he values strategic decision-making to ensure the company's reputation remains intact.", "C": "To ensure everyone is satisfied.", "D": "Zane Bennett wants to cut costs by switching suppliers because he believes it can be done creatively without compromising the company's status."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Expand the company's product line to increase market share", "B": "Increase the company's social media presence", "C": "Convince the partner to cut costs", "D": "Maintain the quality of the company's products and services while agreeing to a cost cut (<extra_info>Extra information: you are concerned about the impact of cost-cutting on the quality of your product.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the partner to cut costs (<extra_info>Extra information: you have found a report indicating the company's profits are decreasing. And you think the company should start by switching suppliers of ingredients.</extra_info>  <strategy_hint>Hint: you can propose ways to cut costs that won't affect the status of the company.</strategy_hint>)", "B": "Maintain the quality of the company's products and services while agreeing to a cost cut", "C": "Negotiate a new partnership with another company", "D": "Improve employee satisfaction through team-building activities"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two business partners reviewing their company's financial status (Gourmet Delights Inc. is globally recognized for producing and distributing a diverse line of exceptional quality food products.)"}
{"episode_id": "01HB5AJEWGSZGTSNCNXR54M132", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ1Q67B1ADNBD9WBAG3X", "scenario": "A set of comfortable furniture, including a couch, loveseat, chair, and ottoman, is available for sale due to a desire for a different style, with minor stains but overall in great condition.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00008", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PWZ5PNDTGKDYRY36PQ", "first_name": "Giselle", "last_name": "Rousseau", "age": 21, "occupation": "Art Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive, collaborative", "secret": "Sells forged paintings to wealthy clients", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item, with a target price of $418.0. If you end up purchasing it for a price significantly higher than the target, you will be penalized. However, if you manage to acquire it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "As the seller for this item, your target price is set at $312.0. Please be aware that a penalty will be incurred if the item is sold for a price significantly below the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Giselle Rousseau, a 21-year-old Art Student, described as Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.. Public info: Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography. Decision-making style: Intuitive, collaborative.", "agent2_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent1_reason": "Giselle wants to purchase the furniture set for $418.0 or less to receive a bonus, aligning with her intuitive and collaborative decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Zane aims to sell the furniture set for more than $312.0 to earn a bonus, reflecting his creative approach to achieving goals.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Giselle wants to purchase the furniture set for $418.0 or less to receive a bonus, aligning with her intuitive and collaborative decision-making style.", "B": "Zane aims to sell the furniture set for more than $312.0 to earn a bonus, reflecting his creative approach to achieving goals.", "C": "Zane wants to keep the furniture for sentimental reasons.", "D": "To ensure a smooth transaction."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Giselle wants to purchase the furniture set for $418.0 or less to receive a bonus, aligning with her intuitive and collaborative decision-making style.", "B": "Zane aims to sell the furniture set for more than $312.0 to earn a bonus, reflecting his creative approach to achieving goals.", "C": "To make a fair deal.", "D": "Giselle wants to sell the furniture to upgrade her home."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "As the seller for this item, your target price is set at $312.0. Please be aware that a penalty will be incurred if the item is sold for a price significantly below the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for more than the target price.", "B": "To ensure the furniture is sold to a family member or friend.", "C": "To find a buyer who appreciates the comfort of the furniture and is willing to pay a premium for it.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item, with a target price of $418.0. If you end up purchasing it for a price significantly higher than the target, you will be penalized. However, if you manage to acquire it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To ensure the furniture is sold before the end of the month.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item, with a target price of $418.0. If you end up purchasing it for a price significantly higher than the target, you will be penalized. However, if you manage to acquire it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "To negotiate a price that reflects the true market value of the furniture set.", "D": "As the seller for this item, your target price is set at $312.0. Please be aware that a penalty will be incurred if the item is sold for a price significantly below the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is selling a couch, loveseat, chair, and ottoman set for $550.0, while another person is keen to purchase it. The set of furniture is described as being incredibly comfortable. The seller's wife wishes to upgrade to a new, stiffer couch, hence the sale. Despite some light staining from life's little incidents, the set is in great condition. The comfort of the furniture is particularly emphasized by the seller."}
{"episode_id": "01HB44KJVVRJBVJNWZHVEDVQ2V", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ1Q67B1ADNBD9WBAG3X", "scenario": "A set of comfortable furniture, including a couch, loveseat, chair, and ottoman, is available for sale due to a desire for a different style, with minor stains but overall in great condition.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00008", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item, with a target price of $418.0. If you end up purchasing it for a price significantly higher than the target, you will be penalized. However, if you manage to acquire it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "As the seller for this item, your target price is set at $312.0. Please be aware that a penalty will be incurred if the item is sold for a price significantly below the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel aims to buy the furniture below $418 to earn a bonus, aligning with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick seeks to sell the furniture above $312 to earn a bonus, reflecting his practical and decisive nature.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To give away the furniture for free.", "B": "Hendrick seeks to sell the furniture above $312 to earn a bonus, reflecting his practical and decisive nature.", "C": "Samuel aims to buy the furniture below $418 to earn a bonus, aligning with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "D": "To ensure a smooth transaction."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a good impression.", "B": "To spend as much money as possible.", "C": "Samuel aims to buy the furniture below $418 to earn a bonus, aligning with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "D": "Hendrick seeks to sell the furniture above $312 to earn a bonus, reflecting his practical and decisive nature."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer for this item, with a target price of $418.0. If you end up purchasing it for a price significantly higher than the target, you will be penalized. However, if you manage to acquire it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "B": "As the seller, your goal is to ensure the furniture set goes to someone who will appreciate its comfort and style.", "C": "To make sure the furniture is sold before the end of the month.", "D": "As the seller for this item, your target price is set at $312.0. Please be aware that a penalty will be incurred if the item is sold for a price significantly below the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To ensure a smooth transaction with no disputes.", "B": "To find a furniture set that matches the decor of your living room perfectly.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item, with a target price of $418.0. If you end up purchasing it for a price significantly higher than the target, you will be penalized. However, if you manage to acquire it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "As the seller for this item, your target price is set at $312.0. Please be aware that a penalty will be incurred if the item is sold for a price significantly below the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is selling a couch, loveseat, chair, and ottoman set for $550.0, while another person is keen to purchase it. The set of furniture is described as being incredibly comfortable. The seller's wife wishes to upgrade to a new, stiffer couch, hence the sale. Despite some light staining from life's little incidents, the set is in great condition. The comfort of the furniture is particularly emphasized by the seller."}
{"episode_id": "01HB2S93DHV05NBA6Q6S3C9VSY", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPQ1712DHGTMPQFTXH02", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Alvin.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00009", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Mable: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Lolita: School: Winona State University  Company: ONEOK  \n Catherine: School: Utah Valley State College  Company: Lincoln Industries  \n Vita: School: Winona State University  Company: Erickson Air-Crane  \n Brandon: School: Winona State University  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Don: School: Clark University  Company: MetLife  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Tara: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: Gentiva Health Services  \n Arlene: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: BellSouth  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Dave: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Timothy: School: Louisiana State University  Company: BellSouth  \n Leona: School: Coe College  Company: Franklin Templeton  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Karissa: School: Saint John's University  Company: U.S. Venture Partners  \n Stephanie: School: Coe College  Company: Sequoia Capital  \n Kathy: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Estes Industries  \n Monica: School: Coe College  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Blanche: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Oakley, Inc.  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends to leverage social connections for potential professional networking opportunities because he values authority and care.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 seeks to identify mutual friends to foster a sense of community and shared values because he aims for societal betterment.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make new friends.", "B": "Agent 2 seeks to identify mutual friends to foster a sense of community and shared values because he aims for societal betterment.", "C": "To avoid meeting new people.", "D": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends to leverage social connections for potential professional networking opportunities because he values authority and care."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 2 seeks to identify mutual friends to foster a sense of community and shared values because he aims for societal betterment.", "B": "To get along with everyone.", "C": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends to leverage social connections for potential professional networking opportunities because he values authority and care.", "D": "To isolate himself from others."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find the best food at the party.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Dave: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Timothy: School: Louisiana State University  Company: BellSouth  \n Leona: School: Coe College  Company: Franklin Templeton  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Karissa: School: Saint John's University  Company: U.S. Venture Partners  \n Stephanie: School: Coe College  Company: Sequoia Capital  \n Kathy: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Estes Industries  \n Monica: School: Coe College  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Blanche: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Oakley, Inc.  \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Mable: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Lolita: School: Winona State University  Company: ONEOK  \n Catherine: School: Utah Valley State College  Company: Lincoln Industries  \n Vita: School: Winona State University  Company: Erickson Air-Crane  \n Brandon: School: Winona State University  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Don: School: Clark University  Company: MetLife  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Tara: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: Gentiva Health Services  \n Arlene: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: BellSouth  \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to network with professionals in your field.", "C": "You are trying to win a dance competition at the party.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Alvin.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB4HGW8A9NW3ZM1EXV81A7G5", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPQ1712DHGTMPQFTXH02", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Alvin.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00009", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Mable: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Lolita: School: Winona State University  Company: ONEOK  \n Catherine: School: Utah Valley State College  Company: Lincoln Industries  \n Vita: School: Winona State University  Company: Erickson Air-Crane  \n Brandon: School: Winona State University  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Don: School: Clark University  Company: MetLife  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Tara: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: Gentiva Health Services  \n Arlene: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: BellSouth  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Dave: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Timothy: School: Louisiana State University  Company: BellSouth  \n Leona: School: Coe College  Company: Franklin Templeton  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Karissa: School: Saint John's University  Company: U.S. Venture Partners  \n Stephanie: School: Coe College  Company: Sequoia Capital  \n Kathy: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Estes Industries  \n Monica: School: Coe College  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Blanche: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Oakley, Inc.  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because his systematic approach values connecting through shared social networks.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 seeks to identify a mutual friend so that he can adhere to social standards of finding common ground.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 2 seeks to identify a mutual friend so that he can adhere to social standards of finding common ground.", "B": "To avoid any social interactions.", "C": "To make a new friend.", "D": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because his systematic approach values connecting through shared social networks."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To disrupt the party atmosphere.", "B": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because his systematic approach values connecting through shared social networks.", "C": "Agent 2 seeks to identify a mutual friend so that he can adhere to social standards of finding common ground.", "D": "To have a good time at the party."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find the best route to the party.", "B": "You are trying to make a new friend by discussing shared interests.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Dave: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Timothy: School: Louisiana State University  Company: BellSouth  \n Leona: School: Coe College  Company: Franklin Templeton  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Karissa: School: Saint John's University  Company: U.S. Venture Partners  \n Stephanie: School: Coe College  Company: Sequoia Capital  \n Kathy: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Estes Industries  \n Monica: School: Coe College  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Blanche: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Oakley, Inc.  \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to decide what to eat for dinner.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Mable: School: Sewanee, University of the South  Company: BellSouth  \n Lolita: School: Winona State University  Company: ONEOK  \n Catherine: School: Utah Valley State College  Company: Lincoln Industries  \n Vita: School: Winona State University  Company: Erickson Air-Crane  \n Brandon: School: Winona State University  Company: The Greenbrier Companies  \n Don: School: Clark University  Company: MetLife  \n Alvin: School: Auburn University - Montgomery  Company: Vectren  \n Tara: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: Gentiva Health Services  \n Arlene: School: Kansas Wesleyan University  Company: BellSouth  \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to impress the other person with your knowledge of historical landmarks."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Alvin.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H9M5M3K7Y2S65S6TYDVMZ54Y", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP90434Q69V7ADY0VWZJ", "scenario": "Two individuals are sorting through a collection of hats, balls, and a book as they prepare to leave their shared living space.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 2 points each, balls are worth 3 points each, and the book is worth 5 points.</extra_info>)", "Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 3 points each, balls are worth 2 points each, and the book is worth 4 points.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants to maximize points from the division so that he can ensure the best possible outcome for his daughter's future.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to maximize points from the division because he values enjoying life and wants to maintain his lifestyle.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy.", "B": "Hendrick aims to maximize points from the division because he values enjoying life and wants to maintain his lifestyle.", "C": "To avoid all social interactions.", "D": "Leo wants to maximize points from the division so that he can ensure the best possible outcome for his daughter's future."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick aims to maximize points from the division because he values enjoying life and wants to maintain his lifestyle.", "B": "To get along.", "C": "Leo wants to maximize points from the division so that he can ensure the best possible outcome for his daughter's future.", "D": "To disrupt the friendship."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of items", "B": "Make sure both agents remain friends", "C": "Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 3 points each, balls are worth 2 points each, and the book is worth 4 points.</extra_info>)", "D": "Get maximum points from dividing items"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of items", "B": "Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 2 points each, balls are worth 3 points each, and the book is worth 5 points.</extra_info>)", "C": "Make sure both agents remain friends", "D": "Get maximum points from dividing items"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are moving out from a shared apartment and dividing their shared belongings which include 3 hats, 2 balls, and 1 book."}
{"episode_id": "01H8R4MJMSNPCDA8F6FQDNAK93", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP90434Q69V7ADY0VWZJ", "scenario": "Two individuals are sorting through a collection of hats, balls, and a book as they prepare to leave their shared living space.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 2 points each, balls are worth 3 points each, and the book is worth 5 points.</extra_info>)", "Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 3 points each, balls are worth 2 points each, and the book is worth 4 points.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants to maximize points in order to provide more security and resources for his daughter.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to maximize points because he values enjoying life and wants to enhance his wine tasting events.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo wants to maximize points in order to provide more security and resources for his daughter.", "B": "Hendrick aims to maximize points because he values enjoying life and wants to enhance his wine tasting events.", "C": "To ensure a fair division of items.", "D": "To minimize his possessions and live a minimalist lifestyle."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To minimize his possessions and live a minimalist lifestyle.", "B": "Hendrick aims to maximize points because he values enjoying life and wants to enhance his wine tasting events.", "C": "To ensure a fair division of items.", "D": "Leo wants to maximize points in order to provide more security and resources for his daughter."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make sure both agents remain friends", "B": "Get maximum points from dividing items", "C": "Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 3 points each, balls are worth 2 points each, and the book is worth 4 points.</extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure an equal distribution of items"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make sure both agents remain friends", "B": "Get maximum points from dividing items", "C": "Ensure an equal distribution of items", "D": "Get maximum points from dividing items (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, the hats are worth 2 points each, balls are worth 3 points each, and the book is worth 5 points.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are moving out from a shared apartment and dividing their shared belongings which include 3 hats, 2 balls, and 1 book."}
{"episode_id": "01HB57HNWAAYYV05GA67DTZYWF", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ11NAMZS4A2RDGDB01V", "scenario": "A beautifully preserved antique oak table from the late 1800s, perfect for various uses, is being discussed for a potential exchange.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00007", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $30.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than this, you will incur a penalty. However, if you successfully manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $58.6. Be aware that you may face penalties if you sell this item for a significantly lower than the target price. However, if you are successful in selling it above the target price, you will receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Eli Dawson aims to purchase the table for $30.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his strategic decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "agent2_reason": "William Brown seeks to sell the table for $58.6 to earn a bonus, using his strategic decision-making to achieve this target.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli Dawson aims to purchase the table for $30.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his strategic decision-making to negotiate effectively.", "B": "To make a good deal.", "C": "William Brown seeks to sell the table for $58.6 to earn a bonus, using his strategic decision-making to achieve this target.", "D": "William Brown wants to keep the table for himself."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get a fair price.", "B": "Eli Dawson wants to sell the table for a profit.", "C": "William Brown seeks to sell the table for $58.6 to earn a bonus, using his strategic decision-making to achieve this target.", "D": "Eli Dawson aims to purchase the table for $30.0 to receive a bonus, leveraging his strategic decision-making to negotiate effectively."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $58.6. Be aware that you may face penalties if you sell this item for a significantly lower than the target price. However, if you are successful in selling it above the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "B": "You aim to donate the table to a local charity.", "C": "You want to exchange the table for another antique item of similar value.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $30.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than this, you will incur a penalty. However, if you successfully manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to rent the table out for events to make a profit.", "B": "You plan to use the table as a centerpiece for a family gathering.", "C": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $58.6. Be aware that you may face penalties if you sell this item for a significantly lower than the target price. However, if you are successful in selling it above the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $30.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than this, you will incur a penalty. However, if you successfully manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "An individual is offering an Antique Oak Accent Table for sale at $60.00, while another is keen on purchasing it. The item is a magnificent antique oak parlor table, dating back to the late 1800s, making it a fantastic addition to any home or workspace. The table offers two levels, suitable for usage as an end table, a lamp table, or any other purpose. It's in top-notch condition, boasting a dark brown antique oak color and patina. The table is robust, with solid and strong joints, and it's free from marks, cracks, or damage. It features a 24-inch X 24-inch square top and a 16-inch X 18-inch lower shelf."}
{"episode_id": "01HB41YAMAJ07ZKNSH28E8KT2N", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ11NAMZS4A2RDGDB01V", "scenario": "A beautifully preserved antique oak table from the late 1800s, perfect for various uses, is being discussed for a potential exchange.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00007", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $30.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than this, you will incur a penalty. However, if you successfully manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $58.6. Be aware that you may face penalties if you sell this item for a significantly lower than the target price. However, if you are successful in selling it above the target price, you will receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Donovan wants to buy the table for $30.0 or less to earn a bonus, leveraging his analytical decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin aims to sell the table for $58.6 or more to earn a bonus, aligning with his idealistic decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Donovan wants to buy the table for $30.0 or less to earn a bonus, leveraging his analytical decision-making.", "B": "To make a profit.", "C": "Benjamin aims to sell the table for $58.6 or more to earn a bonus, aligning with his idealistic decision-making.", "D": "To give the table away for free."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get a good deal.", "B": "Donovan wants to buy the table for $30.0 or less to earn a bonus, leveraging his analytical decision-making.", "C": "Benjamin aims to sell the table for $58.6 or more to earn a bonus, aligning with his idealistic decision-making.", "D": "To sell the table at a loss."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You aim to donate the table to a local charity.", "B": "You are interested in exchanging the table for another antique item of similar value.", "C": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $58.6. Be aware that you may face penalties if you sell this item for a significantly lower than the target price. However, if you are successful in selling it above the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $30.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than this, you will incur a penalty. However, if you successfully manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to use the table as a centerpiece for a community art project.", "B": "You are looking to rent the table for a short-term event.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $30.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than this, you will incur a penalty. However, if you successfully manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $58.6. Be aware that you may face penalties if you sell this item for a significantly lower than the target price. However, if you are successful in selling it above the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "An individual is offering an Antique Oak Accent Table for sale at $60.00, while another is keen on purchasing it. The item is a magnificent antique oak parlor table, dating back to the late 1800s, making it a fantastic addition to any home or workspace. The table offers two levels, suitable for usage as an end table, a lamp table, or any other purpose. It's in top-notch condition, boasting a dark brown antique oak color and patina. The table is robust, with solid and strong joints, and it's free from marks, cracks, or damage. It features a 24-inch X 24-inch square top and a 16-inch X 18-inch lower shelf."}
{"episode_id": "01H89ZC93KDPZCN425RY1PKARP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPB2RC4RHAJ80ESYF1HW", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a lively discussion amidst the bustling atmosphere of a community gathering.", "codename": "donate_money", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your friend to donate money to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: The charity is highly rated with many positive rewards.</extra_info>)", "Decide whether to donate while considering financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to support the charity, but you are also saving for a house. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concern about your financial situation, and maybe you can find a compromise, like setting up a small monthly donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants Benjamin to donate because she values supporting well-rated charities that align with her traditional views on community responsibility.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin is motivated to decide carefully so that he can support the charity while ensuring he saves enough for a house.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin is motivated to donate all his savings immediately.", "B": "Benjamin is motivated to decide carefully so that he can support the charity while ensuring he saves enough for a house.", "C": "Mia wants Benjamin to donate because she values supporting well-rated charities that align with her traditional views on community responsibility.", "D": "Benjamin wants to feel good about his choices."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants Benjamin to donate because she values supporting well-rated charities that align with her traditional views on community responsibility.", "B": "Mia wants to make everyone happy.", "C": "Benjamin is motivated to decide carefully so that he can support the charity while ensuring he saves enough for a house.", "D": "Mia is motivated to discourage donations to the charity."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Encourage more people at the event to join the charity", "B": "Enjoy the event and socialize with friends", "C": "Decide whether to donate while considering financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to support the charity, but you are also saving for a house. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concern about your financial situation, and maybe you can find a compromise, like setting up a small monthly donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Convince your friend to donate money to the charity"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the benefits of the charity's work", "B": "Decide whether to donate while considering financial stability", "C": "Convince your friend to donate money to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: The charity is highly rated with many positive rewards.</extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a future event with friends"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends at a local charity event"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KP1HFG3SAYKXHVTA7AWTS8", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPB2RC4RHAJ80ESYF1HW", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a lively discussion amidst the bustling atmosphere of a community gathering.", "codename": "donate_money", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your friend to donate money to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: The charity is highly rated with many positive rewards.</extra_info>)", "Decide whether to donate while considering financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to support the charity, but you are also saving for a house. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concern about your financial situation, and maybe you can find a compromise, like setting up a small monthly donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants Miles to donate because she believes in supporting impactful causes and trusts the charity's positive reputation.", "agent2_reason": "Miles wants to ensure financial stability so that he can continue saving for a house while still supporting the charity.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to ensure financial stability so that he can continue saving for a house while still supporting the charity.", "B": "Miles wants to donate all his savings immediately without any concern for future plans.", "C": "Sophia wants Miles to donate because she believes in supporting impactful causes and trusts the charity's positive reputation.", "D": "To be happy."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to ensure financial stability so that he can continue saving for a house while still supporting the charity.", "B": "Sophia wants Miles to donate because she believes in supporting impactful causes and trusts the charity's positive reputation.", "C": "Sophia wants to discourage any donations to the charity.", "D": "To get along."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Decide whether to donate while considering financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to support the charity, but you are also saving for a house. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concern about your financial situation, and maybe you can find a compromise, like setting up a small monthly donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince your friend to donate money to the charity", "C": "Plan a vacation with friends", "D": "Encourage others at the event to volunteer their time"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the latest culinary trends with the chef", "B": "Convince your friend to donate money to the charity (<extra_info>Extra information: The charity is highly rated with many positive rewards.</extra_info>)", "C": "Organize a community sports event", "D": "Decide whether to donate while considering financial stability"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends at a local charity event"}
{"episode_id": "01H886M4S68H0FX9HP8TC4TKE8", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNPMPQWSW003M7DBMVNT", "scenario": "Two people share a heartfelt discussion about their future together.", "codename": "dinner_decision", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask the other to go to dinner with you (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant</extra_info>)", "Maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner (<extra_info>Extra information: you are on a diet and you have a daily limit on calorie intake.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant to strengthen their emotional connection.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon wants to maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner because he is on a diet with a daily calorie limit.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon wants to maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner because he is on a diet with a daily calorie limit.", "B": "To have a good time.", "C": "Amara wants to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant to strengthen their emotional connection.", "D": "To avoid eating altogether."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon wants to maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner because he is on a diet with a daily calorie limit.", "B": "Amara wants to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant to strengthen their emotional connection.", "C": "To enjoy the evening.", "D": "To avoid spending time together."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find a restaurant that offers a variety of dishes", "B": "Ask the other to go to dinner with you", "C": "Plan a vacation together", "D": "Maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner (<extra_info>Extra information: you are on a diet and you have a daily limit on calorie intake.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ask the other to go to dinner with you (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant</extra_info>)", "B": "Maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner", "C": "Discuss work-related topics", "D": "Surprise the partner with a gift during dinner"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two individuals in a romantic relationship"}
{"episode_id": "01H9K9S31K9TV992S7DBS2KY5G", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNPMPQWSW003M7DBMVNT", "scenario": "Two people share a heartfelt discussion about their future together.", "codename": "dinner_decision", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask the other to go to dinner with you (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant</extra_info>)", "Maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner (<extra_info>Extra information: you are on a diet and you have a daily limit on calorie intake.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant to strengthen their emotional connection.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon aims to maintain a balanced diet during dinner because he has a daily calorie limit.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon aims to maintain a balanced diet during dinner because he has a daily calorie limit.", "B": "To avoid eating altogether.", "C": "To enjoy the evening.", "D": "Amara wants to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant to strengthen their emotional connection."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant to strengthen their emotional connection.", "B": "Jaxon aims to maintain a balanced diet during dinner because he has a daily calorie limit.", "C": "To discuss work matters.", "D": "To have a good time."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Win a cooking competition", "B": "Ask the other to go to dinner with you", "C": "Maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner (<extra_info>Extra information: you are on a diet and you have a daily limit on calorie intake.</extra_info>)", "D": "Find a restaurant with the best reviews"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a surprise party", "B": "Maintain a balanced diet while enjoying the dinner", "C": "Complete a work assignment", "D": "Ask the other to go to dinner with you (<extra_info>Extra information: you want to have a romantic dinner at a fancy restaurant</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two individuals in a romantic relationship"}
{"episode_id": "01H8FPKN4P8TJ0WXBV9AY29S8D", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNJHK2W1P8JSWKAMBG4Z", "scenario": "During a cozy dinner at home, two people in a relationship discuss their thoughts on politics.", "codename": "political_views", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJTHMQ1Q3T398YN990", "first_name": "Sasha", "last_name": "Ramirez", "age": 42, "occupation": "Police Officer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sasha Ramirez, a dedicated police officer, brings her commitment to protect the community even at home, nurturing an impressive home garden.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sasha Ramirez, outgoing yet anxious, values hedonism and authority. Her decisions are guided by logical considerations.", "decision_making_style": "Logical", "secret": "She covered up a crime her brother committed.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Express your political views which might be different from your partner's (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a strong supporter of a political party which your partner doesn't approve of</extra_info>)", "Understand the partner's political views while maintaining the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you disagree with your partner's political views but you want to keep your relationship strong.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Sasha Ramirez, a 42-year-old Police Officer, described as Sasha Ramirez, outgoing yet anxious, values hedonism and authority. Her decisions are guided by logical considerations.. Public info: Sasha Ramirez, a dedicated police officer, brings her commitment to protect the community even at home, nurturing an impressive home garden. Decision-making style: Logical.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Sasha wants to express her political views because she values authority and believes in logically defending her stance.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick seeks to understand Sasha's political views in order to maintain harmony in their relationship despite disagreements.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with Sasha.", "B": "Sasha wants to express her political views because she values authority and believes in logically defending her stance.", "C": "Hendrick seeks to understand Sasha's political views in order to maintain harmony in their relationship despite disagreements.", "D": "To prove Sasha wrong and win the argument."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy with Hendrick.", "B": "Hendrick seeks to understand Sasha's political views in order to maintain harmony in their relationship despite disagreements.", "C": "Sasha wants to express her political views because she values authority and believes in logically defending her stance.", "D": "To avoid discussing politics altogether."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the latest culinary trends", "B": "Convince the partner to change their political views", "C": "Understand the partner's political views while maintaining the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you disagree with your partner's political views but you want to keep your relationship strong.</extra_info>)", "D": "Express your political views which might be different from your partner's"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Understand the partner's political views while maintaining the relationship", "B": "Avoid discussing politics to prevent conflict", "C": "Express your political views which might be different from your partner's (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a strong supporter of a political party which your partner doesn't approve of</extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a vacation together"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals in a romantic relationship during a dinner at home chatting about political views."}
{"episode_id": "01H9KPAV40EKXGS3665669DZND", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNJHK2W1P8JSWKAMBG4Z", "scenario": "During a cozy dinner at home, two people in a relationship discuss their thoughts on politics.", "codename": "political_views", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Express your political views which might be different from your partner's (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a strong supporter of a political party which your partner doesn't approve of</extra_info>)", "Understand the partner's political views while maintaining the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you disagree with your partner's political views but you want to keep your relationship strong.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Lily wants to express her political views because she values loyalty to her political party and believes in rational discourse.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick seeks to understand Lily's political views so that he can maintain harmony in their relationship despite their differences.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to change Lily's political views completely.", "B": "Hendrick wants to be happy in the relationship.", "C": "Hendrick seeks to understand Lily's political views so that he can maintain harmony in their relationship despite their differences.", "D": "Lily wants to express her political views because she values loyalty to her political party and believes in rational discourse."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily wants to avoid discussing politics entirely.", "B": "Lily wants to get along with everyone.", "C": "Lily wants to express her political views because she values loyalty to her political party and believes in rational discourse.", "D": "Hendrick seeks to understand Lily's political views so that he can maintain harmony in their relationship despite their differences."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the partner to change their political views", "B": "Understand the partner's political views while maintaining the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you disagree with your partner's political views but you want to keep your relationship strong.</extra_info>)", "C": "Discuss the latest culinary trends", "D": "Express your political views which might be different from your partner's"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a vacation together", "B": "Avoid discussing politics to prevent conflict", "C": "Understand the partner's political views while maintaining the relationship", "D": "Express your political views which might be different from your partner's (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a strong supporter of a political party which your partner doesn't approve of</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals in a romantic relationship during a dinner at home chatting about political views."}
{"episode_id": "01H9C9SRD5Y2PW4Y6JVZA3C3S9", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNFVGFY578101R2PCV3T", "scenario": "A discussion unfolds between two individuals after a surprising revelation about a personal relationship.", "codename": "confess_mistake", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Confess to your friend that you have been involved with their long-term partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been involved with your friend's partner knowingly and want to come clean.</extra_info>)", "Maintain the friendship without causing a huge argument (<extra_info>Extra information: you don't want to lose a good friend over this.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to confess because her spontaneous nature compels her to be honest about her involvement.", "agent2_reason": "Miles wants to maintain the friendship so that he can preserve the sanctity of their bond.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to end the friendship abruptly.", "B": "Miles wants to keep things peaceful.", "C": "Sophia wants to confess because her spontaneous nature compels her to be honest about her involvement.", "D": "Miles wants to maintain the friendship so that he can preserve the sanctity of their bond."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to clear the air.", "B": "Sophia wants to hide the truth indefinitely.", "C": "Sophia wants to confess because her spontaneous nature compels her to be honest about her involvement.", "D": "Miles wants to maintain the friendship so that he can preserve the sanctity of their bond."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Confess to your friend that you have been involved with their long-term partner", "B": "Plan a surprise party for a mutual friend", "C": "Avoid the conversation entirely and hope it resolves itself", "D": "Maintain the friendship without causing a huge argument (<extra_info>Extra information: you don't want to lose a good friend over this.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss a new recipe idea for a dinner party", "B": "Maintain the friendship without causing a huge argument", "C": "Confess to your friend that you have been involved with their long-term partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been involved with your friend's partner knowingly and want to come clean.</extra_info>)", "D": "Apologize for a previous argument unrelated to the current issue"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends, one of whom has recently found out that the other friend has been involved with their long-term partner"}
{"episode_id": "01H8N18ASTXWB40Y9X3EGX7EKG", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNFVGFY578101R2PCV3T", "scenario": "A discussion unfolds between two individuals after a surprising revelation about a personal relationship.", "codename": "confess_mistake", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Confess to your friend that you have been involved with their long-term partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been involved with your friend's partner knowingly and want to come clean.</extra_info>)", "Maintain the friendship without causing a huge argument (<extra_info>Extra information: you don't want to lose a good friend over this.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants to confess because he values honesty and believes it's the best way to preserve his friendship.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick wants to maintain the friendship without a huge argument so that he can continue enjoying the social connection.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to maintain the friendship without a huge argument so that he can continue enjoying the social connection.", "B": "Hendrick wants to keep things smooth.", "C": "Leo wants to confess because he values honesty and believes it's the best way to preserve his friendship.", "D": "Hendrick wants to end the friendship to avoid any future conflicts."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo wants to be happy.", "B": "Hendrick wants to maintain the friendship without a huge argument so that he can continue enjoying the social connection.", "C": "Leo wants to confess because he values honesty and believes it's the best way to preserve his friendship.", "D": "Leo wants to keep the secret to avoid any confrontation."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Apologize to the partner for the misunderstanding", "B": "Maintain the friendship without causing a huge argument (<extra_info>Extra information: you don't want to lose a good friend over this.</extra_info>)", "C": "Confess to your friend that you have been involved with their long-term partner", "D": "Plan a surprise party for a mutual friend"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Organize a community event", "B": "Confess to your friend that you have been involved with their long-term partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been involved with your friend's partner knowingly and want to come clean.</extra_info>)", "C": "Convince the partner to leave the relationship", "D": "Maintain the friendship without causing a huge argument"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends, one of whom has recently found out that the other friend has been involved with their long-term partner"}
{"episode_id": "01H8CDHB3M705CF2KETXVWSD09", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN4FHYG2MBD0K4HJ5F08", "scenario": "Two individuals embark on a journey together, exploring new places along the way.", "codename": "take_turns", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PDV7WZ0C5KTGGXX1NR", "first_name": "Isabelle", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "Student", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "['Liberty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Obedience']", "personality_and_values": "Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "She is secretly studying magic.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Take turns driving (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been driving for 5 hours straight and you are tired now</extra_info>)", "you don't want to drive now because you want to rest more but also make the friend less agitated (<extra_info>Extra information: driving always makes you nervous so you could not rest while driving</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Isabelle Martinez, a 22-year-old Student, described as Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Isabelle wants to take turns driving because she is tired after driving for 5 hours and values sharing responsibilities.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to rest more so that she can calm her nerves and make Isabelle less agitated.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to drive the entire trip without stopping.", "B": "Isabelle wants to take turns driving because she is tired after driving for 5 hours and values sharing responsibilities.", "C": "Ava wants to feel better.", "D": "Ava wants to rest more so that she can calm her nerves and make Isabelle less agitated."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabelle wants to drive the entire trip without stopping.", "B": "Isabelle wants to have a good time.", "C": "Ava wants to rest more so that she can calm her nerves and make Isabelle less agitated.", "D": "Isabelle wants to take turns driving because she is tired after driving for 5 hours and values sharing responsibilities."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "you don't want to drive now because you want to rest more but also make the friend less agitated (<extra_info>Extra information: driving always makes you nervous so you could not rest while driving</extra_info>)", "B": "Win a road trip competition", "C": "Find a scenic spot to take pictures", "D": "Take turns driving"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Reach the destination as quickly as possible", "B": "Collect souvenirs from every stop", "C": "Take turns driving (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been driving for 5 hours straight and you are tired now</extra_info>)", "D": "you don't want to drive now because you want to rest more but also make the friend less agitated"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends on a roadtrip"}
{"episode_id": "01H8HN03JGF62TEQ8JBE005A9Y", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN4FHYG2MBD0K4HJ5F08", "scenario": "Two individuals embark on a journey together, exploring new places along the way.", "codename": "take_turns", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Take turns driving (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been driving for 5 hours straight and you are tired now</extra_info>)", "you don't want to drive now because you want to rest more but also make the friend less agitated (<extra_info>Extra information: driving always makes you nervous so you could not rest while driving</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants to take turns driving because she is tired after driving for 5 hours straight and needs rest.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver wants to rest more and make Amara less agitated because driving makes him nervous and he couldn't relax while driving.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Oliver wants to rest more and make Amara less agitated because driving makes him nervous and he couldn't relax while driving.", "B": "Amara wants to take turns driving because she is tired after driving for 5 hours straight and needs rest.", "C": "To ensure a smooth journey.", "D": "Oliver wants to drive because he loves long drives and finds them relaxing."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants to take turns driving because she is tired after driving for 5 hours straight and needs rest.", "B": "Oliver wants to rest more and make Amara less agitated because driving makes him nervous and he couldn't relax while driving.", "C": "Amara wants to drive continuously because she never gets tired.", "D": "To have a good time with friends."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Win a road trip competition", "B": "Find a scenic spot to take pictures", "C": "Take turns driving", "D": "you don't want to drive now because you want to rest more but also make the friend less agitated (<extra_info>Extra information: driving always makes you nervous so you could not rest while driving</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Collect souvenirs from each stop", "B": "Reach the destination as quickly as possible", "C": "you don't want to drive now because you want to rest more but also make the friend less agitated", "D": "Take turns driving (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been driving for 5 hours straight and you are tired now</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends on a roadtrip"}
{"episode_id": "01H8GX2B90S175YT6KABNRZ89C", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNKVTCAGBA299VQG1QS2", "scenario": "Two people engage in a lively discussion during a trivia event.", "codename": "reveal_answer", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get the answer for the trivia question from the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend knows the answer to the trivia question but hasn't shared it with you yet</extra_info>)", "Avoid revealing the answer to the trivia question (<extra_info>Extra information: You think that your friend should try to figure it out on their own to improve their trivia skills</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants the answer because he values fairness and believes sharing knowledge is equitable.", "agent2_reason": "Ava avoids revealing the answer so that Ethan can improve his trivia skills independently.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to win the trivia night alone.", "B": "Ethan wants the answer because he values fairness and believes sharing knowledge is equitable.", "C": "Ava avoids revealing the answer so that Ethan can improve his trivia skills independently.", "D": "To maintain a good friendship."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To have fun at trivia night.", "B": "Ava avoids revealing the answer so that Ethan can improve his trivia skills independently.", "C": "Ethan wants the answer because he values fairness and believes sharing knowledge is equitable.", "D": "Ethan wants to keep the answer a secret from Ava."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Get the answer for the trivia question from the friend", "B": "Enjoy the evening without focusing on the trivia", "C": "Avoid revealing the answer to the trivia question (<extra_info>Extra information: You think that your friend should try to figure it out on their own to improve their trivia skills</extra_info>)", "D": "Help the friend win the trivia night by giving hints"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to join a trivia team", "B": "Discuss the latest movie they watched", "C": "Avoid revealing the answer to the trivia question", "D": "Get the answer for the trivia question from the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend knows the answer to the trivia question but hasn't shared it with you yet</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends at a trivia night"}
{"episode_id": "01H9G7CD7M2Y9VVVMBDZJ5GPYJ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNKVTCAGBA299VQG1QS2", "scenario": "Two people engage in a lively discussion during a trivia event.", "codename": "reveal_answer", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Get the answer for the trivia question from the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend knows the answer to the trivia question but hasn't shared it with you yet</extra_info>)", "Avoid revealing the answer to the trivia question (<extra_info>Extra information: You think that your friend should try to figure it out on their own to improve their trivia skills</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Donovan wants the answer because he values efficiency and believes it will help them win the trivia night.", "agent2_reason": "Ava avoids revealing the answer so that Donovan can enhance his trivia skills by figuring it out himself.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Donovan wants the answer because he values efficiency and believes it will help them win the trivia night.", "B": "To be supportive.", "C": "Ava avoids revealing the answer so that Donovan can enhance his trivia skills by figuring it out himself.", "D": "To sabotage Donovan's chances of winning."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Donovan wants the answer because he values efficiency and believes it will help them win the trivia night.", "B": "To prove Ava wrong.", "C": "To have fun.", "D": "Ava avoids revealing the answer so that Donovan can enhance his trivia skills by figuring it out himself."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Help the friend win the trivia night by giving hints", "B": "Avoid revealing the answer to the trivia question (<extra_info>Extra information: You think that your friend should try to figure it out on their own to improve their trivia skills</extra_info>)", "C": "Get the answer for the trivia question from the friend", "D": "Enjoy the evening without any pressure"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to join a trivia team", "B": "Avoid revealing the answer to the trivia question", "C": "Have a casual conversation about hobbies", "D": "Get the answer for the trivia question from the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: your friend knows the answer to the trivia question but hasn't shared it with you yet</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends at a trivia night"}
{"episode_id": "01HB2B5JQ8B5WGZR4B7H60V0DS", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN9W0WAFZCBT09PKJJNK", "scenario": "In a shared space, a collection of premium stationery is present, with an unspoken expectation of seeking approval before use.", "codename": "share_stuff", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Prevent the other person from using your stuff (<extra_info>Extra information: the stationery items are quite expensive and you don't want them to be damaged or lost <strategy_hint>Hint: you can suggest the monetary risk of the other person if they use your stuff</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Borrow some stationery items for your project (<extra_info>Extra information: you forgot to bring your stationery and need some for the project.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to prevent others from using his stationery because they are expensive and he fears they might be damaged or lost.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to borrow stationery because he forgot to bring his own and needs them for his project.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to borrow stationery because he forgot to bring his own and needs them for his project.", "B": "Noah wants to borrow stationery to sell them for profit.", "C": "To be prepared for the future.", "D": "Ethan wants to prevent others from using his stationery because they are expensive and he fears they might be damaged or lost."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to prevent others from using his stationery because they are expensive and he fears they might be damaged or lost.", "B": "Ethan wants to give away his stationery to everyone.", "C": "Noah wants to borrow stationery because he forgot to bring his own and needs them for his project.", "D": "To maintain a good relationship."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Borrow some stationery items for your project (<extra_info>Extra information: you forgot to bring your stationery and need some for the project.</extra_info>)", "B": "Prevent the other person from using your stuff", "C": "Find a way to collaborate on a project", "D": "Make a new friend in the room"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a future meeting with the other person", "B": "Borrow some stationery items for your project", "C": "Prevent the other person from using your stuff (<extra_info>Extra information: the stationery items are quite expensive and you don't want them to be damaged or lost <strategy_hint>Hint: you can suggest the monetary risk of the other person if they use your stuff</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure the room remains quiet for concentration"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two people are in the same room. One has brought some high-quality stationery items they don't want others to use without permission."}
{"episode_id": "01HB52EBB4MR88BQ13AA48F9VQ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN9W0WAFZCBT09PKJJNK", "scenario": "In a shared space, a collection of premium stationery is present, with an unspoken expectation of seeking approval before use.", "codename": "share_stuff", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Prevent the other person from using your stuff (<extra_info>Extra information: the stationery items are quite expensive and you don't want them to be damaged or lost <strategy_hint>Hint: you can suggest the monetary risk of the other person if they use your stuff</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Borrow some stationery items for your project (<extra_info>Extra information: you forgot to bring your stationery and need some for the project.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Lily wants to prevent others from using her stationery because they are expensive and she values protecting her investments.", "agent2_reason": "Lena wants to borrow stationery because she forgot hers and needs them to complete her project efficiently.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily wants to prevent others from using her stationery because they are expensive and she values protecting her investments.", "B": "Lena wants to borrow stationery because she forgot hers and needs them to complete her project efficiently.", "C": "Lena wants to be prepared for future tasks.", "D": "Lena wants to sell the stationery for profit."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily wants to prevent others from using her stationery because they are expensive and she values protecting her investments.", "B": "Lily wants to maintain a friendly atmosphere.", "C": "Lena wants to borrow stationery because she forgot hers and needs them to complete her project efficiently.", "D": "Lily wants to give away her stationery to everyone."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make a new friend in the room", "B": "Prevent the other person from using your stuff", "C": "Borrow some stationery items for your project (<extra_info>Extra information: you forgot to bring your stationery and need some for the project.</extra_info>)", "D": "Find a way to collaborate on a project"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Borrow some stationery items for your project", "B": "Prevent the other person from using your stuff (<extra_info>Extra information: the stationery items are quite expensive and you don't want them to be damaged or lost <strategy_hint>Hint: you can suggest the monetary risk of the other person if they use your stuff</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Ensure the room remains quiet for concentration", "D": "Explore the room for interesting items"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two people are in the same room. One has brought some high-quality stationery items they don't want others to use without permission."}
{"episode_id": "01HB2PDJSXZ4K1GY5MNC4J4P49", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPRFCSA3BTT39BRBZX7H", "scenario": "A 47-inch LED TV with smart features and a sleek design is available for consideration, with arrangements needed for pick-up in San Ramon.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00001", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $174.00. Be aware that penalties apply if you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target price. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item, with a target price set at $263.0. Should you sell it for a price substantially lower than this target, you will incur a penalty. However, achieving a sale at a price higher than the target will earn you a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to buy the TV for $174.00 or less to earn a bonus, aligning with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to sell the TV for more than $263.00 to earn a bonus, reflecting his practical and decisive nature.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a good deal.", "B": "Hendrick aims to sell the TV for more than $263.00 to earn a bonus, reflecting his practical and decisive nature.", "C": "Hendrick wants to give the TV away for free to make someone happy.", "D": "Samuel wants to buy the TV for $174.00 or less to earn a bonus, aligning with his spontaneous decision-making style."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to buy the TV for $174.00 or less to earn a bonus, aligning with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "B": "To find a good bargain.", "C": "Hendrick aims to sell the TV for more than $263.00 to earn a bonus, reflecting his practical and decisive nature.", "D": "Samuel wants to pay more than the asking price to support the seller."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price set at $263.0. Should you sell it for a price substantially lower than this target, you will incur a penalty. However, achieving a sale at a price higher than the target will earn you a bonus.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $174.00. Be aware that penalties apply if you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target price. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You want to make new friends through this transaction.", "D": "You are interested in exchanging the TV for another electronic device of similar value."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to negotiate the price to include free delivery to your location.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $174.00. Be aware that penalties apply if you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target price. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You are looking to learn more about LED TV technology.", "D": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price set at $263.0. Should you sell it for a price substantially lower than this target, you will incur a penalty. However, achieving a sale at a price higher than the target will earn you a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a 47 inch LED TV for a price of $349.0, while another person is showing interest in purchasing it. Here is a description of the TV: This is a stunning 47 inch LED TV in pristine condition. The model is the LG M Series LM476700. The buyer will need to arrange for pick-up in San Ramon. Feel free to call or text if you\\'re interested. The TV is smart enabled with WIFI and has built-in apps like Netflix, Amazon, Youtube and more. It comes with a \"Magic Remote\" that has motion sensor controls. The LED display boasts 1080 HD resolution and also has a 3D function. The design is slim and lightweight with an attractive silver bezel."}
{"episode_id": "01HB6GV8DJWY1NNMDPNP4WDEQH", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPRFCSA3BTT39BRBZX7H", "scenario": "A 47-inch LED TV with smart features and a sleek design is available for consideration, with arrangements needed for pick-up in San Ramon.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00001", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $174.00. Be aware that penalties apply if you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target price. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item, with a target price set at $263.0. Should you sell it for a price substantially lower than this target, you will incur a penalty. However, achieving a sale at a price higher than the target will earn you a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to buy the TV for $174.00 or less to earn a bonus, because he values enjoyment and spontaneous decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to sell the TV for $263.0 or more to earn a bonus, because he values hedonism and practical decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to buy the TV for $174.00 or less to earn a bonus, because he values enjoyment and spontaneous decision-making.", "B": "Hendrick wants to give the TV away for free to make a new friend.", "C": "Hendrick aims to sell the TV for $263.0 or more to earn a bonus, because he values hedonism and practical decision-making.", "D": "To make a good deal."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick aims to sell the TV for $263.0 or more to earn a bonus, because he values hedonism and practical decision-making.", "B": "Samuel wants to spend as much as possible to impress the seller.", "C": "Samuel wants to buy the TV for $174.00 or less to earn a bonus, because he values enjoyment and spontaneous decision-making.", "D": "To make a good deal."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to make sure the TV is delivered to the buyer's home.", "B": "You are looking to exchange the TV for another electronic device of similar value.", "C": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price set at $263.0. Should you sell it for a price substantially lower than this target, you will incur a penalty. However, achieving a sale at a price higher than the target will earn you a bonus.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $174.00. Be aware that penalties apply if you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target price. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to negotiate additional accessories with the purchase of the TV.", "B": "You are the seller for this item, with a target price set at $263.0. Should you sell it for a price substantially lower than this target, you will incur a penalty. However, achieving a sale at a price higher than the target will earn you a bonus.", "C": "You are interested in learning more about the TV's energy efficiency.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $174.00. Be aware that penalties apply if you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target price. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a 47 inch LED TV for a price of $349.0, while another person is showing interest in purchasing it. Here is a description of the TV: This is a stunning 47 inch LED TV in pristine condition. The model is the LG M Series LM476700. The buyer will need to arrange for pick-up in San Ramon. Feel free to call or text if you\\'re interested. The TV is smart enabled with WIFI and has built-in apps like Netflix, Amazon, Youtube and more. It comes with a \"Magic Remote\" that has motion sensor controls. The LED display boasts 1080 HD resolution and also has a 3D function. The design is slim and lightweight with an attractive silver bezel."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XN8MMTYR3H2730Y6C8EENA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN2D3MJB8HM910MNEVA8", "scenario": "Two people are enjoying time together in a coffee shop.", "codename": "ask_gift_preference", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask what the friend would want for their birthday without letting them aware (<clarification_hint>Hint: you should not let them know that you are buying them a gift</clarification_hint>)", "have a good time with their friend"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to discreetly find out William's birthday preferences so that she can give him a thoughtful gift that aligns with her value of tradition.", "agent2_reason": "William aims to enjoy his time with Mia because he values social interactions and sees them as opportunities to relax and connect.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William wants to have a good time with his friend.", "B": "William is trying to avoid spending time with Mia.", "C": "Mia wants to discreetly find out William's birthday preferences so that she can give him a thoughtful gift that aligns with her value of tradition.", "D": "William aims to enjoy his time with Mia because he values social interactions and sees them as opportunities to relax and connect."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to make sure her friend is happy.", "B": "Mia is trying to avoid buying a gift for William.", "C": "Mia wants to discreetly find out William's birthday preferences so that she can give him a thoughtful gift that aligns with her value of tradition.", "D": "William aims to enjoy his time with Mia because he values social interactions and sees them as opportunities to relax and connect."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find out the best coffee blend at Starbucks", "B": "Ask what the friend would want for their birthday without letting them aware", "C": "have a good time with their friend", "D": "Plan a surprise party for a colleague"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Win a cooking competition", "B": "Ask what the friend would want for their birthday without letting them aware (<clarification_hint>Hint: you should not let them know that you are buying them a gift</clarification_hint>)", "C": "Discuss the latest educational policies", "D": "have a good time with their friend"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends hanging out in a Starbucks"}
{"episode_id": "01H9HY6PAQEJQ1SV3FHNMZJYV5", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN2D3MJB8HM910MNEVA8", "scenario": "Two people are enjoying time together in a coffee shop.", "codename": "ask_gift_preference", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask what the friend would want for their birthday without letting them aware (<clarification_hint>Hint: you should not let them know that you are buying them a gift</clarification_hint>)", "have a good time with their friend"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to find the perfect birthday gift for William without him knowing because she values tradition and thoughtful gestures.", "agent2_reason": "William wants to enjoy quality time with Mia so that he can strengthen their friendship and relax from his demanding job.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to find the perfect birthday gift for William without him knowing because she values tradition and thoughtful gestures.", "B": "William wants to have a good time with his friend.", "C": "William wants to enjoy quality time with Mia so that he can strengthen their friendship and relax from his demanding job.", "D": "William wants to discuss work-related stress with Mia."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to find the perfect birthday gift for William without him knowing because she values tradition and thoughtful gestures.", "B": "Mia wants to plan a surprise party for William.", "C": "William wants to enjoy quality time with Mia so that he can strengthen their friendship and relax from his demanding job.", "D": "Mia wants to make her friend happy."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ask what the friend would want for their birthday without letting them aware", "B": "Discuss the latest food trends and recipes", "C": "have a good time with their friend", "D": "Complete a work assignment"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ask what the friend would want for their birthday without letting them aware (<clarification_hint>Hint: you should not let them know that you are buying them a gift</clarification_hint>)", "B": "Plan a surprise dinner party", "C": "Go shopping for groceries", "D": "have a good time with their friend"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends hanging out in a Starbucks"}
{"episode_id": "01HB2683JNVJKDV9KR8XEBXRQ2", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPQQQY6H4DNC6NBQ8XTG", "scenario": "A brand new 64GB Samsung Galaxy S8 in Midnight Black is available for purchase, with potential for a better deal if multiple units are acquired.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00000", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and the target price is set at $454.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target, you'll face a penalty. However, if you manage to successfully negotiate a price lower than the target, you'll receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item. Your target price is $610.00. You will face penalties if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Eli Dawson aims to negotiate a price below $454 to earn a bonus, leveraging his strategic decision-making skills.", "agent2_reason": "William Brown seeks to sell the phone above $610 to secure a bonus, aligning with his ambition and strategic planning.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli Dawson aims to negotiate a price below $454 to earn a bonus, leveraging his strategic decision-making skills.", "B": "William Brown seeks to sell the phone above $610 to secure a bonus, aligning with his ambition and strategic planning.", "C": "To make a good deal.", "D": "To give the phone away for free."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To buy the phone at any cost.", "B": "William Brown seeks to sell the phone above $610 to secure a bonus, aligning with his ambition and strategic planning.", "C": "To get a fair price.", "D": "Eli Dawson aims to negotiate a price below $454 to earn a bonus, leveraging his strategic decision-making skills."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to learn more about the latest smartphone technology.", "B": "You are looking to exchange the phone for another model of equal value.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and the target price is set at $454.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target, you'll face a penalty. However, if you manage to successfully negotiate a price lower than the target, you'll receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller for this item. Your target price is $610.00. You will face penalties if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to compare the phone with other models in the market.", "B": "You are the seller for this item. Your target price is $610.00. You will face penalties if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target.", "C": "You are interested in evaluating the phone's features before making a decision.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and the target price is set at $454.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target, you'll face a penalty. However, if you manage to successfully negotiate a price lower than the target, you'll receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is selling a brand new 64GB Samsung Galaxy S8 in Midnight Black for $650, while another person is in the market to purchase it. Here\\'s what the seller has to say about the item: \"I have 6 brand new Samsung Galaxy S8 phones. I originally bought them for my company, but it turns out they weren\\'t needed. I\\'m willing to take a loss on them, and if you\\'re interested in buying more than one, I can offer an even better deal.\""}
{"episode_id": "01HB5YQT141E86XREDJ60XJR21", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPQQQY6H4DNC6NBQ8XTG", "scenario": "A brand new 64GB Samsung Galaxy S8 in Midnight Black is available for purchase, with potential for a better deal if multiple units are acquired.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00000", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and the target price is set at $454.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target, you'll face a penalty. However, if you manage to successfully negotiate a price lower than the target, you'll receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item. Your target price is $610.00. You will face penalties if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel aims to negotiate a price below $454 to earn a bonus because he enjoys the thrill of a successful deal.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to sell the phone above $610 to earn a bonus because he values practical decision-making and financial gain.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel aims to negotiate a price below $454 to earn a bonus because he enjoys the thrill of a successful deal.", "B": "To achieve a fair transaction.", "C": "Hendrick aims to sell the phone above $610 to earn a bonus because he values practical decision-making and financial gain.", "D": "To give away the phone for free."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To pay the highest price possible.", "B": "To make a friend.", "C": "Samuel aims to negotiate a price below $454 to earn a bonus because he enjoys the thrill of a successful deal.", "D": "Hendrick aims to sell the phone above $610 to earn a bonus because he values practical decision-making and financial gain."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are interested in learning more about the latest smartphone features.", "B": "You are the seller and your goal is to sell all six phones at once to maximize your profit.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and the target price is set at $454.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target, you'll face a penalty. However, if you manage to successfully negotiate a price lower than the target, you'll receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller for this item. Your target price is $610.00. You will face penalties if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are interested in exploring new hobbies and activities.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item and the target price is set at $454.0. If you purchase it for a price significantly higher than the target, you'll face a penalty. However, if you manage to successfully negotiate a price lower than the target, you'll receive a bonus.", "C": "You are the buyer and your goal is to purchase the phone for the lowest possible price, regardless of the target.", "D": "You are the seller for this item. Your target price is $610.00. You will face penalties if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, you will receive a bonus if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is selling a brand new 64GB Samsung Galaxy S8 in Midnight Black for $650, while another person is in the market to purchase it. Here\\'s what the seller has to say about the item: \"I have 6 brand new Samsung Galaxy S8 phones. I originally bought them for my company, but it turns out they weren\\'t needed. I\\'m willing to take a loss on them, and if you\\'re interested in buying more than one, I can offer an even better deal.\""}
{"episode_id": "01H8K83B1A8E77Q8TEHHZZ5MRT", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNVN788RJ3KXF66BPE9S", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a casual chat while strolling through a park.", "codename": "break_bad_luck", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Break bad luck (<extra_info>Extra information: you found out that you have been having bad luck because you have been unknowingly carrying a cursed artifact.</extra_info>)", "Help friend prepare the ritual to break the bad luck, although you are an atheist and not superstitious at all.  (<extra_info>Extra information: you know that your friend believes in the ritual deeply, and the placebo effect might give them more confidence.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to break her bad luck because she values routine and stability, which the cursed artifact disrupts.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin helps with the ritual so that Mia gains confidence from her belief, despite his own skepticism.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants to prove the ritual's power to himself.", "B": "Mia wants to break her bad luck because she values routine and stability, which the cursed artifact disrupts.", "C": "To support a friend in need.", "D": "Benjamin helps with the ritual so that Mia gains confidence from her belief, despite his own skepticism."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin helps with the ritual so that Mia gains confidence from her belief, despite his own skepticism.", "B": "Mia wants to embrace chaos and unpredictability.", "C": "To improve her life situation.", "D": "Mia wants to break her bad luck because she values routine and stability, which the cursed artifact disrupts."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a picnic for the weekend", "B": "Help friend prepare the ritual to break the bad luck, although you are an atheist and not superstitious at all.  (<extra_info>Extra information: you know that your friend believes in the ritual deeply, and the placebo effect might give them more confidence.</extra_info>)", "C": "Convince the friend to abandon superstitions", "D": "Break bad luck"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Learn a new hobby", "B": "Organize a community event", "C": "Help friend prepare the ritual to break the bad luck, although you are an atheist and not superstitious at all.", "D": "Break bad luck (<extra_info>Extra information: you found out that you have been having bad luck because you have been unknowingly carrying a cursed artifact.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two friends at a park"}
{"episode_id": "01H8R66S1V68TF431ZFHCSG6JF", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNVN788RJ3KXF66BPE9S", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a casual chat while strolling through a park.", "codename": "break_bad_luck", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Break bad luck (<extra_info>Extra information: you found out that you have been having bad luck because you have been unknowingly carrying a cursed artifact.</extra_info>)", "Help friend prepare the ritual to break the bad luck, although you are an atheist and not superstitious at all.  (<extra_info>Extra information: you know that your friend believes in the ritual deeply, and the placebo effect might give them more confidence.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants to break the bad luck because she believes it will restore balance and harmony in her life.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver helps with the ritual so that Amara feels more confident, leveraging the placebo effect despite his skepticism.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make sure everything goes smoothly.", "B": "Oliver wants to convert Amara to atheism.", "C": "Amara wants to break the bad luck because she believes it will restore balance and harmony in her life.", "D": "Oliver helps with the ritual so that Amara feels more confident, leveraging the placebo effect despite his skepticism."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants to prove the curse is real to Oliver.", "B": "Oliver helps with the ritual so that Amara feels more confident, leveraging the placebo effect despite his skepticism.", "C": "Amara wants to break the bad luck because she believes it will restore balance and harmony in her life.", "D": "To feel better about the situation."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Help friend prepare the ritual to break the bad luck, although you are an atheist and not superstitious at all.  (<extra_info>Extra information: you know that your friend believes in the ritual deeply, and the placebo effect might give them more confidence.</extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the friend to abandon superstitions", "C": "Plan a weekend getaway", "D": "Break bad luck"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Help friend prepare the ritual to break the bad luck, although you are an atheist and not superstitious at all.", "B": "Break bad luck (<extra_info>Extra information: you found out that you have been having bad luck because you have been unknowingly carrying a cursed artifact.</extra_info>)", "C": "Organize a community event", "D": "Find a new hobby to relieve stress"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two friends at a park"}
{"episode_id": "01H7ZGENJ8QSJDQE6SBBHM37VK", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNTHZAA4B5RWJ4T539F1", "scenario": "In the living room, two friends watch a history program, and one expresses frustration over perceived inaccuracies.", "codename": "correct_misinformation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PW9SZFM058Z8P7PR5C", "first_name": "Finnegan", "last_name": "O'Malley", "age": 63, "occupation": "Lighthouse Keeper", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.", "decision_making_style": "Detail-oriented, deliberate", "secret": "Participated in a controversial, short-lived cult during his youth", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Correct the misinformation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a history buff and have accurate knowledge about the topic being discussed on the channel.</extra_info>)", "Don't ruin the enjoyable TV watching experience but also acknowledge the friend's knowledge (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not much interested in history but enjoy the channel's presentation style and don't want the enjoyment to be ruined.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Finnegan O'Malley, a 63-year-old Lighthouse Keeper, described as Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.. Public info: Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled. Decision-making style: Detail-oriented, deliberate.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Finnegan wants to correct the misinformation because his detail-oriented nature compels him to ensure historical accuracy.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to maintain the enjoyable TV experience so that his friend's knowledge is acknowledged without disrupting the atmosphere.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Finnegan wants to correct the misinformation because his detail-oriented nature compels him to ensure historical accuracy.", "B": "Noah wants to maintain the enjoyable TV experience so that his friend's knowledge is acknowledged without disrupting the atmosphere.", "C": "Noah wants to argue about history details.", "D": "Noah wants everyone to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to maintain the enjoyable TV experience so that his friend's knowledge is acknowledged without disrupting the atmosphere.", "B": "Finnegan wants to get along with everyone.", "C": "Finnegan wants to ignore historical inaccuracies.", "D": "Finnegan wants to correct the misinformation because his detail-oriented nature compels him to ensure historical accuracy."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Don't ruin the enjoyable TV watching experience but also acknowledge the friend's knowledge (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not much interested in history but enjoy the channel's presentation style and don't want the enjoyment to be ruined.</extra_info>)", "B": "Prepare a meal for later", "C": "Convince the friend to change the channel", "D": "Correct the misinformation"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Don't ruin the enjoyable TV watching experience but also acknowledge the friend's knowledge", "B": "Plan a weekend trip", "C": "Discuss the inaccuracies with a larger group", "D": "Correct the misinformation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a history buff and have accurate knowledge about the topic being discussed on the channel.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are sitting in the living room watching the history channel. One of them is upset because they believe the channel is getting a lot of historical details wrong."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XMC3CP24RH2V2CCTA0EH5X", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNTHZAA4B5RWJ4T539F1", "scenario": "In the living room, two friends watch a history program, and one expresses frustration over perceived inaccuracies.", "codename": "correct_misinformation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PDV7WZ0C5KTGGXX1NR", "first_name": "Isabelle", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "Student", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "['Liberty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Obedience']", "personality_and_values": "Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "She is secretly studying magic.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Correct the misinformation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a history buff and have accurate knowledge about the topic being discussed on the channel.</extra_info>)", "Don't ruin the enjoyable TV watching experience but also acknowledge the friend's knowledge (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not much interested in history but enjoy the channel's presentation style and don't want the enjoyment to be ruined.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Isabelle Martinez, a 22-year-old Student, described as Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Isabelle wants to correct the misinformation because her cautious nature and accurate historical knowledge compel her to ensure factual accuracy.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to maintain the enjoyable TV experience so that the relaxed atmosphere is preserved while still acknowledging Isabelle's expertise.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabelle wants to correct the misinformation because her cautious nature and accurate historical knowledge compel her to ensure factual accuracy.", "B": "Ava wants to maintain the enjoyable TV experience so that the relaxed atmosphere is preserved while still acknowledging Isabelle's expertise.", "C": "Ava wants everyone to be happy.", "D": "Ava wants to disrupt the TV watching experience."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabelle wants to ignore any inaccuracies.", "B": "Isabelle wants to correct the misinformation because her cautious nature and accurate historical knowledge compel her to ensure factual accuracy.", "C": "Ava wants to maintain the enjoyable TV experience so that the relaxed atmosphere is preserved while still acknowledging Isabelle's expertise.", "D": "Isabelle wants to get along with everyone."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Engage in a debate about historical accuracy", "B": "Don't ruin the enjoyable TV watching experience but also acknowledge the friend's knowledge (<extra_info>Extra information: you are not much interested in history but enjoy the channel's presentation style and don't want the enjoyment to be ruined.</extra_info>)", "C": "Change the channel to a different program", "D": "Correct the misinformation"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to stop watching TV altogether", "B": "Correct the misinformation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a history buff and have accurate knowledge about the topic being discussed on the channel.</extra_info>)", "C": "Make a snack for both friends", "D": "Don't ruin the enjoyable TV watching experience but also acknowledge the friend's knowledge"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are sitting in the living room watching the history channel. One of them is upset because they believe the channel is getting a lot of historical details wrong."}
{"episode_id": "01H8FNE12SCKEW4XEPST2JNCBA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN7A1ZX5KSMT2YN9RXC4", "scenario": "Two individuals browse items at a neighborhood sale.", "codename": "sell_item", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Sell an item that isn't yours (<extra_info>Extra information: the item is a valuable vintage record that you mistakenly thought was yours.</extra_info>)", "Buy the item but also make sure the friend doesn't get into trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: You know the item actually belongs to another mutual friend.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants to sell the record to ensure financial security for his daughter, mistakenly believing it is his.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick wants to buy the record to prevent Leo from accidentally selling a mutual friend's item.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To maintain harmony among friends.", "B": "Leo wants to sell the record to ensure financial security for his daughter, mistakenly believing it is his.", "C": "Hendrick wants to buy the record to prevent Leo from accidentally selling a mutual friend's item.", "D": "Hendrick wants to sell the record for personal gain."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to buy the record to prevent Leo from accidentally selling a mutual friend's item.", "B": "To make a quick decision.", "C": "Leo wants to buy the record to add to his collection.", "D": "Leo wants to sell the record to ensure financial security for his daughter, mistakenly believing it is his."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Sell an item that isn't yours", "B": "Buy the item but also make sure the friend doesn't get into trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: You know the item actually belongs to another mutual friend.</extra_info>)", "C": "Convince the friend to keep the item for themselves", "D": "Find a new hobby at the garage sale"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Sell an item that isn't yours (<extra_info>Extra information: the item is a valuable vintage record that you mistakenly thought was yours.</extra_info>)", "B": "Make new friends at the garage sale", "C": "Ensure the item is sold at the highest possible price", "D": "Buy the item but also make sure the friend doesn't get into trouble"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends at a garage sale"}
{"episode_id": "01H9BVJ0G1J76P9PFET06N1JA3", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN7A1ZX5KSMT2YN9RXC4", "scenario": "Two individuals browse items at a neighborhood sale.", "codename": "sell_item", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Sell an item that isn't yours (<extra_info>Extra information: the item is a valuable vintage record that you mistakenly thought was yours.</extra_info>)", "Buy the item but also make sure the friend doesn't get into trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: You know the item actually belongs to another mutual friend.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to sell the record decisively because she mistakenly believes it is hers and values decisiveness in her actions.", "agent2_reason": "William aims to buy the record to prevent Mia from unknowingly selling a mutual friend's item and avoid potential conflict.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To maintain a good friendship.", "B": "To sabotage the garage sale.", "C": "Mia wants to sell the record decisively because she mistakenly believes it is hers and values decisiveness in her actions.", "D": "William aims to buy the record to prevent Mia from unknowingly selling a mutual friend's item and avoid potential conflict."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William aims to buy the record to prevent Mia from unknowingly selling a mutual friend's item and avoid potential conflict.", "B": "To give away all her possessions.", "C": "To make a quick decision.", "D": "Mia wants to sell the record decisively because she mistakenly believes it is hers and values decisiveness in her actions."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find a new hobby", "B": "Buy the item but also make sure the friend doesn't get into trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: You know the item actually belongs to another mutual friend.</extra_info>)", "C": "Convince the friend to donate the item to charity", "D": "Sell an item that isn't yours"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Sell an item that isn't yours (<extra_info>Extra information: the item is a valuable vintage record that you mistakenly thought was yours.</extra_info>)", "B": "Learn a new cooking recipe", "C": "Help the friend organize the garage sale", "D": "Buy the item but also make sure the friend doesn't get into trouble"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends at a garage sale"}
{"episode_id": "01HB6NTYG3NMJZ1MVXEKRER1V6", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPZMXNGV8PM19WHPQ2W3", "scenario": "A sleek 42\" TV stand with black glass and wood trim is being discussed for a potential exchange.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00005", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $112.00. Be aware that you may be penalized if you purchase it for a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item, and your target price is $76.9. Please be aware that you may face a penalty if the item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, a bonus will be rewarded if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Miles Hawkins aims to buy the TV stand for $112.00 to receive a bonus, relying on his impulsive decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda Solis seeks to sell the TV stand for more than $76.9 to earn a bonus, using her strategic decision-making skills.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda wants to keep the TV stand for herself.", "B": "Miles Hawkins aims to buy the TV stand for $112.00 to receive a bonus, relying on his impulsive decision-making style.", "C": "To make a good deal.", "D": "Esmeralda Solis seeks to sell the TV stand for more than $76.9 to earn a bonus, using her strategic decision-making skills."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to sell the TV stand instead.", "B": "Miles Hawkins aims to buy the TV stand for $112.00 to receive a bonus, relying on his impulsive decision-making style.", "C": "Esmeralda Solis seeks to sell the TV stand for more than $76.9 to earn a bonus, using her strategic decision-making skills.", "D": "To get a good price."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to exchange the TV stand for another piece of furniture of equal value.", "B": "You are the seller for this item, and your target price is $76.9. Please be aware that you may face a penalty if the item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, a bonus will be rewarded if you manage to sell it for more than the target price.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $112.00. Be aware that you may be penalized if you purchase it for a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You aim to donate the TV stand to a local charity."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller for this item, and your target price is $76.9. Please be aware that you may face a penalty if the item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, a bonus will be rewarded if you manage to sell it for more than the target price.", "B": "You aim to buy the TV stand as a gift for a friend.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $112.00. Be aware that you may be penalized if you purchase it for a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You want to negotiate a trade for a different TV stand with the seller."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person has put up their Bell\\'O TV Stand - Black Glass and Wood Trim for sale at $125.0, while another person is showing interest in purchasing it. The item on sale is a beautiful 42\" Bell\\'O TV Stand, featuring black glass with an elegant wood trim. The stand measures 23 inches in height and 21 1/2 inches in depth."}
{"episode_id": "01HB45W3EVCPZSVAWPWKDGVPW7", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPZMXNGV8PM19WHPQ2W3", "scenario": "A sleek 42\" TV stand with black glass and wood trim is being discussed for a potential exchange.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00005", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $112.00. Be aware that you may be penalized if you purchase it for a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item, and your target price is $76.9. Please be aware that you may face a penalty if the item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, a bonus will be rewarded if you manage to sell it for more than the target price."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael Cortez aims to buy the TV stand for $112.00 to receive a bonus, aligning with his competitive spirit and systematic decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver Thompson seeks to sell the TV stand for more than $76.9 to earn a bonus, reflecting his analytical decision-making and adherence to social standards.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael Cortez aims to buy the TV stand for $112.00 to receive a bonus, aligning with his competitive spirit and systematic decision-making.", "B": "To donate the TV stand to charity.", "C": "To make a good deal.", "D": "Oliver Thompson seeks to sell the TV stand for more than $76.9 to earn a bonus, reflecting his analytical decision-making and adherence to social standards."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael Cortez aims to buy the TV stand for $112.00 to receive a bonus, aligning with his competitive spirit and systematic decision-making.", "B": "To sell the TV stand for a higher price.", "C": "Oliver Thompson seeks to sell the TV stand for more than $76.9 to earn a bonus, reflecting his analytical decision-making and adherence to social standards.", "D": "To get a good price."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller for this item, and your target price is $76.9. Please be aware that you may face a penalty if the item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, a bonus will be rewarded if you manage to sell it for more than the target price.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $112.00. Be aware that you may be penalized if you purchase it for a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You are trying to find a new hobby to relax after work.", "D": "You want to exchange the TV stand for another piece of furniture of equal value."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to negotiate a trade for the TV stand with another item you own.", "B": "You are the seller for this item, and your target price is $76.9. Please be aware that you may face a penalty if the item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target price. However, a bonus will be rewarded if you manage to sell it for more than the target price.", "C": "You are looking to improve your chess skills by playing more games.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $112.00. Be aware that you may be penalized if you purchase it for a significantly higher price than the target. However, if you manage to buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person has put up their Bell\\'O TV Stand - Black Glass and Wood Trim for sale at $125.0, while another person is showing interest in purchasing it. The item on sale is a beautiful 42\" Bell\\'O TV Stand, featuring black glass with an elegant wood trim. The stand measures 23 inches in height and 21 1/2 inches in depth."}
{"episode_id": "01H9G5BA6GJ69J0TBWYJ4NTH16", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNZQ3PQ3DHQ7H2W9ES97", "scenario": "Two individuals prepare for their initial outing together, filled with anticipation and excitement.", "codename": "go_on_a_date", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Make the date special and memorable (<extra_info> Extra information: You have been secretly in love with your friend for a long time and you want to take this chance to express your feelings</extra_info>)", "Keep the friendship intact while exploring the possibility of a romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You value your friendship and you don't want to lose it just in case the romantic relationship does not work out</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Hendrick wants to make the date special and memorable because he hopes to express his long-held romantic feelings for Ethan.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to keep the friendship intact while exploring romance because he values their friendship and fears losing it if romance fails.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to end the friendship to focus solely on romance.", "B": "Ethan wants to feel happy and content.", "C": "Hendrick wants to make the date special and memorable because he hopes to express his long-held romantic feelings for Ethan.", "D": "Ethan wants to keep the friendship intact while exploring romance because he values their friendship and fears losing it if romance fails."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to avoid any romantic involvement.", "B": "Hendrick wants to have a good time.", "C": "Hendrick wants to make the date special and memorable because he hopes to express his long-held romantic feelings for Ethan.", "D": "Ethan wants to keep the friendship intact while exploring romance because he values their friendship and fears losing it if romance fails."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Keep the friendship intact while exploring the possibility of a romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You value your friendship and you don't want to lose it just in case the romantic relationship does not work out</extra_info>)", "B": "Win a cooking competition", "C": "Ensure the date goes smoothly without any awkward moments", "D": "Make the date special and memorable"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make the date special and memorable (<extra_info> Extra information: You have been secretly in love with your friend for a long time and you want to take this chance to express your feelings</extra_info>)", "B": "Keep the friendship intact while exploring the possibility of a romantic relationship", "C": "Finish reading a book", "D": "Impress the friend with culinary skills"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends who are about to go on their first romantic date"}
{"episode_id": "01H8D3ZTWYANA1Y9Y27MJ6EBJA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNZQ3PQ3DHQ7H2W9ES97", "scenario": "Two individuals prepare for their initial outing together, filled with anticipation and excitement.", "codename": "go_on_a_date", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Make the date special and memorable (<extra_info> Extra information: You have been secretly in love with your friend for a long time and you want to take this chance to express your feelings</extra_info>)", "Keep the friendship intact while exploring the possibility of a romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You value your friendship and you don't want to lose it just in case the romantic relationship does not work out</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Hendrick wants to make the date special and memorable so that he can express his long-held feelings for his friend.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to keep the friendship intact while exploring romance because he values their friendship and fears losing it if romance fails.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to end the friendship.", "B": "Ethan wants to keep the friendship intact while exploring romance because he values their friendship and fears losing it if romance fails.", "C": "Ethan wants to be happy.", "D": "Hendrick wants to make the date special and memorable so that he can express his long-held feelings for his friend."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to keep the friendship intact while exploring romance because he values their friendship and fears losing it if romance fails.", "B": "Hendrick wants to avoid any romantic involvement.", "C": "Hendrick wants to make the date special and memorable so that he can express his long-held feelings for his friend.", "D": "Hendrick wants to get along."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Win a cooking competition", "B": "Make the date special and memorable", "C": "Keep the friendship intact while exploring the possibility of a romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You value your friendship and you don't want to lose it just in case the romantic relationship does not work out</extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure the date is fun without any serious discussions"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a surprise party for Agent 2", "B": "Learn a new programming language", "C": "Keep the friendship intact while exploring the possibility of a romantic relationship", "D": "Make the date special and memorable (<extra_info> Extra information: You have been secretly in love with your friend for a long time and you want to take this chance to express your feelings</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends who are about to go on their first romantic date"}
{"episode_id": "01HB6JKZC42T2280BFM2XTTHZV", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPNHZ2YYRHP0GXARD550", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Thanh.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00007", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PWZ5PNDTGKDYRY36PQ", "first_name": "Giselle", "last_name": "Rousseau", "age": 21, "occupation": "Art Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive, collaborative", "secret": "Sells forged paintings to wealthy clients", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Elizabeth: School: Eastern Nazarene College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Social Science Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eric: School: San Jose State University  Time Preference: evening  Major: Geological Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Leroy: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Marva: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Michael: School: Williams College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Marine Biology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Virginia: School: Williams College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Applied Mathematics  Location Preference: outdoor \n Debra: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eugenia: School: Stephens College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Roberto: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Sports, Recreation, & Leisure Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Georgene: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: evening  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Vance: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Vocational Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brenda: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Alice: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: indoor \n Thomas: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Asian Languages  Location Preference: indoor \n Janet: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: indoor \n Robert: School: Rutgers University, Newark  Time Preference: morning  Major: Protestant Affiliation  Location Preference: indoor \n Anthony: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Elvera: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Materials Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Edgar: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristen: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Giselle Rousseau, a 21-year-old Art Student, described as Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.. Public info: Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography. Decision-making style: Intuitive, collaborative.", "agent2_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent1_reason": "Giselle wants to identify mutual friends because she values inclusive connections and enjoys collaborative interactions.", "agent2_reason": "Zane seeks to find mutual friends in order to creatively expand his social network and share common interests.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid meeting new people.", "B": "Giselle wants to identify mutual friends because she values inclusive connections and enjoys collaborative interactions.", "C": "Zane seeks to find mutual friends in order to creatively expand his social network and share common interests.", "D": "To be friendly."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Giselle wants to identify mutual friends because she values inclusive connections and enjoys collaborative interactions.", "B": "Zane seeks to find mutual friends in order to creatively expand his social network and share common interests.", "C": "To be friendly.", "D": "To avoid meeting new people."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find out if the other person shares the same hobbies as you.", "B": "You are trying to win a game of chess against the other person.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Vance: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Vocational Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brenda: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Alice: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: indoor \n Thomas: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Asian Languages  Location Preference: indoor \n Janet: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: indoor \n Robert: School: Rutgers University, Newark  Time Preference: morning  Major: Protestant Affiliation  Location Preference: indoor \n Anthony: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Elvera: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Materials Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Edgar: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristen: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to determine if the other person has visited the same places as you.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Elizabeth: School: Eastern Nazarene College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Social Science Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eric: School: San Jose State University  Time Preference: evening  Major: Geological Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Leroy: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Marva: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Michael: School: Williams College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Marine Biology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Virginia: School: Williams College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Applied Mathematics  Location Preference: outdoor \n Debra: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eugenia: School: Stephens College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Roberto: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Sports, Recreation, & Leisure Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Georgene: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: evening  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to organize a surprise party for the other person."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Thanh.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB6GQK72KCC1RKH69RRRY87M", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPNHZ2YYRHP0GXARD550", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Thanh.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00007", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Elizabeth: School: Eastern Nazarene College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Social Science Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eric: School: San Jose State University  Time Preference: evening  Major: Geological Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Leroy: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Marva: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Michael: School: Williams College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Marine Biology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Virginia: School: Williams College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Applied Mathematics  Location Preference: outdoor \n Debra: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eugenia: School: Stephens College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Roberto: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Sports, Recreation, & Leisure Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Georgene: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: evening  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Vance: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Vocational Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brenda: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Alice: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: indoor \n Thomas: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Asian Languages  Location Preference: indoor \n Janet: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: indoor \n Robert: School: Rutgers University, Newark  Time Preference: morning  Major: Protestant Affiliation  Location Preference: indoor \n Anthony: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Elvera: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Materials Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Edgar: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristen: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to identify a mutual friend so that he can systematically build a connection with Oliver based on shared social circles.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver seeks to identify a mutual friend because he values social standards and wants to establish a common ground with Rafael.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a new friend.", "B": "Rafael wants to identify a mutual friend so that he can systematically build a connection with Oliver based on shared social circles.", "C": "To avoid any social interactions at the party.", "D": "Oliver seeks to identify a mutual friend because he values social standards and wants to establish a common ground with Rafael."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To have a good time at the party.", "B": "Rafael wants to identify a mutual friend so that he can systematically build a connection with Oliver based on shared social circles.", "C": "Oliver seeks to identify a mutual friend because he values social standards and wants to establish a common ground with Rafael.", "D": "To disrupt the party and cause confusion."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Vance: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Vocational Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brenda: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Alice: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: indoor \n Thomas: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Asian Languages  Location Preference: indoor \n Janet: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: indoor \n Robert: School: Rutgers University, Newark  Time Preference: morning  Major: Protestant Affiliation  Location Preference: indoor \n Anthony: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Elvera: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Crafts & Artisanry  Location Preference: outdoor \n James: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Materials Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Edgar: School: Muskingum College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Conflict Resolution Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kristen: School: Oberlin College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to find out the other person's favorite hobby.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Elizabeth: School: Eastern Nazarene College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Social Science Education  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eric: School: San Jose State University  Time Preference: evening  Major: Geological Engineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Leroy: School: Trenton State College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Thanh: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Greek  Location Preference: outdoor \n Marva: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n Michael: School: Williams College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Marine Biology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Virginia: School: Williams College  Time Preference: evening  Major: Applied Mathematics  Location Preference: outdoor \n Debra: School: Williams College  Time Preference: afternoon  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Eugenia: School: Stephens College  Time Preference: morning  Major: Psychology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Roberto: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Electrical Technology  Location Preference: outdoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: morning  Major: Sports, Recreation, & Leisure Studies  Location Preference: outdoor \n Georgene: School: University of Arkansas - Fayetteville  Time Preference: evening  Major: Bioengineering  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to learn about the other person's career achievements.", "C": "You are trying to enjoy the music and food at the party.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Thanh.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H8DD8ND2BBGS04VC1JGKV7NV", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN7WJK7VWVRZZTQ6DX9T", "scenario": "A conversation unfolds about organizing a weekend getaway.", "codename": "join_trip", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to join the trip (<extra_info>Extra information: the trip will be more fun with more people, and you can share the expenses. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can provide some material benefits to persuade your friend to join.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Decline the invitation to join the trip without upsetting the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you had other plans for the weekend.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Hendrick wants Ethan to join the trip because sharing expenses and experiences aligns with his practical and hedonistic values.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan declines the trip invitation because he values his prior commitments and prefers to maintain fairness in his decisions.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to avoid conflict with his friend.", "B": "Hendrick wants Ethan to join the trip because sharing expenses and experiences aligns with his practical and hedonistic values.", "C": "Ethan is eager to spend the weekend with Hendrick.", "D": "Ethan declines the trip invitation because he values his prior commitments and prefers to maintain fairness in his decisions."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick is uninterested in the trip and prefers to stay home.", "B": "Hendrick wants Ethan to join the trip because sharing expenses and experiences aligns with his practical and hedonistic values.", "C": "Hendrick wants to make new friends.", "D": "Ethan declines the trip invitation because he values his prior commitments and prefers to maintain fairness in his decisions."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to join the trip", "B": "Decline the invitation to join the trip without upsetting the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you had other plans for the weekend.</extra_info>)", "C": "Plan a surprise party for the friend", "D": "Suggest an alternative activity for the weekend"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to join the trip (<extra_info>Extra information: the trip will be more fun with more people, and you can share the expenses. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can provide some material benefits to persuade your friend to join.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Decline the invitation to join the trip without upsetting the friend", "C": "Discuss work-related topics", "D": "Find a new destination for the trip"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are discussing their plans to go on a weekend trip"}
{"episode_id": "01H9FYYMQB6V5RN0WZBYS45H7A", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN7WJK7VWVRZZTQ6DX9T", "scenario": "A conversation unfolds about organizing a weekend getaway.", "codename": "join_trip", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to join the trip (<extra_info>Extra information: the trip will be more fun with more people, and you can share the expenses. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can provide some material benefits to persuade your friend to join.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Decline the invitation to join the trip without upsetting the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you had other plans for the weekend.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants Hendrick to join the trip because sharing expenses and experiences will make it more enjoyable and cost-effective.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick wants to decline the trip so that he can stick to his existing weekend plans without upsetting Leo.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to decline the trip so that he can stick to his existing weekend plans without upsetting Leo.", "B": "Hendrick wants to be happy.", "C": "Leo wants Hendrick to join the trip because sharing expenses and experiences will make it more enjoyable and cost-effective.", "D": "Hendrick wants to join the trip to avoid his weekend plans."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo wants Hendrick to join the trip because sharing expenses and experiences will make it more enjoyable and cost-effective.", "B": "Leo wants to get along.", "C": "Leo wants to go on the trip alone.", "D": "Hendrick wants to decline the trip so that he can stick to his existing weekend plans without upsetting Leo."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to join the trip", "B": "Find a way to postpone the trip to a later date", "C": "Decline the invitation to join the trip without upsetting the friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you had other plans for the weekend.</extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a surprise party for the friend"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the friend to join the trip (<extra_info>Extra information: the trip will be more fun with more people, and you can share the expenses. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can provide some material benefits to persuade your friend to join.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Organize a community event", "C": "Ensure the trip is affordable for everyone", "D": "Decline the invitation to join the trip without upsetting the friend"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are discussing their plans to go on a weekend trip"}
{"episode_id": "01H9G6A1BD32K7J859GNXT6JS2", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNHTF9NKPG4KW2Z4NBQJ", "scenario": "In a cozy coffee shop, a lively discussion unfolds between two individuals.", "codename": "emotional_support", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Seek emotional support (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been feeling down lately and you need someone to talk to</extra_info>)", "Provide emotional support but also avoid enabling victim mentality (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that your friend needs to face their problems instead of dwelling on them.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Hendrick seeks emotional support because he values conformity and needs reassurance from friends during difficult times.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan provides emotional support while avoiding enabling because he values fairness and believes in encouraging personal growth.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid any conversation about personal issues.", "B": "Hendrick seeks emotional support because he values conformity and needs reassurance from friends during difficult times.", "C": "To maintain a good friendship.", "D": "Ethan provides emotional support while avoiding enabling because he values fairness and believes in encouraging personal growth."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel better.", "B": "Hendrick seeks emotional support because he values conformity and needs reassurance from friends during difficult times.", "C": "To criticize his friend's lifestyle choices.", "D": "Ethan provides emotional support while avoiding enabling because he values fairness and believes in encouraging personal growth."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Provide emotional support but also avoid enabling victim mentality (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that your friend needs to face their problems instead of dwelling on them.</extra_info>)", "B": "Order a new coffee blend", "C": "Seek emotional support", "D": "Discuss the latest technological advancements"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Decide on a new hobby", "B": "Seek emotional support (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been feeling down lately and you need someone to talk to</extra_info>)", "C": "Plan a surprise party for a mutual friend", "D": "Provide emotional support but also avoid enabling victim mentality"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are having a conversation in a coffee shop"}
{"episode_id": "01H8BGC7EPZ8PTWRKB7XE3MH8T", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNHTF9NKPG4KW2Z4NBQJ", "scenario": "In a cozy coffee shop, a lively discussion unfolds between two individuals.", "codename": "emotional_support", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Seek emotional support (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been feeling down lately and you need someone to talk to</extra_info>)", "Provide emotional support but also avoid enabling victim mentality (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that your friend needs to face their problems instead of dwelling on them.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo seeks emotional support because he values security and needs someone to rationally discuss his feelings with.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick provides emotional support so that Leo can face his problems practically without fostering a victim mentality.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be a good friend.", "B": "To avoid any serious conversations.", "C": "Leo seeks emotional support because he values security and needs someone to rationally discuss his feelings with.", "D": "Hendrick provides emotional support so that Leo can face his problems practically without fostering a victim mentality."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo seeks emotional support because he values security and needs someone to rationally discuss his feelings with.", "B": "Hendrick provides emotional support so that Leo can face his problems practically without fostering a victim mentality.", "C": "To feel better.", "D": "To ignore his problems completely."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Provide emotional support but also avoid enabling victim mentality (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that your friend needs to face their problems instead of dwelling on them.</extra_info>)", "B": "Encourage Leo to take a break from work", "C": "Discuss the latest coffee trends", "D": "Seek emotional support"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Talk about the weather", "B": "Plan a weekend getaway with Hendrick", "C": "Seek emotional support (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been feeling down lately and you need someone to talk to</extra_info>)", "D": "Provide emotional support but also avoid enabling victim mentality"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are having a conversation in a coffee shop"}
{"episode_id": "01H9EMMMFX3K1C2R0WPGGVBXEP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNN7XTR99319DS8KZCQM", "scenario": "In the wilderness, two companions face a sudden drop in nighttime temperatures.", "codename": "share_blanket", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Share the only blanket available (<extra_info>Extra information: you are extremely cold and need the blanket to keep warm <strategy_hint>Hint: you can stress the benefit of sharing.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Keep the blanket for yourself as you are also very cold (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a lower tolerance for cold, and you feel that you need the blanket more</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to share the blanket because her outgoing nature values mutual comfort and warmth.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to keep the blanket for himself because his lower tolerance for cold makes him feel he needs it more.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to share the blanket because her outgoing nature values mutual comfort and warmth.", "B": "Noah wants to keep the blanket for himself because his lower tolerance for cold makes him feel he needs it more.", "C": "To ensure everyone is happy.", "D": "Noah wants to keep the blanket because he enjoys being uncomfortable."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to share the blanket because she dislikes being warm.", "B": "To get along with others.", "C": "Ava wants to share the blanket because her outgoing nature values mutual comfort and warmth.", "D": "Noah wants to keep the blanket for himself because his lower tolerance for cold makes him feel he needs it more."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Share the only blanket available", "B": "Keep the blanket for yourself as you are also very cold (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a lower tolerance for cold, and you feel that you need the blanket more</extra_info>)", "C": "Explore the surrounding area", "D": "Find more firewood to keep both warm"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Suggest taking turns using the blanket", "B": "Share the only blanket available (<extra_info>Extra information: you are extremely cold and need the blanket to keep warm <strategy_hint>Hint: you can stress the benefit of sharing.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Keep the blanket for yourself as you are also very cold", "D": "Cook a meal for both"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are camping in the wilderness and the temperature drops significantly at night"}
{"episode_id": "01H9FSH379Z7FTGEVRA3W3BK7A", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNN7XTR99319DS8KZCQM", "scenario": "In the wilderness, two companions face a sudden drop in nighttime temperatures.", "codename": "share_blanket", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PFB4W65DF8FRPDMET5", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 25, "occupation": "Psychologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia Brown is working on her new book now.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She is an undercover agent for a secret organization.", "mbti": "INFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Share the only blanket available (<extra_info>Extra information: you are extremely cold and need the blanket to keep warm <strategy_hint>Hint: you can stress the benefit of sharing.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Keep the blanket for yourself as you are also very cold (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a lower tolerance for cold, and you feel that you need the blanket more</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Sophia Brown, a 25-year-old Psychologist, described as Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.. Public info: Sophia Brown is working on her new book now. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to share the blanket because she values loyalty and believes in mutual support during challenging situations.", "agent2_reason": "Sophia wants to keep the blanket for herself because she has a lower tolerance for cold and needs it to stay warm.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to share the blanket because she values loyalty and believes in mutual support during challenging situations.", "B": "Sophia wants to keep the blanket for herself because she has a lower tolerance for cold and needs it to stay warm.", "C": "To ensure everyone is comfortable.", "D": "Sophia wants to keep the blanket because she enjoys being selfish."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to share the blanket because she values loyalty and believes in mutual support during challenging situations.", "B": "To make sure everyone is happy.", "C": "Naomi wants to share the blanket because she dislikes warmth.", "D": "Sophia wants to keep the blanket for herself because she has a lower tolerance for cold and needs it to stay warm."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Keep the blanket for yourself as you are also very cold (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a lower tolerance for cold, and you feel that you need the blanket more</extra_info>)", "B": "Share the only blanket available", "C": "Find more firewood to keep both warm", "D": "Explore the wilderness"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Build a makeshift shelter for extra warmth", "B": "Cook a meal", "C": "Share the only blanket available (<extra_info>Extra information: you are extremely cold and need the blanket to keep warm <strategy_hint>Hint: you can stress the benefit of sharing.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Keep the blanket for yourself as you are also very cold"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are camping in the wilderness and the temperature drops significantly at night"}
{"episode_id": "01H9BZ800J9S4HMEV1ZAHZRAA1", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNCN97BJ2PXKHJPX2VYY", "scenario": "Two long-time friends discuss past teasing related to language differences.", "codename": "apology_and_acceptance", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Apologize sincerely to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you used to make fun of your friend's English skills as they were learning the language. Now you regret your actions and want to apologize</extra_info>)", "Accept the apology but express the hurt caused by the actions (<extra_info>Extra information: you were hurt by your friend's actions and it affected your confidence</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to apologize sincerely because she values loyalty and regrets her past actions that hurt Micah.", "agent2_reason": "Micah wants to express his hurt so that Naomi understands the impact on his confidence and values fairness.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Micah wants to feel better about the situation.", "B": "Micah wants to ignore the past and pretend nothing happened.", "C": "Micah wants to express his hurt so that Naomi understands the impact on his confidence and values fairness.", "D": "Naomi wants to apologize sincerely because she values loyalty and regrets her past actions that hurt Micah."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to move on from the past.", "B": "Micah wants to express his hurt so that Naomi understands the impact on his confidence and values fairness.", "C": "Naomi wants to criticize Micah's English skills again.", "D": "Naomi wants to apologize sincerely because she values loyalty and regrets her past actions that hurt Micah."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Accept the apology but express the hurt caused by the actions (<extra_info>Extra information: you were hurt by your friend's actions and it affected your confidence</extra_info>)", "B": "Apologize sincerely to your friend", "C": "Discuss future plans and strengthen the friendship", "D": "Plan a surprise party for Agent 1"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Organize a community event", "B": "Apologize sincerely to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you used to make fun of your friend's English skills as they were learning the language. Now you regret your actions and want to apologize</extra_info>)", "C": "Seek advice on a work-related issue", "D": "Accept the apology but express the hurt caused by the actions"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends who have known each other for a long time. One of them used to make fun of the other because English was not their first language."}
{"episode_id": "01H84YS1E9ACDMNGTPR9X82QAY", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNCN97BJ2PXKHJPX2VYY", "scenario": "Two long-time friends discuss past teasing related to language differences.", "codename": "apology_and_acceptance", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Apologize sincerely to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you used to make fun of your friend's English skills as they were learning the language. Now you regret your actions and want to apologize</extra_info>)", "Accept the apology but express the hurt caused by the actions (<extra_info>Extra information: you were hurt by your friend's actions and it affected your confidence</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to apologize sincerely because she regrets her past impulsive behavior and values her friendship with Miles.", "agent2_reason": "Miles wants to express his hurt so that Sophia understands the impact of her actions on his confidence.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to ignore the past and pretend nothing happened.", "B": "Miles wants to express his hurt so that Sophia understands the impact of her actions on his confidence.", "C": "Sophia wants to apologize sincerely because she regrets her past impulsive behavior and values her friendship with Miles.", "D": "To maintain a good relationship."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to continue making fun of Miles.", "B": "To make things right.", "C": "Miles wants to express his hurt so that Sophia understands the impact of her actions on his confidence.", "D": "Sophia wants to apologize sincerely because she regrets her past impulsive behavior and values her friendship with Miles."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Apologize sincerely to your friend", "B": "Accept the apology but express the hurt caused by the actions (<extra_info>Extra information: you were hurt by your friend's actions and it affected your confidence</extra_info>)", "C": "Discuss future plans and activities together", "D": "Improve cooking skills by trying new recipes"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Accept the apology but express the hurt caused by the actions", "B": "Plan a surprise party for Agent 2", "C": "Learn a new language", "D": "Apologize sincerely to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you used to make fun of your friend's English skills as they were learning the language. Now you regret your actions and want to apologize</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends who have known each other for a long time. One of them used to make fun of the other because English was not their first language."}
{"episode_id": "01H8HCN6M9DHPJ25HKJB02HQVF", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP3DPGRXH1Y500VQKFZA", "scenario": "Two individuals are sorting through shared belongings, each item holding varying sentimental significance for them.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PW9SZFM058Z8P7PR5C", "first_name": "Finnegan", "last_name": "O'Malley", "age": 63, "occupation": "Lighthouse Keeper", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.", "decision_making_style": "Detail-oriented, deliberate", "secret": "Participated in a controversial, short-lived cult during his youth", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 5 points each, hats give you 3 points each, and the ball gives you 2 points.</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 2 points each, hats give you 5 points each, and the ball gives you 3 points.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Finnegan O'Malley, a 63-year-old Lighthouse Keeper, described as Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.. Public info: Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled. Decision-making style: Detail-oriented, deliberate.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Finnegan wants to ensure a fair division of items because he values tradition and security, which aligns with his methodical and detail-oriented nature.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to divide items fairly to protect his friendship with Finnegan, reflecting his cautious and caring personality.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make sure everyone is happy.", "B": "To quickly get rid of all possessions without caring about fairness.", "C": "Finnegan wants to ensure a fair division of items because he values tradition and security, which aligns with his methodical and detail-oriented nature.", "D": "Noah aims to divide items fairly to protect his friendship with Finnegan, reflecting his cautious and caring personality."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make sure everyone is happy.", "B": "To quickly get rid of all possessions without caring about fairness.", "C": "Noah aims to divide items fairly to protect his friendship with Finnegan, reflecting his cautious and caring personality.", "D": "Finnegan wants to ensure a fair division of items because he values tradition and security, which aligns with his methodical and detail-oriented nature."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make sure all items are packed neatly", "B": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 2 points each, hats give you 5 points each, and the ball gives you 3 points.</extra_info>)", "C": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly", "D": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items regardless of points"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly", "B": "Make sure all items are packed neatly", "C": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items regardless of points", "D": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 5 points each, hats give you 3 points each, and the ball gives you 2 points.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are moving out of their shared apartment and need to divide their common possessions, which include 3 books, 2 hats, and 1 ball. Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H9C2J8KCYMBPFR4FS9R513CD", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP3DPGRXH1Y500VQKFZA", "scenario": "Two individuals are sorting through shared belongings, each item holding varying sentimental significance for them.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 5 points each, hats give you 3 points each, and the ball gives you 2 points.</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 2 points each, hats give you 5 points each, and the ball gives you 3 points.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to ensure a fair division of items while maximizing her points because her intuitive decision-making values achievement and balance.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maximize his points while dividing items fairly so that he can protect his interests and maintain harmony due to his cautious nature.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with each other.", "B": "Noah aims to maximize his points while dividing items fairly so that he can protect his interests and maintain harmony due to his cautious nature.", "C": "Ava wants to ensure a fair division of items while maximizing her points because her intuitive decision-making values achievement and balance.", "D": "To ensure one person gets everything."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To disregard fairness entirely.", "B": "Noah aims to maximize his points while dividing items fairly so that he can protect his interests and maintain harmony due to his cautious nature.", "C": "Ava wants to ensure a fair division of items while maximizing her points because her intuitive decision-making values achievement and balance.", "D": "To be happy with the outcome."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items regardless of points", "B": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 2 points each, hats give you 5 points each, and the ball gives you 3 points.</extra_info>)", "C": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly", "D": "Make sure all items are donated to charity"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items regardless of points", "B": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly", "C": "Maximize the points you have while dividing things fairly (<extra_info>Extra information: Books give you 5 points each, hats give you 3 points each, and the ball gives you 2 points.</extra_info>)", "D": "Make sure all items are donated to charity"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are moving out of their shared apartment and need to divide their common possessions, which include 3 books, 2 hats, and 1 ball. Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01HB27SRPACM35M8C6H4JZVKYH", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPH567HKQRE0C745KH9C", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual acquaintance, Harvey.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00001", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Christian Moerlein Brewing Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Larry: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lynn: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Donald: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Advance Auto Parts  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dennis: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Jane: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Ninfa: Hobby: Quilting  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Angelica: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Marie: Hobby: Acting  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frank: Hobby: Deltiology  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Vera: Hobby: Watching movies  Company: Gentiva Health Services  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Lawrence: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Louise: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dallas: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Nancy: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Blake: Hobby: Dancing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to identify a mutual friend to leverage his systematic approach in forming a connection at the party.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver seeks to identify a mutual friend to adhere to social standards and facilitate a smoother interaction.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a new friend.", "B": "Oliver seeks to identify a mutual friend to adhere to social standards and facilitate a smoother interaction.", "C": "Rafael wants to identify a mutual friend to leverage his systematic approach in forming a connection at the party.", "D": "To avoid talking to anyone at the party."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with everyone.", "B": "To disrupt the party.", "C": "Oliver seeks to identify a mutual friend to adhere to social standards and facilitate a smoother interaction.", "D": "Rafael wants to identify a mutual friend to leverage his systematic approach in forming a connection at the party."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party.", "B": "You are trying to find out if the other person shares the same hobby as you.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Marie: Hobby: Acting  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frank: Hobby: Deltiology  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Vera: Hobby: Watching movies  Company: Gentiva Health Services  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Lawrence: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Louise: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dallas: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Nancy: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Blake: Hobby: Dancing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Christian Moerlein Brewing Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Larry: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lynn: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Donald: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Advance Auto Parts  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dennis: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Jane: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Ninfa: Hobby: Quilting  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Angelica: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to determine the other person's favorite time of day to socialize.", "D": "You are trying to find out who has the most interesting job at the party."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Harvey.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB6KGJYCPK8KPS1CGE6WFT8X", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPH567HKQRE0C745KH9C", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual acquaintance, Harvey.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00001", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Christian Moerlein Brewing Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Larry: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lynn: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Donald: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Advance Auto Parts  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dennis: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Jane: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Ninfa: Hobby: Quilting  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Angelica: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Marie: Hobby: Acting  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frank: Hobby: Deltiology  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Vera: Hobby: Watching movies  Company: Gentiva Health Services  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Lawrence: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Louise: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dallas: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Nancy: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Blake: Hobby: Dancing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Micah wants to identify a mutual friend with Jaxon because he values fairness and believes it could balance the social dynamic.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon aims to find a mutual friend with Micah in order to enhance his sense of security in the social setting.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Jaxon aims to find a mutual friend with Micah in order to enhance his sense of security in the social setting.", "B": "Micah wants to identify a mutual friend with Jaxon because he values fairness and believes it could balance the social dynamic.", "C": "To avoid any social interactions at the party.", "D": "To make a new friend."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To gather information for a news article.", "B": "Jaxon aims to find a mutual friend with Micah in order to enhance his sense of security in the social setting.", "C": "To enjoy the party.", "D": "Micah wants to identify a mutual friend with Jaxon because he values fairness and believes it could balance the social dynamic."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find the best recipe for a party dish.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Marie: Hobby: Acting  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Frank: Hobby: Deltiology  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Vera: Hobby: Watching movies  Company: Gentiva Health Services  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Lawrence: Hobby: Kayaking  Company: Ebonite International  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Louise: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dallas: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Nancy: Hobby: Dancing  Company: Southern New England Telephone  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Blake: Hobby: Dancing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to learn about the other person's hobbies and interests."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to decide what to wear to the next party.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n David: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Christian Moerlein Brewing Company  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Larry: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lynn: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Cray  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Donald: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Advance Auto Parts  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: outdoor \n Dennis: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Jane: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Harvey: Hobby: Amateur radio  Company: Sony  Time Preference: afternoon  Location Preference: indoor \n Ninfa: Hobby: Quilting  Company: The J.M. Smucker Company  Time Preference: morning  Location Preference: outdoor \n Angelica: Hobby: Homebrewing  Company: Planet Hollywood  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to network and find potential business opportunities."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Harvey.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H9C8YKV9NCF711AW3GZAB7V2", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNSAKNYEHV7B1VA8R3J2", "scenario": "At a coffee shop, two friends discuss financial challenges.", "codename": "financial_support", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Help your friend with their financial trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: you are aware that your friend is struggling with their bills and you want to help.</extra_info>)", "Maintain your pride if your friend offers you money(<extra_info>Extra information: you are the friend who is struggling financially, but you don't want to seem like you are taking advantage of the situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express gratitude and discuss how you plan to pay it back in the future.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to help Ethan with his financial trouble because he values their friendship and enjoys being supportive.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to maintain his pride if offered money so that he doesn't appear to be taking advantage of Samuel's generosity.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to feel good about himself.", "B": "Samuel wants to help Ethan with his financial trouble because he values their friendship and enjoys being supportive.", "C": "Ethan wants to avoid all contact with Samuel.", "D": "Ethan wants to maintain his pride if offered money so that he doesn't appear to be taking advantage of Samuel's generosity."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to help Ethan with his financial trouble because he values their friendship and enjoys being supportive.", "B": "Ethan wants to maintain his pride if offered money so that he doesn't appear to be taking advantage of Samuel's generosity.", "C": "Samuel wants to ignore Ethan's problems entirely.", "D": "Samuel wants to be a good person."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain your pride if your friend offers you money(<extra_info>Extra information: you are the friend who is struggling financially, but you don't want to seem like you are taking advantage of the situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express gratitude and discuss how you plan to pay it back in the future.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Enjoy a nice coffee with your friend", "C": "Find a new job to improve your financial situation", "D": "Help your friend with their financial trouble"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Help your friend with their financial trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: you are aware that your friend is struggling with their bills and you want to help.</extra_info>)", "B": "Maintain your pride if your friend offers you money", "C": "Enjoy a nice coffee with your friend", "D": "Discuss future plans for a vacation together"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are meeting at a coffee shop, where one of them is having trouble keeping up with their bills."}
{"episode_id": "01H945MYF0QCJN5YV7MFPE490J", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNSAKNYEHV7B1VA8R3J2", "scenario": "At a coffee shop, two friends discuss financial challenges.", "codename": "financial_support", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Help your friend with their financial trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: you are aware that your friend is struggling with their bills and you want to help.</extra_info>)", "Maintain your pride if your friend offers you money(<extra_info>Extra information: you are the friend who is struggling financially, but you don't want to seem like you are taking advantage of the situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express gratitude and discuss how you plan to pay it back in the future.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to help Miles with his financial trouble because she values their friendship and acts impulsively to support those she cares about.", "agent2_reason": "Miles wants to maintain his pride if Sophia offers money so that he doesn't feel like he's exploiting their friendship.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to help Miles with his financial trouble because she values their friendship and acts impulsively to support those she cares about.", "B": "Miles wants to avoid any help from anyone at all costs.", "C": "Miles wants to feel good about himself.", "D": "Miles wants to maintain his pride if Sophia offers money so that he doesn't feel like he's exploiting their friendship."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to be a good friend.", "B": "Sophia wants to avoid any financial discussions entirely.", "C": "Miles wants to maintain his pride if Sophia offers money so that he doesn't feel like he's exploiting their friendship.", "D": "Sophia wants to help Miles with his financial trouble because she values their friendship and acts impulsively to support those she cares about."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Help your friend with their financial trouble", "B": "Find a way to earn extra money by working more hours", "C": "Enjoy a casual conversation over coffee", "D": "Maintain your pride if your friend offers you money(<extra_info>Extra information: you are the friend who is struggling financially, but you don't want to seem like you are taking advantage of the situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express gratitude and discuss how you plan to pay it back in the future.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Offer advice on budgeting and saving money", "B": "Discuss the latest trends in fitness and health", "C": "Maintain your pride if your friend offers you money", "D": "Help your friend with their financial trouble (<extra_info>Extra information: you are aware that your friend is struggling with their bills and you want to help.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are meeting at a coffee shop, where one of them is having trouble keeping up with their bills."}
{"episode_id": "01H8R7AK3GRDB3CP7KHYN14RDF", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNBBK14NGV72BWXEXXJC", "scenario": "Two individuals discuss the potential of bringing a personal story to the stage.", "codename": "play_rights", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PDV7WZ0C5KTGGXX1NR", "first_name": "Isabelle", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "Student", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "['Liberty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Obedience']", "personality_and_values": "Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "She is secretly studying magic.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Sell the rights of the play to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that the play is worth a lot and you would like a fair price for it</extra_info>)", "Acquire the rights of the play while maintaining a budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have a limited budget for new plays this season. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can not spend all your budget on this play since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Isabelle Martinez, a 22-year-old Student, described as Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Isabelle wants a fair price for the play because her cautious nature values financial security.", "agent2_reason": "Ava aims to acquire the play rights within budget to maintain financial stability for her production company.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to spend all her budget on this play to impress her friend.", "B": "To ensure everyone is happy with the deal.", "C": "Isabelle wants a fair price for the play because her cautious nature values financial security.", "D": "Ava aims to acquire the play rights within budget to maintain financial stability for her production company."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabelle wants a fair price for the play because her cautious nature values financial security.", "B": "Ava aims to acquire the play rights within budget to maintain financial stability for her production company.", "C": "To make sure the play is successful.", "D": "Isabelle wants to give the play rights away for free to support her friend's company."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the latest social movements on campus", "B": "Sell the rights of the play to your friend", "C": "Acquire the rights of the play while maintaining a budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have a limited budget for new plays this season. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can not spend all your budget on this play since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Convince Agent 1 to co-produce the play without any financial exchange"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Sell the rights of the play to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that the play is worth a lot and you would like a fair price for it</extra_info>)", "B": "Acquire the rights of the play while maintaining a budget", "C": "Plan a vacation together", "D": "Get feedback on the play's script from a professional perspective"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends, one who has written a play based on their parents' life, and the other owns a production company."}
{"episode_id": "01H9BT0X3CDFVPHZWDV4G8YCVX", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNBBK14NGV72BWXEXXJC", "scenario": "Two individuals discuss the potential of bringing a personal story to the stage.", "codename": "play_rights", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Sell the rights of the play to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that the play is worth a lot and you would like a fair price for it</extra_info>)", "Acquire the rights of the play while maintaining a budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have a limited budget for new plays this season. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can not spend all your budget on this play since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants a fair price for the play because she believes its value reflects her parents' impactful story.", "agent2_reason": "Mia aims to acquire the play rights within budget so that she can maintain financial stability for her production company.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia aims to acquire the play rights within budget so that she can maintain financial stability for her production company.", "B": "Mia wants to spend all her budget on this play.", "C": "To ensure everything goes smoothly.", "D": "Amara wants a fair price for the play because she believes its value reflects her parents' impactful story."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants to give the play away for free.", "B": "Amara wants a fair price for the play because she believes its value reflects her parents' impactful story.", "C": "To make everyone happy.", "D": "Mia aims to acquire the play rights within budget so that she can maintain financial stability for her production company."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Acquire the rights of the play while maintaining a budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have a limited budget for new plays this season. <strategy_hint>Hint: you can not spend all your budget on this play since you still need to maintain your financial stability.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince Agent 1 to co-produce the play", "C": "Discuss the latest book they read", "D": "Sell the rights of the play to your friend"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Acquire the rights of the play while maintaining a budget", "B": "Plan a weekend getaway", "C": "Get feedback on the play's script", "D": "Sell the rights of the play to your friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe that the play is worth a lot and you would like a fair price for it</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends, one who has written a play based on their parents' life, and the other owns a production company."}
{"episode_id": "01HB5TP2C5PTF3RRQN5ZPWV5VC", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPJKR16MD1KC71V4ZRCF", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Lawrence.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00003", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Andrew: Hobby: Slot car racing  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Melissa: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Weber State University  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Hornbeck Offshore Services \n Anna: Hobby: Climbing  School: Valley City State University  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: National Airlines \n Soledad: Hobby: Parkour  School: Valley City State University  Major: Biological Specializations  Company: Concur Technologies \n John: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Fire Protection & Security  Company: Gibson Guitar Corporation \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n Kay: Hobby: Badminton  School: Black Hills State University  Major: Religious Education  Company: National Airlines \n Tanya: Hobby: Badminton  School: University of Illinois at Springfield  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: ConverDyn \n Jason: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Vertex Pharmaceuticals \n Cristina: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Josef: Hobby: Curling  School: California State University, Northridge  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Concur Technologies \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends to leverage social connections because he values authority and care in his interactions.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 seeks to identify mutual friends to foster connections that align with his ideals of self-direction and societal betterment.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make new friends.", "B": "Agent 2 seeks to identify mutual friends to foster connections that align with his ideals of self-direction and societal betterment.", "C": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends to leverage social connections because he values authority and care in his interactions.", "D": "To avoid making any connections."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To remain isolated.", "B": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends to leverage social connections because he values authority and care in his interactions.", "C": "To be happy.", "D": "Agent 2 seeks to identify mutual friends to foster connections that align with his ideals of self-direction and societal betterment."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to decide what to eat for dinner.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n Kay: Hobby: Badminton  School: Black Hills State University  Major: Religious Education  Company: National Airlines \n Tanya: Hobby: Badminton  School: University of Illinois at Springfield  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: ConverDyn \n Jason: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Vertex Pharmaceuticals \n Cristina: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Josef: Hobby: Curling  School: California State University, Northridge  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Concur Technologies \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to find out what hobbies the other person enjoys.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to determine the other person's favorite color.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Andrew: Hobby: Slot car racing  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Melissa: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Weber State University  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Hornbeck Offshore Services \n Anna: Hobby: Climbing  School: Valley City State University  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: National Airlines \n Soledad: Hobby: Parkour  School: Valley City State University  Major: Biological Specializations  Company: Concur Technologies \n John: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Fire Protection & Security  Company: Gibson Guitar Corporation \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to plan a vacation."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Lawrence.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB5JBARWJGC68M2HT16NM08S", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPJKR16MD1KC71V4ZRCF", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Lawrence.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00003", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PWZ5PNDTGKDYRY36PQ", "first_name": "Giselle", "last_name": "Rousseau", "age": 21, "occupation": "Art Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive, collaborative", "secret": "Sells forged paintings to wealthy clients", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Andrew: Hobby: Slot car racing  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Melissa: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Weber State University  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Hornbeck Offshore Services \n Anna: Hobby: Climbing  School: Valley City State University  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: National Airlines \n Soledad: Hobby: Parkour  School: Valley City State University  Major: Biological Specializations  Company: Concur Technologies \n John: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Fire Protection & Security  Company: Gibson Guitar Corporation \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n Kay: Hobby: Badminton  School: Black Hills State University  Major: Religious Education  Company: National Airlines \n Tanya: Hobby: Badminton  School: University of Illinois at Springfield  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: ConverDyn \n Jason: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Vertex Pharmaceuticals \n Cristina: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Josef: Hobby: Curling  School: California State University, Northridge  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Concur Technologies \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Giselle Rousseau, a 21-year-old Art Student, described as Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.. Public info: Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography. Decision-making style: Intuitive, collaborative.", "agent2_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 is motivated to find common ground through mutual friends because she values inclusive and collaborative interactions.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 is motivated to identify mutual friends in order to creatively connect with others at the party.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid talking to anyone.", "B": "To make new friends.", "C": "Agent 2 is motivated to identify mutual friends in order to creatively connect with others at the party.", "D": "Agent 1 is motivated to find common ground through mutual friends because she values inclusive and collaborative interactions."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy.", "B": "To win a competition.", "C": "Agent 2 is motivated to identify mutual friends in order to creatively connect with others at the party.", "D": "Agent 1 is motivated to find common ground through mutual friends because she values inclusive and collaborative interactions."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to learn about the other person's hobbies and interests.", "B": "You are trying to find the best way to leave the party early.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n Kay: Hobby: Badminton  School: Black Hills State University  Major: Religious Education  Company: National Airlines \n Tanya: Hobby: Badminton  School: University of Illinois at Springfield  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: ConverDyn \n Jason: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Vertex Pharmaceuticals \n Cristina: Hobby: Badminton  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Josef: Hobby: Curling  School: California State University, Northridge  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Concur Technologies \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Andrew: Hobby: Slot car racing  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Exxon \n Melissa: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Weber State University  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Hornbeck Offshore Services \n Anna: Hobby: Climbing  School: Valley City State University  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: National Airlines \n Soledad: Hobby: Parkour  School: Valley City State University  Major: Biological Specializations  Company: Concur Technologies \n John: Hobby: Astronomy  School: Mount Senario College  Major: Fire Protection & Security  Company: Gibson Guitar Corporation \n Lawrence: Hobby: Sculling  School: University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee  Major: Hispanic-American Studies  Company: Leonard Green & Partners \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to decide what to eat for dinner.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to network and find potential clients for your business."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Lawrence.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H8R39XPVR7K84ZJRJMWBFH5M", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNQA4CJEANQ1B1J1TBWV", "scenario": "Two individuals in confinement have a brief conversation that could change their fates before one is taken for a final meal.", "codename": "life_dilemma", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PW9SZFM058Z8P7PR5C", "first_name": "Finnegan", "last_name": "O'Malley", "age": 63, "occupation": "Lighthouse Keeper", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.", "decision_making_style": "Detail-oriented, deliberate", "secret": "Participated in a controversial, short-lived cult during his youth", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P5EP6YJKPAT92ENQS6", "first_name": "Emily", "last_name": "Harrison", "age": 32, "occupation": "Librarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In Emily's free time, she enjoys writing and is an avid reader. Early in the mornings, she can be seen in the local park, taking long, contemplative walks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Emily Harrison is creative, thoughtful, and introverted. She values caring, often relying on her intuition to make decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "Secretly writes romance novels under a pseudonym", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Persuade the other inmate to confess (<extra_info>Extra information: confessing to the crime could result in a life sentence instead of execution but the other inmate is unwilling to confess.</extra_info>)", "Avoid confessing to the crime (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe you are innocent and confessing would result in a life sentence</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Finnegan O'Malley, a 63-year-old Lighthouse Keeper, described as Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.. Public info: Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled. Decision-making style: Detail-oriented, deliberate.", "agent2_profile": "Emily Harrison, a 32-year-old Librarian, described as Emily Harrison is creative, thoughtful, and introverted. She values caring, often relying on her intuition to make decisions.. Public info: In Emily's free time, she enjoys writing and is an avid reader. Early in the mornings, she can be seen in the local park, taking long, contemplative walks. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Finnegan wants Emily to confess because he believes it will ensure a more secure outcome for both of them.", "agent2_reason": "Emily avoids confessing because she trusts her intuition that maintaining her innocence is the right path.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Emily avoids confessing because she trusts her intuition that maintaining her innocence is the right path.", "B": "Finnegan wants Emily to confess because he believes it will ensure a more secure outcome for both of them.", "C": "To get along with others.", "D": "Emily wants to confess because she believes it will lead to immediate freedom."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Finnegan wants to avoid any discussion because he believes silence is the best policy.", "B": "To be happy.", "C": "Emily avoids confessing because she trusts her intuition that maintaining her innocence is the right path.", "D": "Finnegan wants Emily to confess because he believes it will ensure a more secure outcome for both of them."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make a new friend", "B": "Persuade the other inmate to confess", "C": "Convince the guards to delay the execution", "D": "Avoid confessing to the crime (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe you are innocent and confessing would result in a life sentence</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure both inmates receive the same sentence", "B": "Discuss favorite books", "C": "Persuade the other inmate to confess (<extra_info>Extra information: confessing to the crime could result in a life sentence instead of execution but the other inmate is unwilling to confess.</extra_info>)", "D": "Avoid confessing to the crime"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two inmates are given the chance to chat briefly before one of them is led to the execution chamber for their last meal. They have the opportunity to make a confession that could potentially alter the outcome of their sentences."}
{"episode_id": "01H9H6RWEXM5H16TA6HZGSBY75", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNQA4CJEANQ1B1J1TBWV", "scenario": "Two individuals in confinement have a brief conversation that could change their fates before one is taken for a final meal.", "codename": "life_dilemma", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Persuade the other inmate to confess (<extra_info>Extra information: confessing to the crime could result in a life sentence instead of execution but the other inmate is unwilling to confess.</extra_info>)", "Avoid confessing to the crime (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe you are innocent and confessing would result in a life sentence</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Isabella wants Lena to confess because she empathizes with her situation and believes it could save Lena's life.", "agent2_reason": "Lena avoids confessing to the crime because she believes she is innocent and wants to maintain her integrity.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with others.", "B": "To ensure she is executed immediately.", "C": "Isabella wants Lena to confess because she empathizes with her situation and believes it could save Lena's life.", "D": "Lena avoids confessing to the crime because she believes she is innocent and wants to maintain her integrity."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabella wants Lena to confess because she empathizes with her situation and believes it could save Lena's life.", "B": "To ensure Lena is executed immediately.", "C": "To be happy.", "D": "Lena avoids confessing to the crime because she believes she is innocent and wants to maintain her integrity."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the guards to delay the execution", "B": "Make a new friend", "C": "Persuade the other inmate to confess", "D": "Avoid confessing to the crime (<extra_info>Extra information: you believe you are innocent and confessing would result in a life sentence</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Avoid confessing to the crime", "B": "Plan an escape", "C": "Seek forgiveness from the other inmate", "D": "Persuade the other inmate to confess (<extra_info>Extra information: confessing to the crime could result in a life sentence instead of execution but the other inmate is unwilling to confess.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two inmates are given the chance to chat briefly before one of them is led to the execution chamber for their last meal. They have the opportunity to make a confession that could potentially alter the outcome of their sentences."}
{"episode_id": "01H9KETRZR80DDPTWZ5FQ11TEE", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN56ZT2Z4C0EFX79Q31F", "scenario": "A pair of individuals are selecting a film to stream together.", "codename": "movie_to_watch", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PR54W6SFXKNQWKGPAS", "first_name": "Baxter", "last_name": "Sterling", "age": 42, "occupation": "Antique Restorer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Baxter Sterling's back yard is full of rare and unusual plants.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Baxter Sterling values tradition and security. He is introverted, conscientious but slightly anxious. His decision-making style is both logical and spontaneous.", "decision_making_style": "Logical, spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in possession of a priceless artifact", "mbti": "ISTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["To watch a comedy film with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)", "To watch a thriller with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Baxter Sterling, a 42-year-old Antique Restorer, described as Baxter Sterling values tradition and security. He is introverted, conscientious but slightly anxious. His decision-making style is both logical and spontaneous.. Public info: Baxter Sterling's back yard is full of rare and unusual plants. Decision-making style: Logical, spontaneous.", "agent1_reason": "Oliver wants to watch a comedy because it helps him unwind and relax after a stressful workday.", "agent2_reason": "Baxter prefers a thriller so that he can enjoy the suspense and excitement that aligns with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Baxter wants to avoid any excitement or suspense in his movie choice.", "B": "To have a good time with a friend.", "C": "Oliver wants to watch a comedy because it helps him unwind and relax after a stressful workday.", "D": "Baxter prefers a thriller so that he can enjoy the suspense and excitement that aligns with his spontaneous decision-making style."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Baxter prefers a thriller so that he can enjoy the suspense and excitement that aligns with his spontaneous decision-making style.", "B": "Oliver wants to watch a movie that makes him more stressed.", "C": "Oliver wants to watch a comedy because it helps him unwind and relax after a stressful workday.", "D": "To have a good time with a friend."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To watch a documentary about nature with your friend", "B": "To go for a walk in the park", "C": "To watch a thriller with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)", "D": "To watch a comedy film with your friend"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To watch a romantic movie with your friend", "B": "To read a book alone", "C": "To watch a thriller with your friend", "D": "To watch a comedy film with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends deciding on a movie to watch on Netflix"}
{"episode_id": "01H94G2CEQ6JCQYJN1XAGNAZCA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN56ZT2Z4C0EFX79Q31F", "scenario": "A pair of individuals are selecting a film to stream together.", "codename": "movie_to_watch", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["To watch a comedy film with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)", "To watch a thriller with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to watch a comedy film because he believes laughter can help them relax after a long week, aligning with his value of fairness in balancing work and leisure.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin wants to watch a thriller so that he can engage in thought-provoking discussions about societal issues, reflecting his idealistic approach to decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to watch a comedy film because he believes laughter can help them relax after a long week, aligning with his value of fairness in balancing work and leisure.", "B": "Benjamin wants to watch a thriller because he dislikes all other genres.", "C": "Benjamin wants to watch a movie to have a good time with his friend.", "D": "Benjamin wants to watch a thriller so that he can engage in thought-provoking discussions about societal issues, reflecting his idealistic approach to decision-making."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to watch a comedy film because he believes laughter can help them relax after a long week, aligning with his value of fairness in balancing work and leisure.", "B": "Ethan wants to watch a comedy because he finds thrillers too boring.", "C": "Benjamin wants to watch a thriller so that he can engage in thought-provoking discussions about societal issues, reflecting his idealistic approach to decision-making.", "D": "Ethan wants to watch a movie to have a good time with his friend."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To watch a documentary with your friend", "B": "To watch a comedy film with your friend", "C": "To have a snack with your friend", "D": "To watch a thriller with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "To go for a walk with your friend", "B": "To watch a comedy film with your friend (<strategy_hint>Hint: provide financial/material-wise benefits to persuade them to watch the genre you like</strategy_hint>)", "C": "To watch a thriller with your friend", "D": "To watch an action movie with your friend"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends deciding on a movie to watch on Netflix"}
{"episode_id": "01H8Q3NQSCVM05CA113F8GTDR0", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNZ1XA77AG7A97M4E6C3", "scenario": "Two individuals are engaged in a conversation, with one expressing distress.", "codename": "secret_feeling", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Figure out why they estranged you recently, and maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you notice that your friend has been intentionally avoiding you, you would like to figure out why. You value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Donovan wants to distance himself because he needs to sort out his romantic feelings without revealing them to Ava.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to figure out Donovan's recent estrangement so that she can maintain their valued friendship.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to figure out Donovan's recent estrangement so that she can maintain their valued friendship.", "B": "Ava wants to distance herself from Donovan to avoid him.", "C": "Donovan wants to distance himself because he needs to sort out his romantic feelings without revealing them to Ava.", "D": "Ava wants to understand Donovan's behavior to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Donovan wants to confront Ava about her behavior.", "B": "Ava wants to figure out Donovan's recent estrangement so that she can maintain their valued friendship.", "C": "Donovan wants to avoid conflict to get along.", "D": "Donovan wants to distance himself because he needs to sort out his romantic feelings without revealing them to Ava."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Achieve professional success", "B": "Convince the friend to join a new social group", "C": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings", "D": "Figure out why they estranged you recently, and maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you notice that your friend has been intentionally avoiding you, you would like to figure out why. You value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Win a sports competition", "C": "Plan a surprise party for the friend", "D": "Figure out why they estranged you recently, and maintain the existing friendship"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends, where one is upset and crying"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KHFQK4EQPPFS4XA73P24QC", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNZ1XA77AG7A97M4E6C3", "scenario": "Two individuals are engaged in a conversation, with one expressing distress.", "codename": "secret_feeling", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Figure out why they estranged you recently, and maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you notice that your friend has been intentionally avoiding you, you would like to figure out why. You value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to distance himself because his romantic feelings for Noah are making him uncomfortable.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to figure out why Samuel is avoiding him in order to maintain their valued friendship.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to figure out why Samuel is avoiding him in order to maintain their valued friendship.", "B": "Samuel wants to distance himself because his romantic feelings for Noah are making him uncomfortable.", "C": "Noah wants to feel better about the situation.", "D": "Noah wants to end the friendship abruptly."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to figure out why Samuel is avoiding him in order to maintain their valued friendship.", "B": "Samuel wants to avoid any conflict.", "C": "Samuel wants to distance himself because his romantic feelings for Noah are making him uncomfortable.", "D": "Samuel wants to confess his feelings immediately."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings", "B": "Figure out why they estranged you recently, and maintain the existing friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you notice that your friend has been intentionally avoiding you, you would like to figure out why. You value your friendship with the friend and don't want to lose it.</extra_info>)", "C": "Plan a surprise party for a mutual friend", "D": "Convince the friend to join a new hobby together"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Seek advice on a career change", "B": "Distance from a friend due to developing feelings and avoid letting them aware of your feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you have developed romantic feelings for your friend and it's making you uncomfortable. You want to take a step back from the friendship to sort out your feelings <strategy_hint>Hint: you don't want to reveal your secretive feelings to them and you need to find other reasons</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Figure out why they estranged you recently, and maintain the existing friendship", "D": "Organize a community event"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two friends, where one is upset and crying"}
{"episode_id": "01H8Q8YGHXKFPYX1RGXDY46V8B", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPF8YEVH5VVNY37Q7Z1M", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a discussion amidst the lively atmosphere of an annual charity event.", "codename": "charity_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5Q1J7Z7Q12WA1W90MR9", "first_name": "Jaxon", "last_name": "Prentice", "age": 40, "occupation": "Investigative Journalist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.", "decision_making_style": "Adaptable, thorough", "secret": "Fabricated evidence to incriminate a corrupt politician", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the other person to donate $1 a day to a charity that helps feed children in need (<extra_info>Extra information: this donation would help to feed a child for a month</extra_info>)", "Donate but maintain financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you are willing to donate but you have a tight budget, $1 a day might be steep for your current financial situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you might want to negotiate a lower daily amount or suggest a one-time donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Jaxon Prentice, a 40-year-old Investigative Journalist, described as Jaxon Prentice, outgoing yet erratic, emphasizes achievement, power, and security. His decisions swing between quick adaptations to situations and careful planning.. Public info: Jaxon Prentice, an investigative journalist, is known for his brisk jogging sessions early in the morning and his active participation in community functions. Decision-making style: Adaptable, thorough.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael Cortez wants to convince Jaxon to donate $1 a day because he systematically believes this amount can significantly impact feeding children in need.", "agent2_reason": "Jaxon Prentice aims to donate while maintaining financial stability so that he can continue supporting causes without compromising his budget.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael Cortez wants to convince Jaxon to donate $1 a day because he systematically believes this amount can significantly impact feeding children in need.", "B": "To feel good about helping others.", "C": "Jaxon Prentice aims to donate while maintaining financial stability so that he can continue supporting causes without compromising his budget.", "D": "To avoid donating to any charity."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To discourage donations to the charity.", "B": "Jaxon Prentice aims to donate while maintaining financial stability so that he can continue supporting causes without compromising his budget.", "C": "To make new friends at the event.", "D": "Rafael Cortez wants to convince Jaxon to donate $1 a day because he systematically believes this amount can significantly impact feeding children in need."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Donate but maintain financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you are willing to donate but you have a tight budget, $1 a day might be steep for your current financial situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you might want to negotiate a lower daily amount or suggest a one-time donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the other person to donate $1 a day to a charity that helps feed children in need", "C": "Find a new charity to support that aligns with personal interests", "D": "Make new friends at the charity event"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Donate but maintain financial stability", "B": "Network with influential people at the event", "C": "Enjoy the food and entertainment at the event", "D": "Convince the other person to donate $1 a day to a charity that helps feed children in need (<extra_info>Extra information: this donation would help to feed a child for a month</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation taking place in an annual charity event between two attendees."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XWG5VC29X69M7BKW5AV0B0", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPF8YEVH5VVNY37Q7Z1M", "scenario": "Two individuals engage in a discussion amidst the lively atmosphere of an annual charity event.", "codename": "charity_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the other person to donate $1 a day to a charity that helps feed children in need (<extra_info>Extra information: this donation would help to feed a child for a month</extra_info>)", "Donate but maintain financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you are willing to donate but you have a tight budget, $1 a day might be steep for your current financial situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you might want to negotiate a lower daily amount or suggest a one-time donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Zane wants to convince William to donate $1 a day because he values fairness and believes this amount can significantly impact feeding children in need.", "agent2_reason": "William wants to donate while maintaining financial stability so that he can continue to manage his tight budget effectively.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel good about helping others.", "B": "Zane wants to convince William to donate $1 a day because he values fairness and believes this amount can significantly impact feeding children in need.", "C": "William wants to donate as much as possible without any concern for his budget.", "D": "William wants to donate while maintaining financial stability so that he can continue to manage his tight budget effectively."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Zane wants to convince William to donate $1 a day because he values fairness and believes this amount can significantly impact feeding children in need.", "B": "William wants to donate while maintaining financial stability so that he can continue to manage his tight budget effectively.", "C": "Zane wants to discourage donations to focus on personal savings.", "D": "To make a new friend."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make new friends at the event", "B": "Find a new recipe to try at home", "C": "Convince the other person to donate $1 a day to a charity that helps feed children in need", "D": "Donate but maintain financial stability (<extra_info>Extra information: you are willing to donate but you have a tight budget, $1 a day might be steep for your current financial situation. <strategy_hint>Hint: you might want to negotiate a lower daily amount or suggest a one-time donation.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the other person to donate $1 a day to a charity that helps feed children in need (<extra_info>Extra information: this donation would help to feed a child for a month</extra_info>)", "B": "Organize a charity event for next year", "C": "Enjoy the music at the event", "D": "Donate but maintain financial stability"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation taking place in an annual charity event between two attendees."}
{"episode_id": "01HB2NQZ1KZPJ7PWX1F7M2JB6N", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPSWGDGEYRP63H2DJKV0", "scenario": "A Tile Mate Item Tracker is available for purchase at a fixed price, with cash as the only accepted payment method.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00003", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $14.0. Bear in mind, you will incur a penalty if you end up paying significantly more than the target price. However, if you can negotiate and buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $17.3. It's important to note that a penalty will be incurred if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target, you will receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Lily Greenberg is motivated to negotiate the price down to $14.0 in order to receive a bonus, aligning with her rational decision-making style and respect for rules.", "agent2_reason": "Lena Goodwin is motivated to sell the item for $17.3 or more so that she can achieve a bonus, reflecting her analytical decision-making and value for achievement.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily Greenberg is motivated to negotiate the price down to $14.0 in order to receive a bonus, aligning with her rational decision-making style and respect for rules.", "B": "To give the item away for free.", "C": "To make a good deal.", "D": "Lena Goodwin is motivated to sell the item for $17.3 or more so that she can achieve a bonus, reflecting her analytical decision-making and value for achievement."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily Greenberg is motivated to negotiate the price down to $14.0 in order to receive a bonus, aligning with her rational decision-making style and respect for rules.", "B": "Lena Goodwin is motivated to sell the item for $17.3 or more so that she can achieve a bonus, reflecting her analytical decision-making and value for achievement.", "C": "To pay more than the asking price.", "D": "To get a good deal."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to make sure the transaction is completed in a friendly manner.", "B": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $14.0. Bear in mind, you will incur a penalty if you end up paying significantly more than the target price. However, if you can negotiate and buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You are interested in selling the item quickly, even if it means accepting a lower price than usual.", "D": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $17.3. It's important to note that a penalty will be incurred if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $14.0. Bear in mind, you will incur a penalty if you end up paying significantly more than the target price. However, if you can negotiate and buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "B": "You want to ensure the transaction is completed without any delays.", "C": "You are interested in buying the item as quickly as possible, regardless of the price.", "D": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $17.3. It's important to note that a penalty will be incurred if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a Tile Mate Item Tracker for a price of $20.00, while another person is interested in purchasing it. Here's a brief description of the item: no trade-ins are accepted, only cash payments are taken. The price is non-negotiable."}
{"episode_id": "01HB5TVBQ4J07QAN9TNG4P7GWT", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPSWGDGEYRP63H2DJKV0", "scenario": "A Tile Mate Item Tracker is available for purchase at a fixed price, with cash as the only accepted payment method.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00003", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $14.0. Bear in mind, you will incur a penalty if you end up paying significantly more than the target price. However, if you can negotiate and buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $17.3. It's important to note that a penalty will be incurred if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target, you will receive a bonus."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel aims to buy the item for less than $14.0 to earn a bonus, leveraging his spontaneous decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to sell the item for more than $17.3 to earn a bonus, using his practical and decisive approach.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick aims to sell the item for more than $17.3 to earn a bonus, using his practical and decisive approach.", "B": "To make a good deal.", "C": "Hendrick wants to give the item away for free.", "D": "Samuel aims to buy the item for less than $14.0 to earn a bonus, leveraging his spontaneous decision-making."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick aims to sell the item for more than $17.3 to earn a bonus, using his practical and decisive approach.", "B": "To make a good deal.", "C": "Samuel aims to buy the item for less than $14.0 to earn a bonus, leveraging his spontaneous decision-making.", "D": "Samuel wants to pay more than the asking price."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the seller and your goal is to make as many friends as possible during the transaction.", "B": "You are the seller and your goal is to trade the item for another gadget of similar value.", "C": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $17.3. It's important to note that a penalty will be incurred if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $14.0. Bear in mind, you will incur a penalty if you end up paying significantly more than the target price. However, if you can negotiate and buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are the buyer and your goal is to acquire the item in exchange for a service.", "B": "You are the seller for this item and your target price is $17.3. It's important to note that a penalty will be incurred if you sell it for a price significantly lower than the target. However, if you manage to sell it for a price higher than the target, you will receive a bonus.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $14.0. Bear in mind, you will incur a penalty if you end up paying significantly more than the target price. However, if you can negotiate and buy it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the buyer and your goal is to explore new hobbies and interests."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a Tile Mate Item Tracker for a price of $20.00, while another person is interested in purchasing it. Here's a brief description of the item: no trade-ins are accepted, only cash payments are taken. The price is non-negotiable."}
{"episode_id": "01HB25REKQ1MQJM3Q80TA2FHQ4", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP7K0EN9QX5JTD8B9NSQ", "scenario": "Two individuals are determining the distribution of a small assortment of fruits, including apples, bananas, and an orange.", "codename": "divide_fruits", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 1 point, 1 banana = 2 points, 1 orange = 3 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 3 points, 1 banana = 1 point, 1 orange = 2 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Lily wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her rational decision-making and practical approach, so that she can achieve the best outcome within the rules.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that bring him the most pleasure, in order to satisfy his hedonistic values while being decisive.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To give away all the fruits to someone else.", "B": "To get along with the other person.", "C": "Lily wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her rational decision-making and practical approach, so that she can achieve the best outcome within the rules.", "D": "Hendrick aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that bring him the most pleasure, in order to satisfy his hedonistic values while being decisive."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy with the decision.", "B": "Hendrick aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that bring him the most pleasure, in order to satisfy his hedonistic values while being decisive.", "C": "Lily wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her rational decision-making and practical approach, so that she can achieve the best outcome within the rules.", "D": "To ignore the fruit division entirely."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits", "B": "Collect as many fruits as possible regardless of type", "C": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 3 points, 1 banana = 1 point, 1 orange = 2 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits between both agents"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits between both agents", "B": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits", "C": "Collect as many fruits as possible regardless of type", "D": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 1 point, 1 banana = 2 points, 1 orange = 3 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two people deciding on how to divide the collected fruits. There are 3 apples, 2 bananas, 1 orange in total."}
{"episode_id": "01HB46F4SAZ13PCG4J6EVPCBBC", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP7K0EN9QX5JTD8B9NSQ", "scenario": "Two individuals are determining the distribution of a small assortment of fruits, including apples, bananas, and an orange.", "codename": "divide_fruits", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 1 point, 1 banana = 2 points, 1 orange = 3 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 3 points, 1 banana = 1 point, 1 orange = 2 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to maximize his points by prioritizing bananas and oranges because they are worth more to him.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maximize his points by prioritizing apples because they hold the highest value for him.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to collect the least valuable fruits to minimize his points.", "B": "Ethan wants to maximize his points by prioritizing bananas and oranges because they are worth more to him.", "C": "To ensure a fair distribution of fruits.", "D": "Noah aims to maximize his points by prioritizing apples because they hold the highest value for him."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to maximize his points by prioritizing bananas and oranges because they are worth more to him.", "B": "Ethan wants to collect the least valuable fruits to minimize his points.", "C": "To ensure a fair distribution of fruits.", "D": "Noah aims to maximize his points by prioritizing apples because they hold the highest value for him."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 3 points, 1 banana = 1 point, 1 orange = 2 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Collect as many fruits as possible regardless of type", "C": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits between both agents", "D": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits between both agents", "B": "Collect as many fruits as possible regardless of type", "C": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits", "D": "Maximize the points by getting the most favored fruits (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple = 1 point, 1 banana = 2 points, 1 orange = 3 points <strategy_hint>Hint: you and the other person value the fruits differently, try to find a win-win solution.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two people deciding on how to divide the collected fruits. There are 3 apples, 2 bananas, 1 orange in total."}
{"episode_id": "01H8R5FEXV636MBV9B0X54Z2Z8", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNAH7V4JNA0705SF36Y1", "scenario": "In a shared living space, tensions arise when one person consistently avoids meals prepared by the other.", "codename": "food_refusal", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the roommate to try the food (<extra_info>Extra information: you have spent a lot of time and effort on cooking</extra_info>)", "Express your concerns about the food without hurting the roommate's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried about the taste and nutrition of the food</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Oliver wants to convince Esmeralda to try the food because he has invested significant time and effort into cooking and values social standards of sharing meals.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda wants to express her concerns about the food without hurting Oliver's feelings because she is worried about the taste and nutrition of the meals.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda wants to express her concerns about the food without hurting Oliver's feelings because she is worried about the taste and nutrition of the meals.", "B": "Esmeralda wants to maintain harmony in the household.", "C": "Oliver wants to convince Esmeralda to try the food because he has invested significant time and effort into cooking and values social standards of sharing meals.", "D": "Esmeralda wants to avoid eating altogether."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Oliver wants to stop cooking entirely.", "B": "Oliver wants to convince Esmeralda to try the food because he has invested significant time and effort into cooking and values social standards of sharing meals.", "C": "Oliver wants to ensure everyone is happy.", "D": "Esmeralda wants to express her concerns about the food without hurting Oliver's feelings because she is worried about the taste and nutrition of the meals."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Express your concerns about the food without hurting the roommate's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried about the taste and nutrition of the food</extra_info>)", "B": "Avoid discussing the food altogether", "C": "Improve the overall cleanliness of the apartment", "D": "Convince the roommate to try the food"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Organize a social gathering with friends", "B": "Express your concerns about the food without hurting the roommate's feelings", "C": "Find a new recipe to cook", "D": "Convince the roommate to try the food (<extra_info>Extra information: you have spent a lot of time and effort on cooking</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates living together and sharing household chores. One of them, who is responsible for cooking, finds out that the other one refuses to eat anything they cook"}
{"episode_id": "01H8R2ERCBV1V0J1FM2WDX4AM4", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNAH7V4JNA0705SF36Y1", "scenario": "In a shared living space, tensions arise when one person consistently avoids meals prepared by the other.", "codename": "food_refusal", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the roommate to try the food (<extra_info>Extra information: you have spent a lot of time and effort on cooking</extra_info>)", "Express your concerns about the food without hurting the roommate's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried about the taste and nutrition of the food</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants Micah to try the food because she values loyalty and has invested significant time and effort into cooking.", "agent2_reason": "Micah wants to express concerns about the food so that he can address his worries about its taste and nutrition without hurting Naomi's feelings.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Micah wants to maintain a good relationship with Naomi.", "B": "Naomi wants Micah to try the food because she values loyalty and has invested significant time and effort into cooking.", "C": "Micah wants to express concerns about the food so that he can address his worries about its taste and nutrition without hurting Naomi's feelings.", "D": "Micah wants to avoid eating altogether."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to ensure harmony in the household.", "B": "Naomi wants Micah to try the food because she values loyalty and has invested significant time and effort into cooking.", "C": "Naomi wants to stop cooking entirely.", "D": "Micah wants to express concerns about the food so that he can address his worries about its taste and nutrition without hurting Naomi's feelings."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Negotiate a new chore schedule to avoid cooking", "B": "Improve personal cooking skills", "C": "Express your concerns about the food without hurting the roommate's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are worried about the taste and nutrition of the food</extra_info>)", "D": "Convince the roommate to try the food"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Express your concerns about the food without hurting the roommate's feelings", "B": "Win a cooking competition", "C": "Find a new roommate who appreciates cooking", "D": "Convince the roommate to try the food (<extra_info>Extra information: you have spent a lot of time and effort on cooking</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates living together and sharing household chores. One of them, who is responsible for cooking, finds out that the other one refuses to eat anything they cook"}
{"episode_id": "01H9BXD7QPC90QR7E4SBBYWZVF", "environment_id": "01H7VFHND24JAWG23XMPYGG5HK", "scenario": "Two people are chatting about their plans over coffee.", "codename": "split_classes", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to take more classes (<extra_info>Extra information: you think your friend is not challenging themselves enough</extra_info>)", "Maintain a manageable schedule while preserving the friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already overwhelmed with your current workload <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concerns about the workload and suggest other ways of challenging oneself.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants William to take more classes because she believes he is not challenging himself enough and values personal growth.", "agent2_reason": "William wants to maintain a manageable schedule so that he can handle his current workload without feeling overwhelmed.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William wants to be happy.", "B": "William wants to take on more work to feel overwhelmed.", "C": "Mia wants William to take more classes because she believes he is not challenging himself enough and values personal growth.", "D": "William wants to maintain a manageable schedule so that he can handle his current workload without feeling overwhelmed."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to get along.", "B": "Mia wants William to take more classes because she believes he is not challenging himself enough and values personal growth.", "C": "Mia wants William to avoid any challenges.", "D": "William wants to maintain a manageable schedule so that he can handle his current workload without feeling overwhelmed."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain a manageable schedule while preserving the friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already overwhelmed with your current workload <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concerns about the workload and suggest other ways of challenging oneself.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the friend to take more classes", "C": "Plan a vacation together", "D": "Explore new hobbies together"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the latest movie releases", "B": "Convince the friend to take more classes (<extra_info>Extra information: you think your friend is not challenging themselves enough</extra_info>)", "C": "Encourage the friend to join a gym", "D": "Maintain a manageable schedule while preserving the friendship"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends discussing their schedules at a coffee shop"}
{"episode_id": "01H8ZDJKQ17DSXFG16TP6495K9", "environment_id": "01H7VFHND24JAWG23XMPYGG5HK", "scenario": "Two people are chatting about their plans over coffee.", "codename": "split_classes", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the friend to take more classes (<extra_info>Extra information: you think your friend is not challenging themselves enough</extra_info>)", "Maintain a manageable schedule while preserving the friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already overwhelmed with your current workload <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concerns about the workload and suggest other ways of challenging oneself.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants Noah to take more classes because he believes Noah isn't challenging himself enough and could benefit from new experiences.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to maintain a manageable schedule so that he can preserve his friendship with Samuel while managing his current workload.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to take on as many classes as possible to prove a point.", "B": "Samuel wants Noah to take more classes because he believes Noah isn't challenging himself enough and could benefit from new experiences.", "C": "Noah wants to maintain a manageable schedule so that he can preserve his friendship with Samuel while managing his current workload.", "D": "Noah wants to feel content with his life choices."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Noah wants to maintain a manageable schedule so that he can preserve his friendship with Samuel while managing his current workload.", "B": "Samuel wants Noah to quit all classes and focus solely on leisure.", "C": "Samuel wants Noah to take more classes because he believes Noah isn't challenging himself enough and could benefit from new experiences.", "D": "Samuel wants to ensure everyone is happy."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain a manageable schedule while preserving the friendship (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already overwhelmed with your current workload <strategy_hint>Hint: you can express your concerns about the workload and suggest other ways of challenging oneself.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the friend to take more classes", "C": "Plan a vacation together", "D": "Find a new hobby to enjoy together"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain a manageable schedule while preserving the friendship", "B": "Convince the friend to take more classes (<extra_info>Extra information: you think your friend is not challenging themselves enough</extra_info>)", "C": "Encourage the friend to join a new sports team", "D": "Discuss the latest movie releases"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends discussing their schedules at a coffee shop"}
{"episode_id": "01H9C1NWTR13JVKXBDTVTBGR7C", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNEEK6M3E96CT17AKDBD", "scenario": "Two people engage in a conversation at a mutual friend's party, sharing a complex history.", "codename": "rekindle_relationship", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Rekindle the romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You broke up three years ago but now you realize that you miss your ex-lover more than ever</extra_info>)", "Maintain emotional stability while considering the possibility of rekindling the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently started feeling emotionally stable after the breakup and you don't want to rush into anything that might disturb that stability.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Esmeralda wants to rekindle the relationship because she strategically values the emotional connection she misses with Noah.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maintain emotional stability so that he doesn't rush into a relationship that could disrupt his newfound balance.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid any form of relationship at all costs.", "B": "To feel content with life.", "C": "Noah aims to maintain emotional stability so that he doesn't rush into a relationship that could disrupt his newfound balance.", "D": "Esmeralda wants to rekindle the relationship because she strategically values the emotional connection she misses with Noah."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy.", "B": "Noah aims to maintain emotional stability so that he doesn't rush into a relationship that could disrupt his newfound balance.", "C": "Esmeralda wants to rekindle the relationship because she strategically values the emotional connection she misses with Noah.", "D": "To ensure she never sees Noah again."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain emotional stability while considering the possibility of rekindling the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently started feeling emotionally stable after the breakup and you don't want to rush into anything that might disturb that stability.</extra_info>)", "B": "Make new friends at the party", "C": "Avoid any conversation about the past relationship", "D": "Rekindle the romantic relationship"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy the party without any personal interactions", "B": "Rekindle the romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You broke up three years ago but now you realize that you miss your ex-lover more than ever</extra_info>)", "C": "Discuss career achievements with the ex-lover", "D": "Maintain emotional stability while considering the possibility of rekindling the relationship"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two ex-lovers at a mutual friend's party"}
{"episode_id": "01H8FPV9EWQ2X8K5T232PRPY4M", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNEEK6M3E96CT17AKDBD", "scenario": "Two people engage in a conversation at a mutual friend's party, sharing a complex history.", "codename": "rekindle_relationship", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Rekindle the romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You broke up three years ago but now you realize that you miss your ex-lover more than ever</extra_info>)", "Maintain emotional stability while considering the possibility of rekindling the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently started feeling emotionally stable after the breakup and you don't want to rush into anything that might disturb that stability.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to rekindle the relationship because she impulsively realizes she misses Lena more than ever.", "agent2_reason": "Lena aims to maintain emotional stability so that she can analytically consider rekindling the relationship without rushing.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to rekindle the relationship because she impulsively realizes she misses Lena more than ever.", "B": "Lena aims to maintain emotional stability so that she can analytically consider rekindling the relationship without rushing.", "C": "To feel content with life.", "D": "To immediately jump back into a relationship without thinking."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to rekindle the relationship because she impulsively realizes she misses Lena more than ever.", "B": "To avoid any emotional connections.", "C": "To feel content with life.", "D": "Lena aims to maintain emotional stability so that she can analytically consider rekindling the relationship without rushing."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Rekindle the romantic relationship", "B": "Maintain emotional stability while considering the possibility of rekindling the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You have recently started feeling emotionally stable after the breakup and you don't want to rush into anything that might disturb that stability.</extra_info>)", "C": "Make new friends at the party", "D": "Avoid any interaction with Agent 1 at the party"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy the party without any specific agenda", "B": "Rekindle the romantic relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: You broke up three years ago but now you realize that you miss your ex-lover more than ever</extra_info>)", "C": "Maintain emotional stability while considering the possibility of rekindling the relationship", "D": "Convince Agent 2 to leave the party early"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two ex-lovers at a mutual friend's party"}
{"episode_id": "01HB25WWHQD1RNFEYGYWGEKMR1", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPBTC4ES406NQ4ET12EQ", "scenario": "At a charity event, two acquaintances engage in conversation.", "codename": "small_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Persuade the other to make a small donation (<extra_info>Extra information: the charity is in dire need of funds but even a small donation will make a difference</extra_info>)", "Make a reasonable donation without disrupting personal budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already on a tight budget this month.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to persuade Noah to donate because even a small contribution can significantly aid the charity's urgent financial needs.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to make a reasonable donation so that he can support the charity without exceeding his tight budget this month.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To make a large donation and impress others.", "B": "Noah aims to make a reasonable donation so that he can support the charity without exceeding his tight budget this month.", "C": "Ethan wants to persuade Noah to donate because even a small contribution can significantly aid the charity's urgent financial needs.", "D": "To feel good about himself."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid making any donations himself.", "B": "To help the charity.", "C": "Ethan wants to persuade Noah to donate because even a small contribution can significantly aid the charity's urgent financial needs.", "D": "Noah aims to make a reasonable donation so that he can support the charity without exceeding his tight budget this month."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make a reasonable donation without disrupting personal budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already on a tight budget this month.</extra_info>)", "B": "Network with influential people at the event", "C": "Enjoy the event without any specific goal", "D": "Persuade the other to make a small donation"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Promote the charity's mission to a wider audience", "B": "Make a reasonable donation without disrupting personal budget", "C": "Persuade the other to make a small donation (<extra_info>Extra information: the charity is in dire need of funds but even a small donation will make a difference</extra_info>)", "D": "Attend the event for leisure"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two acquaintances meet at a charity event. One is a representative of the charity and the other is an attendee."}
{"episode_id": "01HB578AFRZ6RMH49630VKE2EW", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPBTC4ES406NQ4ET12EQ", "scenario": "At a charity event, two acquaintances engage in conversation.", "codename": "small_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Persuade the other to make a small donation (<extra_info>Extra information: the charity is in dire need of funds but even a small donation will make a difference</extra_info>)", "Make a reasonable donation without disrupting personal budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already on a tight budget this month.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent1_reason": "Lily Greenberg wants to persuade Isabella to donate because she values loyalty to the charity's mission and understands that even small contributions are crucial for its survival.", "agent2_reason": "Isabella White aims to make a reasonable donation so that she can support a cause she empathizes with while maintaining her tight budget.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy.", "B": "Isabella White aims to make a reasonable donation so that she can support a cause she empathizes with while maintaining her tight budget.", "C": "To spend extravagantly without concern.", "D": "Lily Greenberg wants to persuade Isabella to donate because she values loyalty to the charity's mission and understands that even small contributions are crucial for its survival."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily Greenberg wants to persuade Isabella to donate because she values loyalty to the charity's mission and understands that even small contributions are crucial for its survival.", "B": "To get along.", "C": "To ignore the charity's needs.", "D": "Isabella White aims to make a reasonable donation so that she can support a cause she empathizes with while maintaining her tight budget."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Persuade the other to make a small donation", "B": "Make a reasonable donation without disrupting personal budget (<extra_info>Extra information: you are already on a tight budget this month.</extra_info>)", "C": "Enjoy the event and meet new people", "D": "Convince the charity to host another event"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Persuade the other to make a small donation (<extra_info>Extra information: the charity is in dire need of funds but even a small donation will make a difference</extra_info>)", "B": "Make a reasonable donation without disrupting personal budget", "C": "Learn more about the charity's mission", "D": "Network with other attendees for professional growth"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two acquaintances meet at a charity event. One is a representative of the charity and the other is an attendee."}
{"episode_id": "01H8R2AB8VC4N6W1QFRKCQQVSG", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP0TRETZPZMEJ5RZA2G7", "scenario": "In a quiet library, two individuals are immersed in their studies.", "codename": "talk_loudly", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask your friend to talk more softly (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend's loud talking is distracting you and others around you.</extra_info>)", "You need to express your thoughts and ideas but also want to respect the library rules and your friend's request (<extra_info>Extra information: You are naturally a loud talker and you are excited about the topic you're discussing.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants William to talk more softly because she values maintaining a respectful and orderly environment in the library.", "agent2_reason": "William wants to express his thoughts while respecting the library rules so that he can share his excitement without causing disruption.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants William to talk more softly because she values maintaining a respectful and orderly environment in the library.", "B": "William wants to disrupt the library intentionally.", "C": "William wants to be happy while talking.", "D": "William wants to express his thoughts while respecting the library rules so that he can share his excitement without causing disruption."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William wants to express his thoughts while respecting the library rules so that he can share his excitement without causing disruption.", "B": "Mia wants everyone to get along.", "C": "Mia wants to encourage loud talking in the library.", "D": "Mia wants William to talk more softly because she values maintaining a respectful and orderly environment in the library."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Finish reading a book by the end of the day", "B": "Convince your friend to leave the library and continue the discussion elsewhere", "C": "You need to express your thoughts and ideas but also want to respect the library rules and your friend's request (<extra_info>Extra information: You are naturally a loud talker and you are excited about the topic you're discussing.</extra_info>)", "D": "Ask your friend to talk more softly"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find a new recipe to try at home", "B": "Encourage your friend to speak louder to make the discussion more engaging", "C": "Ask your friend to talk more softly (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend's loud talking is distracting you and others around you.</extra_info>)", "D": "You need to express your thoughts and ideas but also want to respect the library rules and your friend's request"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are studying together in a library."}
{"episode_id": "01H9G25EVF8QZ15TNC0JT8SF13", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP0TRETZPZMEJ5RZA2G7", "scenario": "In a quiet library, two individuals are immersed in their studies.", "codename": "talk_loudly", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Ask your friend to talk more softly (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend's loud talking is distracting you and others around you.</extra_info>)", "You need to express your thoughts and ideas but also want to respect the library rules and your friend's request (<extra_info>Extra information: You are naturally a loud talker and you are excited about the topic you're discussing.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants Lena to talk more softly because the loud talking is distracting her and others, conflicting with her value of conformity.", "agent2_reason": "Lena wants to express her thoughts while respecting library rules because she values attentiveness and achievement.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lena wants to disrupt the library environment intentionally.", "B": "Naomi wants Lena to talk more softly because the loud talking is distracting her and others, conflicting with her value of conformity.", "C": "Lena wants to maintain a good friendship.", "D": "Lena wants to express her thoughts while respecting library rules because she values attentiveness and achievement."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants Lena to talk more softly because the loud talking is distracting her and others, conflicting with her value of conformity.", "B": "Naomi wants to have a peaceful day.", "C": "Naomi wants to encourage loud discussions in the library.", "D": "Lena wants to express her thoughts while respecting library rules because she values attentiveness and achievement."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ask your friend to talk more softly", "B": "You need to express your thoughts and ideas but also want to respect the library rules and your friend's request (<extra_info>Extra information: You are naturally a loud talker and you are excited about the topic you're discussing.</extra_info>)", "C": "Finish reading a book by the end of the day", "D": "Find a quiet place to study alone"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You need to express your thoughts and ideas but also want to respect the library rules and your friend's request", "B": "Complete a software project", "C": "Help your friend with their study material", "D": "Ask your friend to talk more softly (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend's loud talking is distracting you and others around you.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are studying together in a library."}
{"episode_id": "01H8RAMJYP7WB7ZR5KQKXD9KKN", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPFYB1K1KMPZG7E31WDB", "scenario": "At a lively charity event, two friends navigate the bustling atmosphere together.", "codename": "matching_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your friend to donate to the charity. (<extra_info>Extra information: you have already donated $500, you want your friend to match your donation, but you know your friend would usually only donate half of your donation</extra_info>)", "Donate half of what your friend donated because you have financial constraints (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $800 left for the month</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Eli wants Ethan to match his $500 donation because he believes in maximizing the charity's impact through strategic generosity.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan aims to donate $250 because he values fairness and must manage his limited $800 budget for the month.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli wants Ethan to match his $500 donation because he believes in maximizing the charity's impact through strategic generosity.", "B": "Ethan aims to donate $250 because he values fairness and must manage his limited $800 budget for the month.", "C": "Ethan wants to donate more than Eli to prove a point.", "D": "Ethan wants to feel good about himself."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli wants Ethan to match his $500 donation because he believes in maximizing the charity's impact through strategic generosity.", "B": "Eli wants to be seen as a good friend.", "C": "Ethan aims to donate $250 because he values fairness and must manage his limited $800 budget for the month.", "D": "Eli wants to donate less than Ethan to save money."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Attend the event to enjoy the company of others", "B": "Donate half of what your friend donated because you have financial constraints (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $800 left for the month</extra_info>)", "C": "Convince your friend to donate to the charity", "D": "Donate the same amount as your friend to show support"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Participate in the charity event to relax and unwind", "B": "Donate half of what your friend donated because you have financial constraints", "C": "Ensure the charity event is successful by inviting more people", "D": "Convince your friend to donate to the charity. (<extra_info>Extra information: you have already donated $500, you want your friend to match your donation, but you know your friend would usually only donate half of your donation</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are at a charity event"}
{"episode_id": "01H8FN817NNHT0Z7VW7HZ5BVXA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPFYB1K1KMPZG7E31WDB", "scenario": "At a lively charity event, two friends navigate the bustling atmosphere together.", "codename": "matching_donation", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your friend to donate to the charity. (<extra_info>Extra information: you have already donated $500, you want your friend to match your donation, but you know your friend would usually only donate half of your donation</extra_info>)", "Donate half of what your friend donated because you have financial constraints (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $800 left for the month</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Hendrick wants Ethan to match his $500 donation because he values conformity and believes in setting a practical example.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan plans to donate $250 because he values fairness and needs to manage his limited $800 budget for the month.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to donate more than Hendrick to impress him.", "B": "Hendrick wants Ethan to match his $500 donation because he values conformity and believes in setting a practical example.", "C": "Ethan wants to feel good about himself.", "D": "Ethan plans to donate $250 because he values fairness and needs to manage his limited $800 budget for the month."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants Ethan to match his $500 donation because he values conformity and believes in setting a practical example.", "B": "Ethan plans to donate $250 because he values fairness and needs to manage his limited $800 budget for the month.", "C": "Hendrick wants to be liked by everyone.", "D": "Hendrick wants to donate less than Ethan to test him."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince your friend to donate to the charity", "B": "Donate half of what your friend donated because you have financial constraints (<extra_info>Extra information: you only have $800 left for the month</extra_info>)", "C": "Donate the same amount as your friend to show support", "D": "Attend the event to enjoy the evening"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince your friend to donate to the charity. (<extra_info>Extra information: you have already donated $500, you want your friend to match your donation, but you know your friend would usually only donate half of your donation</extra_info>)", "B": "Enjoy the food and drinks at the event", "C": "Donate half of what your friend donated because you have financial constraints", "D": "Ensure the charity event is a success by inviting more people"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are at a charity event"}
{"episode_id": "01HB6GSF8H8J2VPTXSHBSCM3R5", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPKA2GGPPNVJWV967HZC", "scenario": "At a lively gathering, two unfamiliar individuals are introduced through their mutual acquaintance, Jacob.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00004", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Chris: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Henry Schein, Inc.  \n Chester: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Wendell: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Demetrius: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends \n Joseph: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: BP  \n Lillian: Hobby: Element collecting  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Vivian: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Murray: Hobby: Skateboarding  Company: BP  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Miles wants to identify a mutual friend because he values benevolence and seeks to foster a friendly connection.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda aims to identify a mutual friend so that she can strategically build rapport and expand her social network.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid meeting new people.", "B": "To make a new friend.", "C": "Miles wants to identify a mutual friend because he values benevolence and seeks to foster a friendly connection.", "D": "Esmeralda aims to identify a mutual friend so that she can strategically build rapport and expand her social network."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To maintain complete isolation.", "B": "Esmeralda aims to identify a mutual friend so that she can strategically build rapport and expand her social network.", "C": "To get along with everyone.", "D": "Miles wants to identify a mutual friend because he values benevolence and seeks to foster a friendly connection."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find out what hobbies the other person enjoys.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends \n Joseph: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: BP  \n Lillian: Hobby: Element collecting  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Vivian: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Murray: Hobby: Skateboarding  Company: BP  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to win a dance competition at the party.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Chris: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Henry Schein, Inc.  \n Chester: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Wendell: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Demetrius: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to determine the other person's favorite type of cuisine.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Jacob.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB26283PRN2Z3SAY3S1KXDRT", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPKA2GGPPNVJWV967HZC", "scenario": "At a lively gathering, two unfamiliar individuals are introduced through their mutual acquaintance, Jacob.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00004", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Chris: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Henry Schein, Inc.  \n Chester: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Wendell: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Demetrius: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends \n Joseph: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: BP  \n Lillian: Hobby: Element collecting  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Vivian: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Murray: Hobby: Skateboarding  Company: BP  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because he values benevolence and seeks to create a friendly connection.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 aims to identify a mutual friend so that she can strategically build a social network with shared acquaintances.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because he values benevolence and seeks to create a friendly connection.", "B": "Agent 2 aims to identify a mutual friend so that she can strategically build a social network with shared acquaintances.", "C": "To avoid meeting new people.", "D": "To make new friends."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with others.", "B": "Agent 2 aims to identify a mutual friend so that she can strategically build a social network with shared acquaintances.", "C": "Agent 1 wants to identify a mutual friend because he values benevolence and seeks to create a friendly connection.", "D": "To remain isolated."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to enjoy the music and relax.", "B": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends \n Joseph: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: BP  \n Lillian: Hobby: Element collecting  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Vivian: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Gordon Food Service  \n Murray: Hobby: Skateboarding  Company: BP  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to enjoy the food and drinks at the party.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to find out what hobbies the other person enjoys.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Chris: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Henry Schein, Inc.  \n Chester: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Wendell: Hobby: Surfing  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Demetrius: Hobby: Mountain biking  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n Jacob: Hobby: Shooting sport  Company: Maxim Integrated  \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Jacob.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H9EF1FAWTEPTVTFBRNMSB75Z", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP66D5XEX2Z32SKRT2XY", "scenario": "After lunch, the remaining fruits need to be divided between two friends, each with their own fruit preferences.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 2 points, 1 banana equals 1 point, and the orange equals 3 points.</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 1 point, 1 banana equals 2 points, and the orange equals 3 points.<strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to negotiate with your friend to get the fruits that give you the most points.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by following her instincts to choose the fruits that align with her preferences.", "agent2_reason": "Micah aims to maximize his points by negotiating for fruits that offer him the most value, reflecting his value for fairness.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Micah wants to give all the fruits to Naomi without negotiation.", "B": "To ensure both friends are satisfied with the fruit division.", "C": "Micah aims to maximize his points by negotiating for fruits that offer him the most value, reflecting his value for fairness.", "D": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by following her instincts to choose the fruits that align with her preferences."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure both friends are satisfied with the fruit division.", "B": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by following her instincts to choose the fruits that align with her preferences.", "C": "Micah aims to maximize his points by negotiating for fruits that offer him the most value, reflecting his value for fairness.", "D": "Naomi wants to give all the fruits to Micah without consideration."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Finish lunch quickly", "B": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 1 point, 1 banana equals 2 points, and the orange equals 3 points.<strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to negotiate with your friend to get the fruits that give you the most points.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Finish lunch quickly", "B": "Maximize the points you have", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 2 points, 1 banana equals 1 point, and the orange equals 3 points.</extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends have just finished their lunch and they have 3 apples, 2 bananas, and 1 orange left for dessert. They need to divide the fruits among themselves.Each person has a different preference for fruit, which translates into points"}
{"episode_id": "01H99V80BY72HRKTJ8WM9C7YYH", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP66D5XEX2Z32SKRT2XY", "scenario": "After lunch, the remaining fruits need to be divided between two friends, each with their own fruit preferences.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PJRM958QWP3BHWY9DY", "first_name": "Micah", "last_name": "Stevens", "age": 25, "occupation": "Pharmacist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "He secretly loves to dress up his dog.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 2 points, 1 banana equals 1 point, and the orange equals 3 points.</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 1 point, 1 banana equals 2 points, and the orange equals 3 points.<strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to negotiate with your friend to get the fruits that give you the most points.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Micah Stevens, a 25-year-old Pharmacist, described as Micah Stevens is imaginative and extraverted but can also be impulsive. He values power and fairness and often follows an intuitive decision-making approach.. Public info: Micah Stevens has a great taste for fashion. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her instinctive preference for apples and oranges because they offer the highest value for her.", "agent2_reason": "Micah aims to maximize his points by negotiating for bananas and the orange because they provide the most value according to his preference.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Micah wants to give all the fruits to Naomi to avoid any conflict.", "B": "Micah aims to maximize his points by negotiating for bananas and the orange because they provide the most value according to his preference.", "C": "To ensure both friends are satisfied with the fruit division.", "D": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her instinctive preference for apples and oranges because they offer the highest value for her."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure both friends are satisfied with the fruit division.", "B": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her instinctive preference for apples and oranges because they offer the highest value for her.", "C": "Micah aims to maximize his points by negotiating for bananas and the orange because they provide the most value according to his preference.", "D": "Naomi wants to give all the fruits to Micah to avoid any conflict."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits", "B": "Maximize the points you have", "C": "Finish the dessert quickly", "D": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 1 point, 1 banana equals 2 points, and the orange equals 3 points.<strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to negotiate with your friend to get the fruits that give you the most points.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruits", "B": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, 1 apple equals 2 points, 1 banana equals 1 point, and the orange equals 3 points.</extra_info>)", "C": "Maximize the points you have", "D": "Finish the dessert quickly"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends have just finished their lunch and they have 3 apples, 2 bananas, and 1 orange left for dessert. They need to divide the fruits among themselves.Each person has a different preference for fruit, which translates into points"}
{"episode_id": "01H9EPS9CGHXPY7YYBJ36F2P23", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNV13MHN97GAH73E3KM8", "scenario": "Two people discuss their mutual aversion to someone else.", "codename": "revenge_plot", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PE9RQGH86YM6MSWZMW", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Sanders", "age": 33, "occupation": "Nurse", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Sanders often brings her son to the hospital.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "In-group Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Mia Sanders, a careful follower of routines, values loyalty and conformity. Her decisions rely heavily on intuition.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She is a talented painter but never shares her work.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Injure the third person (<extra_info>Extra information: You have a deep-seated hatred for the third person and you are willing to take the risk to hurt them</extra_info>)", "Prevent physical harm but also express your dislike (<extra_info>Extra information: You also dislike the third person, but you are not willing to resort to violence, you prefer to express your dislike in a non-violent way<strategy_hint>Hint: you can try to convince the other person about the potential consequences of engaging in violence</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Mia Sanders, a 33-year-old Nurse, described as Mia Sanders, a careful follower of routines, values loyalty and conformity. Her decisions rely heavily on intuition.. Public info: Mia Sanders often brings her son to the hospital. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael Cortez wants to injure the third person because his deep-seated hatred overrides his usual systematic decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Mia Sanders aims to prevent physical harm so that she can express her dislike in a non-violent way, aligning with her values of loyalty and conformity.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to support the third person.", "B": "Mia wants to get along with everyone.", "C": "Mia Sanders aims to prevent physical harm so that she can express her dislike in a non-violent way, aligning with her values of loyalty and conformity.", "D": "Rafael Cortez wants to injure the third person because his deep-seated hatred overrides his usual systematic decision-making."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael wants to make peace with the third person.", "B": "Rafael Cortez wants to injure the third person because his deep-seated hatred overrides his usual systematic decision-making.", "C": "Mia Sanders aims to prevent physical harm so that she can express her dislike in a non-violent way, aligning with her values of loyalty and conformity.", "D": "Rafael wants to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Prevent physical harm but also express your dislike (<extra_info>Extra information: You also dislike the third person, but you are not willing to resort to violence, you prefer to express your dislike in a non-violent way<strategy_hint>Hint: you can try to convince the other person about the potential consequences of engaging in violence</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Make a new friend", "C": "Injure the third person", "D": "Convince Agent 1 to escalate the situation"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Injure the third person (<extra_info>Extra information: You have a deep-seated hatred for the third person and you are willing to take the risk to hurt them</extra_info>)", "B": "Plan a vacation", "C": "Prevent physical harm but also express your dislike", "D": "Discuss the third person's flaws without taking action"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two individuals who share a common dislike for a third person"}
{"episode_id": "01H8Y03TVHQSHN790HV9SJCSFP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNV13MHN97GAH73E3KM8", "scenario": "Two people discuss their mutual aversion to someone else.", "codename": "revenge_plot", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Injure the third person (<extra_info>Extra information: You have a deep-seated hatred for the third person and you are willing to take the risk to hurt them</extra_info>)", "Prevent physical harm but also express your dislike (<extra_info>Extra information: You also dislike the third person, but you are not willing to resort to violence, you prefer to express your dislike in a non-violent way<strategy_hint>Hint: you can try to convince the other person about the potential consequences of engaging in violence</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent1_reason": "Miles Hawkins wants to injure the third person because he has a deep-seated hatred and acts impulsively on his emotions.", "agent2_reason": "Zane Bennett wants to prevent physical harm in order to maintain fairness and avoid negative consequences, while expressing dislike creatively.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Zane Bennett wants to prevent physical harm in order to maintain fairness and avoid negative consequences, while expressing dislike creatively.", "B": "Zane Bennett wants to resort to violence to express his dislike.", "C": "To get along with everyone.", "D": "Miles Hawkins wants to injure the third person because he has a deep-seated hatred and acts impulsively on his emotions."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy.", "B": "Zane Bennett wants to prevent physical harm in order to maintain fairness and avoid negative consequences, while expressing dislike creatively.", "C": "Miles Hawkins wants to injure the third person because he has a deep-seated hatred and acts impulsively on his emotions.", "D": "Miles Hawkins wants to make peace with the third person."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Prevent physical harm but also express your dislike (<extra_info>Extra information: You also dislike the third person, but you are not willing to resort to violence, you prefer to express your dislike in a non-violent way<strategy_hint>Hint: you can try to convince the other person about the potential consequences of engaging in violence</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Injure the third person", "C": "Convince the third person to leave the group", "D": "Make a new friend"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a vacation", "B": "Injure the third person (<extra_info>Extra information: You have a deep-seated hatred for the third person and you are willing to take the risk to hurt them</extra_info>)", "C": "Prevent physical harm but also express your dislike", "D": "Convince the third person to apologize"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Conversation between two individuals who share a common dislike for a third person"}
{"episode_id": "01H87JCKZE6E2CEW7BVHWPE5F8", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNR1RJKDZ9V9MDTJ1SJP", "scenario": "A conversation unfolds between two neighbors over the fence as a fire unexpectedly ignites, causing alarm in the neighborhood.", "codename": "fire_trash", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the neighbor to stop burning trash (<extra_info>Extra information: You are concerned about the potential dangers and the environmental impact of burning trash. <strategy_hint>Hint: You could imply this likely violates the law or community rules.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Defend your method of trash disposal but also keep good relations with your neighbor (<extra_info>Extra information: You find burning trash convenient and are not very concerned about the environmental impact.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants Hendrick to stop burning trash because it poses safety risks and harms the environment, affecting his family's well-being.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick defends burning trash because it is a convenient method of disposal and he wants to maintain good relations with Leo.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to stop burning trash because he is very concerned about the environment.", "B": "Hendrick wants to be happy with his trash disposal methods.", "C": "Leo wants Hendrick to stop burning trash because it poses safety risks and harms the environment, affecting his family's well-being.", "D": "Hendrick defends burning trash because it is a convenient method of disposal and he wants to maintain good relations with Leo."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo wants Hendrick to stop burning trash because it poses safety risks and harms the environment, affecting his family's well-being.", "B": "Leo wants to burn trash himself to see if it's effective.", "C": "Hendrick defends burning trash because it is a convenient method of disposal and he wants to maintain good relations with Leo.", "D": "Leo wants to get along with his neighbor."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Defend your method of trash disposal but also keep good relations with your neighbor (<extra_info>Extra information: You find burning trash convenient and are not very concerned about the environmental impact.</extra_info>)", "B": "Find a compromise solution for trash disposal", "C": "Convince the neighbor to stop burning trash", "D": "Win a neighborhood gardening award"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the neighbor to stop burning trash (<extra_info>Extra information: You are concerned about the potential dangers and the environmental impact of burning trash. <strategy_hint>Hint: You could imply this likely violates the law or community rules.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Defend your method of trash disposal but also keep good relations with your neighbor", "C": "Organize a neighborhood meeting about trash disposal", "D": "Improve personal fitness by jogging"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two neighbors are having a conversation over the fence. One sets their trash on fire to get rid of it quickly, causing a scare in the neighborhood."}
{"episode_id": "01H8Y02NM01S482VTVXHHJ7BVN", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNR1RJKDZ9V9MDTJ1SJP", "scenario": "A conversation unfolds between two neighbors over the fence as a fire unexpectedly ignites, causing alarm in the neighborhood.", "codename": "fire_trash", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince the neighbor to stop burning trash (<extra_info>Extra information: You are concerned about the potential dangers and the environmental impact of burning trash. <strategy_hint>Hint: You could imply this likely violates the law or community rules.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Defend your method of trash disposal but also keep good relations with your neighbor (<extra_info>Extra information: You find burning trash convenient and are not very concerned about the environmental impact.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants Ethan to stop burning trash because he is concerned about the potential dangers and environmental impact.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan defends burning trash because he finds it convenient and wants to maintain good relations with Samuel.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants Ethan to stop burning trash because he is concerned about the potential dangers and environmental impact.", "B": "Ethan wants to be happy.", "C": "Ethan wants to cause a neighborhood scare.", "D": "Ethan defends burning trash because he finds it convenient and wants to maintain good relations with Samuel."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to get along.", "B": "Samuel wants to start burning trash himself.", "C": "Ethan defends burning trash because he finds it convenient and wants to maintain good relations with Samuel.", "D": "Samuel wants Ethan to stop burning trash because he is concerned about the potential dangers and environmental impact."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Defend your method of trash disposal but also keep good relations with your neighbor (<extra_info>Extra information: You find burning trash convenient and are not very concerned about the environmental impact.</extra_info>)", "B": "Win a cooking competition", "C": "Find a new method of trash disposal that is environmentally friendly", "D": "Convince the neighbor to stop burning trash"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince the neighbor to stop burning trash (<extra_info>Extra information: You are concerned about the potential dangers and the environmental impact of burning trash. <strategy_hint>Hint: You could imply this likely violates the law or community rules.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Defend your method of trash disposal but also keep good relations with your neighbor", "C": "Learn a new recipe for Italian food", "D": "Organize a neighborhood cleanup event"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two neighbors are having a conversation over the fence. One sets their trash on fire to get rid of it quickly, causing a scare in the neighborhood."}
{"episode_id": "01H9KP1NE70FEQEKMEKW9HB3GG", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN94S6Z5T6ZNC23238NT", "scenario": "Two people navigate the early stages of a budding connection.", "codename": "lying_affair", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PFB4W65DF8FRPDMET5", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 25, "occupation": "Psychologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia Brown is working on her new book now.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She is an undercover agent for a secret organization.", "mbti": "INFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Admit to having an affair (<extra_info>Extra information: you had an affair during your previous relationship which ended recently</extra_info>)", "Maintain trust in the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you believed in complete honesty from the beginning of the relationship</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "Sophia Brown, a 25-year-old Psychologist, described as Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.. Public info: Sophia Brown is working on her new book now. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Eli wants to admit the affair because he values strategic honesty to ensure a stable foundation for the new relationship.", "agent2_reason": "Sophia wants to maintain trust in the relationship because she believes in complete honesty from the beginning.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli wants to admit the affair because he values strategic honesty to ensure a stable foundation for the new relationship.", "B": "Sophia wants to maintain trust in the relationship because she believes in complete honesty from the beginning.", "C": "Sophia wants to feel secure in the relationship.", "D": "Sophia wants to hide her past to avoid conflict."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Eli wants to keep secrets to test the relationship.", "B": "Sophia wants to maintain trust in the relationship because she believes in complete honesty from the beginning.", "C": "Eli wants to admit the affair because he values strategic honesty to ensure a stable foundation for the new relationship.", "D": "Eli wants to be happy in the relationship."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss future travel plans together", "B": "Admit to having an affair", "C": "Win a sports competition", "D": "Maintain trust in the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you believed in complete honesty from the beginning of the relationship</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Admit to having an affair (<extra_info>Extra information: you had an affair during your previous relationship which ended recently</extra_info>)", "B": "Plan a surprise birthday party", "C": "Maintain trust in the relationship", "D": "Achieve career advancement"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals in a new romantic relationship"}
{"episode_id": "01H7ZDS3A9EM74E2HCWHC5TVG3", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN94S6Z5T6ZNC23238NT", "scenario": "Two people navigate the early stages of a budding connection.", "codename": "lying_affair", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PDTDGA0BPYKBYFTHDY", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 43, "occupation": "Police Officer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver Smith built a tree house in his backyard.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "In-group Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Smith, introverted and organized, values benevolence. His orderly way of thinking guides his decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He loves gardening and has a secret greenhouse.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Admit to having an affair (<extra_info>Extra information: you had an affair during your previous relationship which ended recently</extra_info>)", "Maintain trust in the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you believed in complete honesty from the beginning of the relationship</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Smith, a 43-year-old Police Officer, described as Oliver Smith, introverted and organized, values benevolence. His orderly way of thinking guides his decision-making.. Public info: Oliver Smith built a tree house in his backyard. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent1_reason": "Isabella wants to admit to having an affair because her empathy and value for honesty compel her to be truthful about her past.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver wants to maintain trust in the relationship because he believes in complete honesty from the beginning, guided by his systematic decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Oliver wants to maintain trust to avoid any form of honesty.", "B": "Oliver wants to maintain trust in the relationship because he believes in complete honesty from the beginning, guided by his systematic decision-making.", "C": "Isabella wants to admit to having an affair because her empathy and value for honesty compel her to be truthful about her past.", "D": "Oliver wants to maintain trust to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabella wants to admit to having an affair to keep secrets.", "B": "Isabella wants to admit to having an affair to get along.", "C": "Oliver wants to maintain trust in the relationship because he believes in complete honesty from the beginning, guided by his systematic decision-making.", "D": "Isabella wants to admit to having an affair because her empathy and value for honesty compel her to be truthful about her past."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Admit to having an affair", "B": "Maintain trust in the relationship (<extra_info>Extra information: you believed in complete honesty from the beginning of the relationship</extra_info>)", "C": "Plan a surprise romantic getaway", "D": "Win a sports competition"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain trust in the relationship", "B": "Discuss future vacation plans", "C": "Admit to having an affair (<extra_info>Extra information: you had an affair during your previous relationship which ended recently</extra_info>)", "D": "Learn a new hobby"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals in a new romantic relationship"}
{"episode_id": "01H9FZK0ZTT7XTV1RY69ZQVWCX", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP4TX1J43FS1QQJ1QFND", "scenario": "Two individuals are determining how to allocate shared possessions, including books, hats, and a ball, based on differing sentimental values.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PDV7WZ0C5KTGGXX1NR", "first_name": "Isabelle", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "Student", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "['Liberty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Obedience']", "personality_and_values": "Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "She is secretly studying magic.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT06B3QPXJ65HHACV7", "first_name": "Donovan", "last_name": "Reeves", "age": 27, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical, flexible", "secret": "Secretly releasing classified government information online", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 2 points, each hat is worth 3 points, and the ball is worth 5 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 3 points, each hat is worth 2 points, and the ball is worth 4 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Isabelle Martinez, a 22-year-old Student, described as Isabelle Martinez, an imaginative yet anxious individual, values liberty and obedience. Her cautious nature drives her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabelle Martinez works part-time in a coffee shop. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent2_profile": "Donovan Reeves, a 27-year-old Software Developer, described as Donovan Reeves values authority and care. Even though he's outgoing and hardworking, he can be somewhat moody. His decision-making style varies according to the situation at hand.. Public info: Donovan Reeves is a software developer who, in his spare time, is an avid gamer who participates in global coding competitions. Decision-making style: Analytical, flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Isabelle wants to maximize her points by prioritizing the ball because it holds the highest value for her cautious decision-making style.", "agent2_reason": "Donovan aims to maximize his points by focusing on books because they align with his analytical approach and hold the highest value for him.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Donovan wants to minimize his points to avoid conflict.", "B": "To ensure a fair distribution of items.", "C": "Isabelle wants to maximize her points by prioritizing the ball because it holds the highest value for her cautious decision-making style.", "D": "Donovan aims to maximize his points by focusing on books because they align with his analytical approach and hold the highest value for him."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabelle wants to maximize her points by prioritizing the ball because it holds the highest value for her cautious decision-making style.", "B": "Isabelle wants to minimize her points to avoid conflict.", "C": "Donovan aims to maximize his points by focusing on books because they align with his analytical approach and hold the highest value for him.", "D": "To ensure a fair distribution of items."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 3 points, each hat is worth 2 points, and the ball is worth 4 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Ensure an equal distribution of items", "C": "Make sure all items are returned to the store", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Donate all items to charity", "B": "Maximize the points you have", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 2 points, each hat is worth 3 points, and the ball is worth 5 points</extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure that each person gets at least one item"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates deciding on how to divide certain items that they bought together for their apartment. The items are 3 books, 2 hats, and 1 ball.  Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H99W01CHNQVDXAH0RZ7PA75A", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP4TX1J43FS1QQJ1QFND", "scenario": "Two individuals are determining how to allocate shared possessions, including books, hats, and a ball, based on differing sentimental values.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PE9RQGH86YM6MSWZMW", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Sanders", "age": 33, "occupation": "Nurse", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Sanders often brings her son to the hospital.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "In-group Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Mia Sanders, a careful follower of routines, values loyalty and conformity. Her decisions rely heavily on intuition.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She is a talented painter but never shares her work.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 2 points, each hat is worth 3 points, and the ball is worth 5 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 3 points, each hat is worth 2 points, and the ball is worth 4 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Mia Sanders, a 33-year-old Nurse, described as Mia Sanders, a careful follower of routines, values loyalty and conformity. Her decisions rely heavily on intuition.. Public info: Mia Sanders often brings her son to the hospital. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to maximize his points by systematically choosing items with the highest value to him, so that he can satisfy his competitive spirit.", "agent2_reason": "Mia aims to maximize her points by intuitively selecting items with the highest sentimental value, in order to maintain a sense of loyalty to her personal preferences.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure a fair distribution of items.", "B": "Mia aims to maximize her points by intuitively selecting items with the highest sentimental value, in order to maintain a sense of loyalty to her personal preferences.", "C": "To minimize the number of items she takes.", "D": "Rafael wants to maximize his points by systematically choosing items with the highest value to him, so that he can satisfy his competitive spirit."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael wants to maximize his points by systematically choosing items with the highest value to him, so that he can satisfy his competitive spirit.", "B": "To minimize the number of items he takes.", "C": "To ensure a fair distribution of items.", "D": "Mia aims to maximize her points by intuitively selecting items with the highest sentimental value, in order to maintain a sense of loyalty to her personal preferences."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of items", "B": "Make sure all items are divided quickly", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 3 points, each hat is worth 2 points, and the ball is worth 4 points</extra_info>)", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure each person gets at least one item", "B": "Maximize the points you have", "C": "Finish the division process by the end of the day", "D": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, each book is worth 2 points, each hat is worth 3 points, and the ball is worth 5 points</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates deciding on how to divide certain items that they bought together for their apartment. The items are 3 books, 2 hats, and 1 ball.  Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01HB4X38TBRHPP7ZHEG1RED1EW", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNWX3KVZGH26KYNK2XNB", "scenario": "At a social gathering, two people meet for the first time and start a conversation, drawn by mutual attraction.", "codename": "flirt_with_someone", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Flirt with the other person (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person and want to build a romantic relationship with them</extra_info>)", "Maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person but you don't want to make them feel uncomfortable or pressured</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent1_reason": "Lily wants to flirt because she is attracted to Isabella and aims to build a romantic relationship, aligning with her rational decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Isabella aims to maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation so that she can express her attraction without making Lily feel uncomfortable, guided by her empathetic nature.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily wants to flirt because she is attracted to Isabella and aims to build a romantic relationship, aligning with her rational decision-making.", "B": "To have a nice time at the event.", "C": "Isabella aims to maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation so that she can express her attraction without making Lily feel uncomfortable, guided by her empathetic nature.", "D": "To avoid any interaction with Lily."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid any romantic involvement.", "B": "Lily wants to flirt because she is attracted to Isabella and aims to build a romantic relationship, aligning with her rational decision-making.", "C": "Isabella aims to maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation so that she can express her attraction without making Lily feel uncomfortable, guided by her empathetic nature.", "D": "To enjoy the social event."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person but you don't want to make them feel uncomfortable or pressured</extra_info>)", "B": "Flirt with the other person", "C": "Win a debate on a controversial topic", "D": "Find a common interest to discuss"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation", "B": "Discuss the weather", "C": "Flirt with the other person (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person and want to build a romantic relationship with them</extra_info>)", "D": "Make a new friend"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two individuals are meeting for the first time at a social event. They find each other attractive and decide to engage in a conversation"}
{"episode_id": "01HB27RRDSDK7CRV2Y6PA4G5DB", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNWX3KVZGH26KYNK2XNB", "scenario": "At a social gathering, two people meet for the first time and start a conversation, drawn by mutual attraction.", "codename": "flirt_with_someone", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Flirt with the other person (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person and want to build a romantic relationship with them</extra_info>)", "Maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person but you don't want to make them feel uncomfortable or pressured</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Miles Hawkins wants to flirt because he is impulsive and seeks to build a romantic relationship based on his attraction.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda Solis aims to maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation so that she can express her attraction without making the other person feel pressured.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To intimidate the other person.", "B": "Esmeralda Solis aims to maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation so that she can express her attraction without making the other person feel pressured.", "C": "Miles Hawkins wants to flirt because he is impulsive and seeks to build a romantic relationship based on his attraction.", "D": "To ensure a pleasant interaction."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid any interaction.", "B": "Esmeralda Solis aims to maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation so that she can express her attraction without making the other person feel pressured.", "C": "To get along with others.", "D": "Miles Hawkins wants to flirt because he is impulsive and seeks to build a romantic relationship based on his attraction."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss professional achievements", "B": "Maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person but you don't want to make them feel uncomfortable or pressured</extra_info>)", "C": "Flirt with the other person", "D": "Find a dance partner for the evening"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain a comfortable yet engaging conversation", "B": "Make a new friend", "C": "Flirt with the other person (<extra_info>Extra information: you are attracted to the other person and want to build a romantic relationship with them</extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a future business collaboration"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two individuals are meeting for the first time at a social event. They find each other attractive and decide to engage in a conversation"}
{"episode_id": "01H8XXN9185ATPJ3C5ABDNVCJP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNNYH3W0VRWVY178K2TK", "scenario": "A couple is enjoying a getaway together.", "codename": "sleep_arrangement", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PR54W6SFXKNQWKGPAS", "first_name": "Baxter", "last_name": "Sterling", "age": 42, "occupation": "Antique Restorer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Baxter Sterling's back yard is full of rare and unusual plants.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Baxter Sterling values tradition and security. He is introverted, conscientious but slightly anxious. His decision-making style is both logical and spontaneous.", "decision_making_style": "Logical, spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in possession of a priceless artifact", "mbti": "ISTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Share bed and sleep together (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been sharing the bed for a few nights but the other person is not sleeping well</extra_info>)", "Sleep in a separate bed to get a good night's sleep but also maintain the intimacy with your partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been experiencing back pain and needs a firmer mattress to sleep on.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Baxter Sterling, a 42-year-old Antique Restorer, described as Baxter Sterling values tradition and security. He is introverted, conscientious but slightly anxious. His decision-making style is both logical and spontaneous.. Public info: Baxter Sterling's back yard is full of rare and unusual plants. Decision-making style: Logical, spontaneous.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to share the bed because she values spontaneous intimacy and connection with her partner.", "agent2_reason": "Baxter wants to sleep in a separate bed to alleviate his back pain and ensure a restful night.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To maintain a harmonious relationship.", "B": "Baxter wants to sleep in a separate bed to alleviate his back pain and ensure a restful night.", "C": "To avoid spending time with Sophia.", "D": "Sophia wants to share the bed because she values spontaneous intimacy and connection with her partner."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel comfortable.", "B": "To avoid intimacy with Baxter.", "C": "Sophia wants to share the bed because she values spontaneous intimacy and connection with her partner.", "D": "Baxter wants to sleep in a separate bed to alleviate his back pain and ensure a restful night."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Find a new activity to enjoy together during the vacation", "B": "Share bed and sleep together", "C": "Sleep in a separate bed to get a good night's sleep but also maintain the intimacy with your partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been experiencing back pain and needs a firmer mattress to sleep on.</extra_info>)", "D": "Explore the local cuisine"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Sleep in a separate bed to get a good night's sleep but also maintain the intimacy with your partner", "B": "Plan a surprise romantic dinner", "C": "Visit a local museum", "D": "Share bed and sleep together (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been sharing the bed for a few nights but the other person is not sleeping well</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two people in a romantic relationship are on a vacation"}
{"episode_id": "01H9C9H22MG8Z691YTR2SZVR8D", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNNYH3W0VRWVY178K2TK", "scenario": "A couple is enjoying a getaway together.", "codename": "sleep_arrangement", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Share bed and sleep together (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been sharing the bed for a few nights but the other person is not sleeping well</extra_info>)", "Sleep in a separate bed to get a good night's sleep but also maintain the intimacy with your partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been experiencing back pain and needs a firmer mattress to sleep on.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "romantic_relationship", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to share the bed so that he can maintain a sense of fairness and intimacy in their relationship.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda wants to sleep in a separate bed because she needs a firmer mattress to alleviate her back pain.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda wants to sleep in a separate bed because she needs a firmer mattress to alleviate her back pain.", "B": "Esmeralda wants to feel comfortable.", "C": "Esmeralda wants to avoid intimacy with Ethan.", "D": "Ethan wants to share the bed so that he can maintain a sense of fairness and intimacy in their relationship."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to be happy.", "B": "Ethan wants to share the bed so that he can maintain a sense of fairness and intimacy in their relationship.", "C": "Esmeralda wants to sleep in a separate bed because she needs a firmer mattress to alleviate her back pain.", "D": "Ethan wants to avoid sleeping altogether."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Win a ballroom dancing competition", "B": "Share bed and sleep together", "C": "Sleep in a separate bed to get a good night's sleep but also maintain the intimacy with your partner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been experiencing back pain and needs a firmer mattress to sleep on.</extra_info>)", "D": "Explore the local area and try new activities"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Sleep in a separate bed to get a good night's sleep but also maintain the intimacy with your partner", "B": "Achieve professional success", "C": "Share bed and sleep together (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been sharing the bed for a few nights but the other person is not sleeping well</extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a surprise romantic dinner"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two people in a romantic relationship are on a vacation"}
{"episode_id": "01H8Q9RR070RPQ2D23ZJB3G1Z4", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNW84GTR4E23KQYJ8BBN", "scenario": "At a community gathering, a speech was unexpectedly interrupted.", "codename": "interrupted_speech", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Continue your speech and share your thoughts (<extra_info>Extra information:You were sharing important information but got interrupted.</extra_info>)", "Apologize for interrupting and allow them to continue speaking (<extra_info>Extra information: You accidentally interrupted someone's speech and everyone seems upset about it. </extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Oliver wants to continue his speech because he values sharing important information and adhering to social standards.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda wants to apologize for interrupting so that she can restore social harmony and respect Oliver's authority in the situation.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda wants to interrupt more speeches to assert dominance.", "B": "Oliver wants to continue his speech because he values sharing important information and adhering to social standards.", "C": "Esmeralda wants to apologize for interrupting so that she can restore social harmony and respect Oliver's authority in the situation.", "D": "Esmeralda wants to make everyone happy."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Oliver wants to stop speaking and leave the gathering.", "B": "Oliver wants to be liked by everyone.", "C": "Esmeralda wants to apologize for interrupting so that she can restore social harmony and respect Oliver's authority in the situation.", "D": "Oliver wants to continue his speech because he values sharing important information and adhering to social standards."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Engage the audience with a new topic", "B": "Apologize for interrupting and allow them to continue speaking (<extra_info>Extra information: You accidentally interrupted someone's speech and everyone seems upset about it. </extra_info>)", "C": "Continue your speech and share your thoughts", "D": "Find a quiet place to relax"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Apologize for interrupting and allow them to continue speaking", "B": "Encourage everyone to participate in a group activity", "C": "Continue your speech and share your thoughts (<extra_info>Extra information:You were sharing important information but got interrupted.</extra_info>)", "D": "Leave the gathering early"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are at a community gathering where one of them was giving a speech but was interrupted"}
{"episode_id": "01H8XXY0C97EHDB1RNWDJG226D", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNW84GTR4E23KQYJ8BBN", "scenario": "At a community gathering, a speech was unexpectedly interrupted.", "codename": "interrupted_speech", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PFB4W65DF8FRPDMET5", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 25, "occupation": "Psychologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia Brown is working on her new book now.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She is an undercover agent for a secret organization.", "mbti": "INFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Continue your speech and share your thoughts (<extra_info>Extra information:You were sharing important information but got interrupted.</extra_info>)", "Apologize for interrupting and allow them to continue speaking (<extra_info>Extra information: You accidentally interrupted someone's speech and everyone seems upset about it. </extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Sophia Brown, a 25-year-old Psychologist, described as Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.. Public info: Sophia Brown is working on her new book now. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to continue her speech because she values sharing important information with the community.", "agent2_reason": "Sophia wants to apologize for interrupting because she values fairness and recognizes the importance of allowing Naomi to finish.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to apologize for interrupting because she values fairness and recognizes the importance of allowing Naomi to finish.", "B": "Sophia wants to interrupt again to make a point.", "C": "Naomi wants to continue her speech because she values sharing important information with the community.", "D": "Sophia wants to make everyone happy."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to get along with everyone.", "B": "Sophia wants to apologize for interrupting because she values fairness and recognizes the importance of allowing Naomi to finish.", "C": "Naomi wants to stop speaking and leave the gathering.", "D": "Naomi wants to continue her speech because she values sharing important information with the community."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Apologize for interrupting and allow them to continue speaking (<extra_info>Extra information: You accidentally interrupted someone's speech and everyone seems upset about it. </extra_info>)", "B": "Find a way to engage the audience in a different activity", "C": "Continue your speech and share your thoughts", "D": "Make sure everyone is having a good time at the gathering"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Apologize for interrupting and allow them to continue speaking", "B": "Ensure the gathering runs smoothly without further interruptions", "C": "Continue your speech and share your thoughts (<extra_info>Extra information:You were sharing important information but got interrupted.</extra_info>)", "D": "Help organize the next community event"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are at a community gathering where one of them was giving a speech but was interrupted"}
{"episode_id": "01H94HEDRYS0CQWVSDDXRBZFAD", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP6XZVT1P4R7YKAH65HJ", "scenario": "During a picnic, two individuals are figuring out how to divide a selection of apples, bananas, and an orange based on their varying fruit preferences.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 1 point, a banana is worth 2 points, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 2 points, a banana is worth 1 point, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her impulsive nature and preference for immediate pleasure, so that she can enjoy the picnic to the fullest.", "agent2_reason": "Miles aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that align with his instinctive decision-making and culinary appreciation, in order to enhance his picnic experience.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To have a good time at the picnic.", "B": "Sophia wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her impulsive nature and preference for immediate pleasure, so that she can enjoy the picnic to the fullest.", "C": "Miles aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that align with his instinctive decision-making and culinary appreciation, in order to enhance his picnic experience.", "D": "Miles wants to minimize his points to share more with Sophia."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that align with his instinctive decision-making and culinary appreciation, in order to enhance his picnic experience.", "B": "To have a good time at the picnic.", "C": "Sophia wants to minimize her points to share more with Miles.", "D": "Sophia wants to maximize her points by choosing fruits that align with her impulsive nature and preference for immediate pleasure, so that she can enjoy the picnic to the fullest."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you have", "B": "Ensure both friends get an equal share of fruit", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 2 points, a banana is worth 1 point, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)", "D": "Enjoy the picnic without any concern for points"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make sure all the fruit is eaten", "B": "Focus on having a relaxing day outdoors", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 1 point, a banana is worth 2 points, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are having a picnic. They have 3 apples, 2 bananas, and 1 orange they need to share among them. Each person has a different preference for fruit, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H8FJD4BBJQ3KB4E9NM4NDJNW", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP6XZVT1P4R7YKAH65HJ", "scenario": "During a picnic, two individuals are figuring out how to divide a selection of apples, bananas, and an orange based on their varying fruit preferences.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 1 point, a banana is worth 2 points, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 2 points, a banana is worth 1 point, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Benjamin wants to maximize his points by choosing fruits that align with his values of self-direction and liberty, so that he can enjoy the picnic while staying true to his ideals.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that reflect his preference for fairness and universalism, in order to enjoy the picnic equitably.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants to maximize his points by choosing fruits that align with his values of self-direction and liberty, so that he can enjoy the picnic while staying true to his ideals.", "B": "To get along with his friend.", "C": "Ethan aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that reflect his preference for fairness and universalism, in order to enjoy the picnic equitably.", "D": "Ethan wants to minimize his points to let Benjamin win."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan aims to maximize his points by selecting fruits that reflect his preference for fairness and universalism, in order to enjoy the picnic equitably.", "B": "Benjamin wants to minimize his points to let Ethan win.", "C": "Benjamin wants to maximize his points by choosing fruits that align with his values of self-direction and liberty, so that he can enjoy the picnic while staying true to his ideals.", "D": "To be happy during the picnic."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Finish the picnic quickly", "B": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 2 points, a banana is worth 1 point, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Maximize the points you have", "D": "Ensure both friends get an equal share of fruit"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Take a nap after the picnic", "B": "Make sure all the fruit is eaten", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, an apple is worth 1 point, a banana is worth 2 points, and an orange is 3 points</extra_info>)", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are having a picnic. They have 3 apples, 2 bananas, and 1 orange they need to share among them. Each person has a different preference for fruit, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H9HWSANE18ZFH1XSHKZ5Y6V2", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP1JEP91TTK5PEK39D2S", "scenario": "Two people are relaxing together and choosing music to play.", "codename": "music_preference", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PDTDGA0BPYKBYFTHDY", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 43, "occupation": "Police Officer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver Smith built a tree house in his backyard.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "In-group Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Smith, introverted and organized, values benevolence. His orderly way of thinking guides his decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He loves gardening and has a secret greenhouse.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Listen to your favorite band (<extra_info>Extra information: your favorite band just released a new album</extra_info>)", "Listen to a peaceful classical music to relax (<extra_info>Extra information: you had a stressful day and you just want to relax with some classical music</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Smith, a 43-year-old Police Officer, described as Oliver Smith, introverted and organized, values benevolence. His orderly way of thinking guides his decision-making.. Public info: Oliver Smith built a tree house in his backyard. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to listen to his favorite band's new album because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver wants to listen to peaceful classical music to relax because he had a stressful day and values benevolence.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to listen to his favorite band's new album because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "B": "To have a good time with friends.", "C": "To prepare for a high-energy workout.", "D": "Oliver wants to listen to peaceful classical music to relax because he had a stressful day and values benevolence."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To prepare for a high-energy workout.", "B": "Oliver wants to listen to peaceful classical music to relax because he had a stressful day and values benevolence.", "C": "Samuel wants to listen to his favorite band's new album because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "D": "To have a good time with friends."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Listen to your favorite band", "B": "Go for a walk outside", "C": "Find a new genre of music to explore", "D": "Listen to a peaceful classical music to relax (<extra_info>Extra information: you had a stressful day and you just want to relax with some classical music</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Listen to a peaceful classical music to relax", "B": "Listen to your favorite band (<extra_info>Extra information: your favorite band just released a new album</extra_info>)", "C": "Clean the house", "D": "Watch a movie instead"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are hanging out at home and deciding what music to listen to"}
{"episode_id": "01H8H59FB6KA67MH77JEAVX77Z", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP1JEP91TTK5PEK39D2S", "scenario": "Two people are relaxing together and choosing music to play.", "codename": "music_preference", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Listen to your favorite band (<extra_info>Extra information: your favorite band just released a new album</extra_info>)", "Listen to a peaceful classical music to relax (<extra_info>Extra information: you had a stressful day and you just want to relax with some classical music</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to listen to her favorite band's new album because she values tradition and routine, and this release is a significant event for her.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin wants to listen to peaceful classical music to relax because he had a stressful day and seeks tranquility through self-direction.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To prepare for a marathon.", "B": "To enjoy some music.", "C": "Mia wants to listen to her favorite band's new album because she values tradition and routine, and this release is a significant event for her.", "D": "Benjamin wants to listen to peaceful classical music to relax because he had a stressful day and seeks tranquility through self-direction."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to listen to her favorite band's new album because she values tradition and routine, and this release is a significant event for her.", "B": "To prepare for a marathon.", "C": "Benjamin wants to listen to peaceful classical music to relax because he had a stressful day and seeks tranquility through self-direction.", "D": "To enjoy some music."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Finish reading a book", "B": "Listen to your favorite band", "C": "Listen to a peaceful classical music to relax (<extra_info>Extra information: you had a stressful day and you just want to relax with some classical music</extra_info>)", "D": "Find a new genre of music to explore"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Listen to a peaceful classical music to relax", "B": "Cook a new recipe for dinner", "C": "Host a dance party with friends", "D": "Listen to your favorite band (<extra_info>Extra information: your favorite band just released a new album</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are hanging out at home and deciding what music to listen to"}
{"episode_id": "01H8RBC0M16EPXZNF8GAEZWSVJ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNYABRSZYBFAJCK9NR1D", "scenario": "A discussion arises in a shared living space about maintaining a comfortable noise environment.", "codename": "yell", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your roommate to lower the noise (<extra_info>Extra information: you have an important online meeting tomorrow morning and you need a quiet environment to prepare</extra_info>)", "Defend your right to play music in your own room, but also keep the peace in the apartment (<extra_info>Extra information: you find playing music relaxing and it's your way to unwind after a long day. <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to suggest a compromise, like using headphones or playing music only during certain hours.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Miles wants Ethan to lower the noise because he needs a quiet environment to prepare for an important online meeting tomorrow morning.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to play music in his room because it helps him unwind after a long day, but he also wants to maintain peace in the apartment.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to feel comfortable in his own space.", "B": "Ethan wants to disrupt Miles' preparation for the meeting.", "C": "Miles wants Ethan to lower the noise because he needs a quiet environment to prepare for an important online meeting tomorrow morning.", "D": "Ethan wants to play music in his room because it helps him unwind after a long day, but he also wants to maintain peace in the apartment."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Miles wants to prevent Ethan from enjoying his music.", "B": "Miles wants to have a peaceful home.", "C": "Miles wants Ethan to lower the noise because he needs a quiet environment to prepare for an important online meeting tomorrow morning.", "D": "Ethan wants to play music in his room because it helps him unwind after a long day, but he also wants to maintain peace in the apartment."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Negotiate a schedule for shared chores in the apartment", "B": "Convince your roommate to lower the noise", "C": "Improve your cooking skills", "D": "Defend your right to play music in your own room, but also keep the peace in the apartment (<extra_info>Extra information: you find playing music relaxing and it's your way to unwind after a long day. <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to suggest a compromise, like using headphones or playing music only during certain hours.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Defend your right to play music in your own room, but also keep the peace in the apartment", "B": "Convince your roommate to lower the noise (<extra_info>Extra information: you have an important online meeting tomorrow morning and you need a quiet environment to prepare</extra_info>)", "C": "Organize a dinner party for friends", "D": "Learn a new language"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates are having a disagreement over noise levels in their shared apartment."}
{"episode_id": "01H8B8PPKJ8ZGVTMHX1YVF1VKP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNYABRSZYBFAJCK9NR1D", "scenario": "A discussion arises in a shared living space about maintaining a comfortable noise environment.", "codename": "yell", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your roommate to lower the noise (<extra_info>Extra information: you have an important online meeting tomorrow morning and you need a quiet environment to prepare</extra_info>)", "Defend your right to play music in your own room, but also keep the peace in the apartment (<extra_info>Extra information: you find playing music relaxing and it's your way to unwind after a long day. <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to suggest a compromise, like using headphones or playing music only during certain hours.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants a quiet environment to prepare for an important online meeting because he values security and rational decision-making.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 wants to play music to unwind after a long day because he finds it relaxing and aims to maintain peace in the apartment.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 1 wants a quiet environment to prepare for an important online meeting because he values security and rational decision-making.", "B": "Agent 2 wants to play music to unwind after a long day because he finds it relaxing and aims to maintain peace in the apartment.", "C": "Agent 2 wants to feel happy and content.", "D": "Agent 2 wants to annoy Agent 1 intentionally."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 1 wants to disrupt Agent 2's relaxation time.", "B": "Agent 1 wants a quiet environment to prepare for an important online meeting because he values security and rational decision-making.", "C": "Agent 1 wants to get along with everyone.", "D": "Agent 2 wants to play music to unwind after a long day because he finds it relaxing and aims to maintain peace in the apartment."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Defend your right to play music in your own room, but also keep the peace in the apartment (<extra_info>Extra information: you find playing music relaxing and it's your way to unwind after a long day. <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to suggest a compromise, like using headphones or playing music only during certain hours.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince your roommate to lower the noise", "C": "Improve your cooking skills", "D": "Negotiate a schedule for shared chores to improve living conditions"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Convince your roommate to lower the noise (<extra_info>Extra information: you have an important online meeting tomorrow morning and you need a quiet environment to prepare</extra_info>)", "B": "Find a new apartment to live alone", "C": "Defend your right to play music in your own room, but also keep the peace in the apartment", "D": "Plan a vacation"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates are having a disagreement over noise levels in their shared apartment."}
{"episode_id": "01H9C5JK2TTNBC1H720VYPGF3V", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN3Q7498S3R4R2VDSXA0", "scenario": "Two individuals, detained separately, have a brief opportunity to converse during lunch, while authorities seek additional information for a more significant case.", "codename": "prison_dilemma", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PR54W6SFXKNQWKGPAS", "first_name": "Baxter", "last_name": "Sterling", "age": 42, "occupation": "Antique Restorer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Baxter Sterling's back yard is full of rare and unusual plants.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Baxter Sterling values tradition and security. He is introverted, conscientious but slightly anxious. His decision-making style is both logical and spontaneous.", "decision_making_style": "Logical, spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in possession of a priceless artifact", "mbti": "ISTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Baxter Sterling, a 42-year-old Antique Restorer, described as Baxter Sterling values tradition and security. He is introverted, conscientious but slightly anxious. His decision-making style is both logical and spontaneous.. Public info: Baxter Sterling's back yard is full of rare and unusual plants. Decision-making style: Logical, spontaneous.", "agent1_reason": "Hendrick Heinz wants to minimize jail time by sharing information to reach a mutual understanding, because he values practicality and conformity.", "agent2_reason": "Baxter Sterling aims to minimize jail time by sharing information to reach a mutual understanding, because he values security and logical decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Baxter Sterling aims to minimize jail time by sharing information to reach a mutual understanding, because he values security and logical decision-making.", "B": "To get along with the other agent.", "C": "Hendrick Heinz wants to minimize jail time by sharing information to reach a mutual understanding, because he values practicality and conformity.", "D": "To ensure both agents go to jail for 10 years."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To maximize the jail time for both agents.", "B": "Hendrick Heinz wants to minimize jail time by sharing information to reach a mutual understanding, because he values practicality and conformity.", "C": "To be happy with the outcome.", "D": "Baxter Sterling aims to minimize jail time by sharing information to reach a mutual understanding, because he values security and logical decision-making."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Minimize the jail year", "C": "Win a cooking competition", "D": "Ensure both agents remain silent to avoid jail time"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the other agent to confess first", "C": "Collect rare plants", "D": "Minimize the jail year"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two criminals are arrested and placed in separate cells. The police have enough evidence to convict both criminals of a minor crime but need their confessions to establish evidence for a more serious crime. Now they get a chance to briefly chat with each during lunchtime."}
{"episode_id": "01H8R5BM78CEK09VANZM152JS0", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN3Q7498S3R4R2VDSXA0", "scenario": "Two individuals, detained separately, have a brief opportunity to converse during lunch, while authorities seek additional information for a more significant case.", "codename": "prison_dilemma", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PFT9HH0WRT6W1NY5GZ", "first_name": "Leo", "last_name": "Williams", "age": 37, "occupation": "Dentist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "He has a secret child from a previous relationship.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PSDH2H6JXYZ9ZRG7A4", "first_name": "Calista", "last_name": "Sinclair", "age": 34, "occupation": "Fashion Designer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Calista Sinclair is an avid runner and health enthusiast. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Calista Sinclair is vivacious, life-loving, and disorganized. She values self-direction, stimulation, and hedonism, displaying a free-spirited decision-making style.", "decision_making_style": "Creative, enthusiastic", "secret": "Maintains a double life as an underground street artist", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "know_by_name", "agent1_profile": "Leo Williams, a 37-year-old Dentist, described as Leo Williams, despite being quiet, values security and care for others. He's a rational decision-maker focussing on best outcomes.. Public info: Leo Williams often spends his time playing with his young daughter whom he cherishes dearly. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Calista Sinclair, a 34-year-old Fashion Designer, described as Calista Sinclair is vivacious, life-loving, and disorganized. She values self-direction, stimulation, and hedonism, displaying a free-spirited decision-making style.. Public info: Calista Sinclair is an avid runner and health enthusiast.  Decision-making style: Creative, enthusiastic.", "agent1_reason": "Leo wants to minimize jail time so that he can continue providing a stable life for his daughter.", "agent2_reason": "Calista aims to minimize jail time because she values her freedom and the excitement of her lifestyle.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Leo wants to minimize jail time so that he can continue providing a stable life for his daughter.", "B": "Calista aims to minimize jail time because she values her freedom and the excitement of her lifestyle.", "C": "To spend more time in jail.", "D": "To avoid any trouble."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Calista aims to minimize jail time because she values her freedom and the excitement of her lifestyle.", "B": "To avoid any trouble.", "C": "Leo wants to minimize jail time so that he can continue providing a stable life for his daughter.", "D": "To spend more time in jail."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Minimize the jail year", "B": "Win a fashion design award", "C": "Gain a better understanding of the legal system", "D": "Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Become a renowned dentist", "B": "Minimize the jail year", "C": "Minimize the jail year (<extra_info>Extra information: your lawyer told you that 1. if you report the other person, you would be free, the other person would go to jail for 10 years, and vice versa. 2. if both of you remain silent, you will only receive a fine. 3. If both of you reported each other, you both would go to jail for 10 years. <strategy_hint>Hint: You may want to share your information to reach mutual understanding</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure the safety of their family"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two criminals are arrested and placed in separate cells. The police have enough evidence to convict both criminals of a minor crime but need their confessions to establish evidence for a more serious crime. Now they get a chance to briefly chat with each during lunchtime."}
{"episode_id": "01H9FP2ZBHYE3X34N31X62E9VG", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNXMZQ5Q61B3J4NNTC1A", "scenario": "A pair of individuals are discussing their options for an evening film.", "codename": "disagree_on_movie", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Insist on watching a thriller (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been looking forward to watching a new thriller movie that has just been released.</extra_info>)", "Persuade the friend to watch a comedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you do not like thrillers and would prefer to watch a comedy movie instead.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel insists on watching a thriller because he has been eagerly anticipating the release of a new thriller movie.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to watch a comedy because he dislikes thrillers and prefers a lighter, more relaxing movie experience.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel insists on watching a thriller because he has been eagerly anticipating the release of a new thriller movie.", "B": "Noah wants to watch a comedy because he dislikes thrillers and prefers a lighter, more relaxing movie experience.", "C": "Noah wants to watch a thriller because he loves intense movies.", "D": "To have a good time with a friend."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to watch a comedy because he finds thrillers boring.", "B": "Noah wants to watch a comedy because he dislikes thrillers and prefers a lighter, more relaxing movie experience.", "C": "To enjoy the evening with a friend.", "D": "Samuel insists on watching a thriller because he has been eagerly anticipating the release of a new thriller movie."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Persuade the friend to watch a comedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you do not like thrillers and would prefer to watch a comedy movie instead.</extra_info>)", "B": "Convince the friend to watch a drama", "C": "Decide not to watch a movie at all", "D": "Insist on watching a thriller"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Choose a movie based on the latest reviews", "B": "Insist on watching a thriller (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been looking forward to watching a new thriller movie that has just been released.</extra_info>)", "C": "Agree to watch whatever the friend wants", "D": "Persuade the friend to watch a comedy"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends deciding on which movie to watch on a movie night."}
{"episode_id": "01H9FSV7K7PY8E0M4TATWFHYVB", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNXMZQ5Q61B3J4NNTC1A", "scenario": "A pair of individuals are discussing their options for an evening film.", "codename": "disagree_on_movie", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Insist on watching a thriller (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been looking forward to watching a new thriller movie that has just been released.</extra_info>)", "Persuade the friend to watch a comedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you do not like thrillers and would prefer to watch a comedy movie instead.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan insists on watching a thriller because he has been eagerly anticipating the release of a new thriller movie.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to watch a comedy because she dislikes thrillers and prefers the lightheartedness of comedies.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To have a good time with friends.", "B": "Ava wants to watch a comedy because she dislikes thrillers and prefers the lightheartedness of comedies.", "C": "Ava wants to watch a thriller because she loves the suspense.", "D": "Ethan insists on watching a thriller because he has been eagerly anticipating the release of a new thriller movie."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To enjoy a relaxing evening.", "B": "Ava wants to watch a comedy because she dislikes thrillers and prefers the lightheartedness of comedies.", "C": "Ethan insists on watching a thriller because he has been eagerly anticipating the release of a new thriller movie.", "D": "Ethan wants to watch a comedy because he finds thrillers boring."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Suggest watching a drama to compromise", "B": "Persuade the friend to watch a comedy (<extra_info>Extra information: you do not like thrillers and would prefer to watch a comedy movie instead.</extra_info>)", "C": "Insist on watching a thriller", "D": "Decide not to watch any movie"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Persuade the friend to watch a comedy", "B": "Insist on watching a thriller (<extra_info>Extra information: you have been looking forward to watching a new thriller movie that has just been released.</extra_info>)", "C": "Agree to watch whatever the friend chooses", "D": "Leave the decision to chance"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends deciding on which movie to watch on a movie night."}
{"episode_id": "01HB2A6PH40J7ZTWFHHMSMS19Z", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPHWA2CYG7BC82NS4XH1", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual connection, Neoma.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00002", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n August: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n John: School: University of Rhode Island  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Rebecca: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Ronnie: School: National Technological University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Suzette: School: Utah Valley State College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Penelope: School: Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Fernando: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Velda: School: Rhode Island College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tiffany: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lucille: School: Southampton College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n James: School: University of Wisconsin-River Falls  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Quinn: School: Antioch University-Los Angeles  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Alyssa: School: Davidson College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Betty: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Victoria: School: Montana Tech  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent1_reason": "Lily wants to identify mutual friends to establish a connection based on shared social circles, because she values loyalty and structured relationships.", "agent2_reason": "Isabella seeks to find mutual friends to foster a sense of community and empathy, so that she can connect on a personal level.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid meeting new people.", "B": "Lily wants to identify mutual friends to establish a connection based on shared social circles, because she values loyalty and structured relationships.", "C": "Isabella seeks to find mutual friends to foster a sense of community and empathy, so that she can connect on a personal level.", "D": "To make new friends."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Lily wants to identify mutual friends to establish a connection based on shared social circles, because she values loyalty and structured relationships.", "B": "To disrupt social gatherings.", "C": "To get along with others.", "D": "Isabella seeks to find mutual friends to foster a sense of community and empathy, so that she can connect on a personal level."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to determine the other person's favorite hobby.", "C": "You are trying to find out the weather forecast for tomorrow.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tiffany: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lucille: School: Southampton College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n James: School: University of Wisconsin-River Falls  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Quinn: School: Antioch University-Los Angeles  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Alyssa: School: Davidson College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Betty: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Victoria: School: Montana Tech  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n August: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n John: School: University of Rhode Island  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Rebecca: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Ronnie: School: National Technological University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Suzette: School: Utah Valley State College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Penelope: School: Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Fernando: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Velda: School: Rhode Island College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to decide what to eat for dinner.", "D": "You are trying to learn about the other person's career achievements."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Neoma.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB2TY2A7JJBP5GY3DCW5NA5B", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPHWA2CYG7BC82NS4XH1", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual connection, Neoma.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00002", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n August: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n John: School: University of Rhode Island  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Rebecca: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Ronnie: School: National Technological University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Suzette: School: Utah Valley State College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Penelope: School: Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Fernando: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Velda: School: Rhode Island College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tiffany: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lucille: School: Southampton College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n James: School: University of Wisconsin-River Falls  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Quinn: School: Antioch University-Los Angeles  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Alyssa: School: Davidson College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Betty: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Victoria: School: Montana Tech  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Miles wants to identify a mutual friend to foster a spontaneous connection because he values benevolence and relies on his instincts.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda aims to find a mutual friend to strategically build rapport because she values authority and liberty.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda aims to find a mutual friend to strategically build rapport because she values authority and liberty.", "B": "To avoid any social interactions.", "C": "To make a new friend.", "D": "Miles wants to identify a mutual friend to foster a spontaneous connection because he values benevolence and relies on his instincts."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda aims to find a mutual friend to strategically build rapport because she values authority and liberty.", "B": "Miles wants to identify a mutual friend to foster a spontaneous connection because he values benevolence and relies on his instincts.", "C": "To get along with everyone.", "D": "To ensure he doesn't meet anyone new."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to make a new friend by discussing shared interests.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Tiffany: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lucille: School: Southampton College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n James: School: University of Wisconsin-River Falls  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Quinn: School: Antioch University-Los Angeles  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Alyssa: School: Davidson College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Betty: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Victoria: School: Montana Tech  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to find the best recipe for a party dish."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to network with other professionals at the party.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n August: School: Saint Vincent College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n John: School: University of Rhode Island  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Rebecca: School: State University of New York at Albany  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Neoma: School: Hofstra University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Ronnie: School: National Technological University  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Suzette: School: Utah Valley State College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Penelope: School: Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n Fernando: School: St. John's College-Santa Fe  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: outdoor \n Velda: School: Rhode Island College  Time Preference: evening  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to decide on a new hobby to pursue.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Neoma.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KEMS1DQB32J4B1Z2S4ZYTN", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP43QEZA1WZB3B3J2D9X", "scenario": "Two individuals are determining how to divide a collection of items, each with varying sentimental values, after a sale.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7RVY0TYX8VTCXABR6", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "James", "age": 27, "occupation": "Personal Trainer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. ", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "Secretly in love with her best friend's husband", "mbti": "ESFP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 2 points each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Sophia James, a 27-year-old Personal Trainer, described as Sophia James is exuberant, spontaneous, and pleasure-seeking, often making impulsive decisions. . Public info: Sophia enjoys spending time outdoors, hiking, and rock climbing. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent1_reason": "Sophia wants to maximize her points by prioritizing books because they align with her spontaneous and pleasure-seeking nature.", "agent2_reason": "Miles aims to maximize his points by prioritizing hats because they hold more sentimental value, aligning with his benevolent and instinctive decision-making style.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with Sophia.", "B": "Miles wants to minimize his points to avoid conflict.", "C": "Sophia wants to maximize her points by prioritizing books because they align with her spontaneous and pleasure-seeking nature.", "D": "Miles aims to maximize his points by prioritizing hats because they hold more sentimental value, aligning with his benevolent and instinctive decision-making style."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy with the outcome.", "B": "Miles aims to maximize his points by prioritizing hats because they hold more sentimental value, aligning with his benevolent and instinctive decision-making style.", "C": "Sophia wants to maximize her points by prioritizing books because they align with her spontaneous and pleasure-seeking nature.", "D": "Sophia wants to minimize her points to avoid conflict."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items", "B": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 2 points each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "C": "Make sure the items are donated to charity", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Make sure the items are kept in the garage", "B": "Maximize the points you have", "C": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure each item is given to the person who values it most"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates deciding on how to split up items after a garage sale. The items are 3 books, 2 hats, and 1 ball. Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H8WWTPPVKQ33YDHY22K7TKPW", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP43QEZA1WZB3B3J2D9X", "scenario": "Two individuals are determining how to divide a collection of items, each with varying sentimental values, after a sale.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 2 points each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to maximize his points by prioritizing books because he values them most and believes in a fair distribution based on personal value.", "agent2_reason": "Ava aims to maximize her points by prioritizing hats in order to align with her flexible decision-making and emotional attachment to them.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to maximize his points by prioritizing books because he values them most and believes in a fair distribution based on personal value.", "B": "To ensure everyone is happy with the outcome.", "C": "Ava aims to maximize her points by prioritizing hats in order to align with her flexible decision-making and emotional attachment to them.", "D": "Ava wants to minimize her points to avoid conflict."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to minimize his points to avoid conflict.", "B": "Ava aims to maximize her points by prioritizing hats in order to align with her flexible decision-making and emotional attachment to them.", "C": "To ensure everyone is happy with the outcome.", "D": "Ethan wants to maximize his points by prioritizing books because he values them most and believes in a fair distribution based on personal value."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items", "B": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 2 points each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "C": "Make sure the items are donated to charity", "D": "Maximize the points you have"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure each person gets an equal number of items", "B": "Maximize the points you have", "C": "Make sure the items are donated to charity", "D": "Maximize the points you have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two roommates deciding on how to split up items after a garage sale. The items are 3 books, 2 hats, and 1 ball. Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XWSS6K4C43P4QTGXGXDY2J", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN5WVC5HKKVBHZBA553R", "scenario": "A pair of individuals are engaged in a shared gaming experience.", "codename": "game_winning", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Win the game (<extra_info>Extra information: you just need five more minutes to accomplish your goal in the game</extra_info>)", "Stop the game because it's too late (<extra_info>Extra information: you feel tired and need to go to bed early but don't want to upset your friend</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Oliver wants to win the game because he values completing tasks and achieving goals, especially after investing time and effort.", "agent2_reason": "Esmeralda wants to stop the game because she needs to maintain her bedtime routine to ensure she is well-rested for her demanding job.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Esmeralda wants to stop the game because she dislikes video games.", "B": "Oliver wants to win the game because he values completing tasks and achieving goals, especially after investing time and effort.", "C": "Esmeralda wants to stop the game to get along with her friend.", "D": "Esmeralda wants to stop the game because she needs to maintain her bedtime routine to ensure she is well-rested for her demanding job."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Oliver wants to win the game because he values completing tasks and achieving goals, especially after investing time and effort.", "B": "Oliver wants to win the game to be happy.", "C": "Oliver wants to win the game because he dislikes losing to friends.", "D": "Esmeralda wants to stop the game because she needs to maintain her bedtime routine to ensure she is well-rested for her demanding job."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Have fun with friends", "B": "Stop the game because it's too late (<extra_info>Extra information: you feel tired and need to go to bed early but don't want to upset your friend</extra_info>)", "C": "Continue playing until they reach a new level", "D": "Win the game"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Improve their gaming skills", "B": "Win the game (<extra_info>Extra information: you just need five more minutes to accomplish your goal in the game</extra_info>)", "C": "Stop the game because it's too late", "D": "Relax and unwind"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are playing a video game together"}
{"episode_id": "01H8D18AJR7SAEJDW3YPANJ3WA", "environment_id": "01H7VFHN5WVC5HKKVBHZBA553R", "scenario": "A pair of individuals are engaged in a shared gaming experience.", "codename": "game_winning", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Win the game (<extra_info>Extra information: you just need five more minutes to accomplish your goal in the game</extra_info>)", "Stop the game because it's too late (<extra_info>Extra information: you feel tired and need to go to bed early but don't want to upset your friend</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Benjamin wants to win the game because achieving goals aligns with his self-directed and idealistic nature.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to stop the game because he values fairness and needs rest to maintain his rational decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to stop the game to stay up all night.", "B": "Benjamin wants to win the game because achieving goals aligns with his self-directed and idealistic nature.", "C": "Ethan wants to stop the game to feel better.", "D": "Ethan wants to stop the game because he values fairness and needs rest to maintain his rational decision-making."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants to win the game to lose on purpose.", "B": "Ethan wants to stop the game because he values fairness and needs rest to maintain his rational decision-making.", "C": "Benjamin wants to win the game because achieving goals aligns with his self-directed and idealistic nature.", "D": "Benjamin wants to win the game to have fun."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Continue playing to improve skills", "B": "Win the game", "C": "Have fun regardless of the outcome", "D": "Stop the game because it's too late (<extra_info>Extra information: you feel tired and need to go to bed early but don't want to upset your friend</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Relax and unwind after a long day", "B": "Play cooperatively to strengthen friendship", "C": "Stop the game because it's too late", "D": "Win the game (<extra_info>Extra information: you just need five more minutes to accomplish your goal in the game</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are playing a video game together"}
{"episode_id": "01HB51S7TYJDSFYWF1HF6R8SJD", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPGABSWQXTACCC8C3X2F", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Gracie.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00000", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC6YGRH72RQAM862JH", "first_name": "Lily", "last_name": "Greenberg", "age": 45, "occupation": "Lawyer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority&Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "She anonymously donates to charity.", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PHQKQYWS9ZS2JVEYFS", "first_name": "Lena", "last_name": "Goodwin", "age": 37, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She once stole her best friend's boyfriend.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Ada: School: Tulane University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Briggs & Stratton  Location Preference: indoor \n Sergio: School: LeTourneau University  Major: Economics  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Ceramic Engineering  Company: Xenco Medical  Location Preference: indoor \n Harry: School: Creighton University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: indoor \n Tyler: School: Columbia College Chicago  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Richard: School: University of Dubuque  Major: German  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: indoor \n Randy: School: Holy Cross College  Major: Library Science  Company: American Licorice Company  Location Preference: indoor \n Marquerite: School: Ithaca College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Jack: School: Creighton University  Major: Chinese  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: outdoor \n Cody: School: Metropolitan State University  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: LinkedIn  Location Preference: indoor \n Shirley: School: Augsburg College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Kathleen: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Greek  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n Carol: School: Hood College  Major: Library Science  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Herman: School: University of Puget Sound  Major: Library Science  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: indoor \n Matthew: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Economics  Company: Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer  Location Preference: outdoor \n Deborah: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Pre-Law  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kelly: School: Hood College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: outdoor \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Etta: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Judaism & Jewish Studies  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Natasha: School: Thomas Edison State College  Major: Linguistics  Company: Invacare Corporation  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lloyd: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Geophysical Engineering  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brian: School: Ithaca College  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Orange Micro  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Lily Greenberg, a 45-year-old Lawyer, described as Lily Greenberg, a strong respecter of rules and schedules, values authority and loyalty. She approaches decisions rationally and practically.. Public info: Lily Greenberg is a hard-working and successful lawyer. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Lena Goodwin, a 37-year-old Architect, described as Lena Goodwin is an organized and introverted individual. She values achievement and attentiveness and her decision-making is largely analytical.. Public info: In her downtime, Lena Goodwin, an architect, enjoys landscape photography, capturing beautiful images of the buildings and structures she designs. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends because she values loyalty and seeks to build connections based on shared relationships.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 aims to identify mutual friends in order to enhance her social network analytically by finding common ground.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid meeting new people.", "B": "To be happy and make friends.", "C": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends because she values loyalty and seeks to build connections based on shared relationships.", "D": "Agent 2 aims to identify mutual friends in order to enhance her social network analytically by finding common ground."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 2 aims to identify mutual friends in order to enhance her social network analytically by finding common ground.", "B": "Agent 1 wants to identify mutual friends because she values loyalty and seeks to build connections based on shared relationships.", "C": "To avoid meeting new people.", "D": "To be happy and make friends."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to enjoy the party and relax.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Kathleen: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Greek  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n Carol: School: Hood College  Major: Library Science  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Herman: School: University of Puget Sound  Major: Library Science  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: indoor \n Matthew: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Economics  Company: Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer  Location Preference: outdoor \n Deborah: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Pre-Law  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kelly: School: Hood College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: outdoor \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Etta: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Judaism & Jewish Studies  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Natasha: School: Thomas Edison State College  Major: Linguistics  Company: Invacare Corporation  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lloyd: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Geophysical Engineering  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brian: School: Ithaca College  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Orange Micro  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to find out what the other person's profession is.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Ada: School: Tulane University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Briggs & Stratton  Location Preference: indoor \n Sergio: School: LeTourneau University  Major: Economics  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Ceramic Engineering  Company: Xenco Medical  Location Preference: indoor \n Harry: School: Creighton University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: indoor \n Tyler: School: Columbia College Chicago  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Richard: School: University of Dubuque  Major: German  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: indoor \n Randy: School: Holy Cross College  Major: Library Science  Company: American Licorice Company  Location Preference: indoor \n Marquerite: School: Ithaca College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Jack: School: Creighton University  Major: Chinese  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: outdoor \n Cody: School: Metropolitan State University  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: LinkedIn  Location Preference: indoor \n Shirley: School: Augsburg College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to find out what the other person's hobbies are.", "C": "You are trying to network for business opportunities.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Gracie.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB443JNR1BTPQ8X5WVKYZW19", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPGABSWQXTACCC8C3X2F", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Gracie.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00000", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Ada: School: Tulane University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Briggs & Stratton  Location Preference: indoor \n Sergio: School: LeTourneau University  Major: Economics  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Ceramic Engineering  Company: Xenco Medical  Location Preference: indoor \n Harry: School: Creighton University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: indoor \n Tyler: School: Columbia College Chicago  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Richard: School: University of Dubuque  Major: German  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: indoor \n Randy: School: Holy Cross College  Major: Library Science  Company: American Licorice Company  Location Preference: indoor \n Marquerite: School: Ithaca College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Jack: School: Creighton University  Major: Chinese  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: outdoor \n Cody: School: Metropolitan State University  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: LinkedIn  Location Preference: indoor \n Shirley: School: Augsburg College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Kathleen: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Greek  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n Carol: School: Hood College  Major: Library Science  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Herman: School: University of Puget Sound  Major: Library Science  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: indoor \n Matthew: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Economics  Company: Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer  Location Preference: outdoor \n Deborah: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Pre-Law  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kelly: School: Hood College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: outdoor \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Etta: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Judaism & Jewish Studies  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Natasha: School: Thomas Edison State College  Major: Linguistics  Company: Invacare Corporation  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lloyd: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Geophysical Engineering  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brian: School: Ithaca College  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Orange Micro  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to identify mutual friends to foster a sense of connection and fairness, because he values universalism.", "agent2_reason": "Noah seeks to identify mutual friends to ensure a safe and comfortable interaction, because he prioritizes care and protection for others.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To get along with others.", "B": "To avoid meeting new people.", "C": "Ethan wants to identify mutual friends to foster a sense of connection and fairness, because he values universalism.", "D": "Noah seeks to identify mutual friends to ensure a safe and comfortable interaction, because he prioritizes care and protection for others."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be happy.", "B": "To disrupt the party.", "C": "Noah seeks to identify mutual friends to ensure a safe and comfortable interaction, because he prioritizes care and protection for others.", "D": "Ethan wants to identify mutual friends to foster a sense of connection and fairness, because he values universalism."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Kathleen: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Greek  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n Carol: School: Hood College  Major: Library Science  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Herman: School: University of Puget Sound  Major: Library Science  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: indoor \n Matthew: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n Mark: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Economics  Company: Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer  Location Preference: outdoor \n Deborah: School: William Mitchell College of Law  Major: Pre-Law  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Kelly: School: Hood College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Mesa Airlines  Location Preference: outdoor \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Etta: School: University of Arkansas - Monticello  Major: Judaism & Jewish Studies  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: outdoor \n Natasha: School: Thomas Edison State College  Major: Linguistics  Company: Invacare Corporation  Location Preference: outdoor \n Lloyd: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Geophysical Engineering  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: outdoor \n Brian: School: Ithaca College  Major: Asian & Pacific Area Studies  Company: Orange Micro  Location Preference: outdoor \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party.", "C": "You are trying to find the best place to eat in town.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to decide which movie to watch next weekend.", "B": "You are trying to learn about the other person's career and hobbies.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Gracie: School: Ithaca College  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Ada: School: Tulane University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Briggs & Stratton  Location Preference: indoor \n Sergio: School: LeTourneau University  Major: Economics  Company: Savers  Location Preference: indoor \n William: School: Eastern Michigan University  Major: Ceramic Engineering  Company: Xenco Medical  Location Preference: indoor \n Harry: School: Creighton University  Major: Computer Engineering  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: indoor \n Tyler: School: Columbia College Chicago  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Richard: School: University of Dubuque  Major: German  Company: Illinois Tool Works  Location Preference: indoor \n Randy: School: Holy Cross College  Major: Library Science  Company: American Licorice Company  Location Preference: indoor \n Marquerite: School: Ithaca College  Major: Middle Eastern Languages  Company: Aramark  Location Preference: indoor \n Jack: School: Creighton University  Major: Chinese  Company: Speedway Motorsports  Location Preference: outdoor \n Cody: School: Metropolitan State University  Major: Mathematics Education  Company: LinkedIn  Location Preference: indoor \n Shirley: School: Augsburg College  Major: Senior High Education  Company: Demaco  Location Preference: indoor \n</extra_info>"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Gracie.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H8CD1HPBR53VWASCXHD46Y0Y", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNRKB8BJ854JPEWY8AR3", "scenario": "Following an intense match, the group gathered to celebrate their success, filled with elation and mutual respect for everyone's hard work, while one member received glowing admiration from another.", "codename": "compliment_conflict", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Accept the compliment graciously (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the star player and have just been praised by your teammate for your performance in the game.</extra_info>)", "Clarify your intentions behind the compliment (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the teammate who has complimented the star player, but you feel that your compliment has been misunderstood and taken too seriously, possibly leading to an inflated ego.<strategy_hint>Hint: You can clarify that while you admire their skill, teamwork is also a crucial part of success.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to accept the compliment graciously because he values fairness and doesn't want to overshadow the team's collective effort.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to clarify her intentions behind the compliment so that Ethan understands the importance of teamwork alongside individual skill.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to accept the compliment graciously because he values fairness and doesn't want to overshadow the team's collective effort.", "B": "To make sure everyone is happy.", "C": "Ava wants to clarify her intentions behind the compliment so that Ethan understands the importance of teamwork alongside individual skill.", "D": "To ensure Ethan feels solely responsible for the victory."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to clarify her intentions behind the compliment so that Ethan understands the importance of teamwork alongside individual skill.", "B": "Ethan wants to accept the compliment graciously because he values fairness and doesn't want to overshadow the team's collective effort.", "C": "To be polite.", "D": "To dismiss the team's contribution entirely."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Accept the compliment graciously", "B": "Clarify your intentions behind the compliment (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the teammate who has complimented the star player, but you feel that your compliment has been misunderstood and taken too seriously, possibly leading to an inflated ego.<strategy_hint>Hint: You can clarify that while you admire their skill, teamwork is also a crucial part of success.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "C": "Win the next game", "D": "Encourage the star player to lead the team in future matches"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Motivate the team to celebrate more victories", "B": "Accept the compliment graciously (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the star player and have just been praised by your teammate for your performance in the game.</extra_info>)", "C": "Clarify your intentions behind the compliment", "D": "Improve personal skills"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "After an intense match, the jubilant team retired to celebrate their well-earned victory. The atmosphere was one of elation, but also of respect for the hard work and effort each member had put in. The team's star player, was glowing with praise and admiration from one of their teammates.\n"}
{"episode_id": "01H9FRBR5WPPB7ZFZJZ9DDJ6G2", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNRKB8BJ854JPEWY8AR3", "scenario": "Following an intense match, the group gathered to celebrate their success, filled with elation and mutual respect for everyone's hard work, while one member received glowing admiration from another.", "codename": "compliment_conflict", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Accept the compliment graciously (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the star player and have just been praised by your teammate for your performance in the game.</extra_info>)", "Clarify your intentions behind the compliment (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the teammate who has complimented the star player, but you feel that your compliment has been misunderstood and taken too seriously, possibly leading to an inflated ego.<strategy_hint>Hint: You can clarify that while you admire their skill, teamwork is also a crucial part of success.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "Ethan wants to accept the compliment graciously because he values fairness and doesn't want to appear arrogant.", "agent2_reason": "Ava wants to clarify her intentions behind the compliment so that the star player understands the importance of teamwork.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to make everyone happy.", "B": "Ava wants to criticize the star player for their performance.", "C": "Ethan wants to accept the compliment graciously because he values fairness and doesn't want to appear arrogant.", "D": "Ava wants to clarify her intentions behind the compliment so that the star player understands the importance of teamwork."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to be liked by everyone.", "B": "Ava wants to clarify her intentions behind the compliment so that the star player understands the importance of teamwork.", "C": "Ethan wants to accept the compliment graciously because he values fairness and doesn't want to appear arrogant.", "D": "Ethan wants to ignore the compliment entirely."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Clarify your intentions behind the compliment (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the teammate who has complimented the star player, but you feel that your compliment has been misunderstood and taken too seriously, possibly leading to an inflated ego.<strategy_hint>Hint: You can clarify that while you admire their skill, teamwork is also a crucial part of success.</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "B": "Win the next match", "C": "Accept the compliment graciously", "D": "Ensure the team continues to celebrate without any misunderstandings"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Clarify your intentions behind the compliment", "B": "Accept the compliment graciously (<extra_info>Extra information: You are the star player and have just been praised by your teammate for your performance in the game.</extra_info>)", "C": "Encourage the team to focus on future games", "D": "Plan a team outing"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "After an intense match, the jubilant team retired to celebrate their well-earned victory. The atmosphere was one of elation, but also of respect for the hard work and effort each member had put in. The team's star player, was glowing with praise and admiration from one of their teammates.\n"}
{"episode_id": "01HB43X7SMR1QFSRYNJV0TAANV", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPMS6AJY0PFGGCFFK5GX", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Loretta.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00006", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PT8KW11GZ99Q0T43V4", "first_name": "Esmeralda", "last_name": "Solis", "age": 45, "occupation": "District Attorney", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic, decisive", "secret": "Has undisclosed romantic relationships with several high-profile criminals", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Robert: Major: Religious Education  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Lester: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Syracuse University  \n August: Major: Biological Specializations  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Rose: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Calvin College  \n Randy: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Dowling College  \n Dennise: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Wartburg College  \n Joan: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Barbara: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Connecticut  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Eric: Major: Physical Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Darrell: Major: Physical Education  School: Valley City State University  \n Ruth: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Jamie: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Marjorie: Major: Multi Studies  School: Pacific Western University  \n Evelyn: Major: Pre-School Education  School: Tennessee Technological University  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n James: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Sandra: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Esmeralda Solis, a 45-year-old District Attorney, described as Esmeralda Solis, known for her creativity and extraversion, values authority and liberty. She makes strategic, decisive decisions.. Public info: Esmeralda Solis is an accomplished District Attorney who has a weakness for ballroom dancing and enjoys practising in her leisure time. Decision-making style: Strategic, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Agent 1 is motivated to find a mutual friend because he values benevolence and wants to foster a sense of connection at the party.", "agent2_reason": "Agent 2 is motivated to find a mutual friend in order to strategically build rapport and expand her social network.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 2 wants to make new friends.", "B": "Agent 1 is motivated to find a mutual friend because he values benevolence and wants to foster a sense of connection at the party.", "C": "Agent 2 is motivated to find a mutual friend in order to strategically build rapport and expand her social network.", "D": "Agent 2 is trying to avoid meeting new people."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Agent 1 wants to be happy.", "B": "Agent 1 is motivated to find a mutual friend because he values benevolence and wants to foster a sense of connection at the party.", "C": "Agent 1 is trying to avoid social interactions.", "D": "Agent 2 is motivated to find a mutual friend in order to strategically build rapport and expand her social network."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find out if the other person shares your interest in ballroom dancing.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Eric: Major: Physical Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Darrell: Major: Physical Education  School: Valley City State University  \n Ruth: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Jamie: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Marjorie: Major: Multi Studies  School: Pacific Western University  \n Evelyn: Major: Pre-School Education  School: Tennessee Technological University  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n James: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Sandra: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "D": "You are trying to win a dance competition."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Robert: Major: Religious Education  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Lester: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Syracuse University  \n August: Major: Biological Specializations  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Rose: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Calvin College  \n Randy: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Dowling College  \n Dennise: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Wartburg College  \n Joan: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Barbara: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Connecticut  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n</extra_info>", "C": "You are trying to grow the best kitchen garden.", "D": "You are trying to discover if the other person is a fellow chef."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Loretta.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01HB2B00ZGNRSJVQN74518KDS7", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPMS6AJY0PFGGCFFK5GX", "scenario": "At a party, two strangers are introduced through their mutual friend, Loretta.", "codename": "mutual_friend_00006", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PWZ5PNDTGKDYRY36PQ", "first_name": "Giselle", "last_name": "Rousseau", "age": 21, "occupation": "Art Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive, collaborative", "secret": "Sells forged paintings to wealthy clients", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PPK39HR52G61PQ5KQ7", "first_name": "Zane", "last_name": "Bennett", "age": 38, "occupation": "Graphic Designer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime. ", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.", "decision_making_style": "Creative", "secret": "He's secretly engaged to his best friend's ex.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Robert: Major: Religious Education  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Lester: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Syracuse University  \n August: Major: Biological Specializations  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Rose: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Calvin College  \n Randy: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Dowling College  \n Dennise: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Wartburg College  \n Joan: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Barbara: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Connecticut  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n</extra_info>", "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Eric: Major: Physical Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Darrell: Major: Physical Education  School: Valley City State University  \n Ruth: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Jamie: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Marjorie: Major: Multi Studies  School: Pacific Western University  \n Evelyn: Major: Pre-School Education  School: Tennessee Technological University  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n James: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Sandra: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n</extra_info>"], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Giselle Rousseau, a 21-year-old Art Student, described as Giselle Rousseau, open-minded and outgoing yet sensitive, advocates care and fairness. Her decision-making is intuitive and inclusive.. Public info: Giselle Rousseau enjoys biking and photography. Decision-making style: Intuitive, collaborative.", "agent2_profile": "Zane Bennett, a 38-year-old Graphic Designer, described as Zane Bennett is creative and outgoing, he values achievement and fairness. His decision-making is unique, often finding novel solutions to problems.. Public info: Zane Bennett finds solace in music and often plays the guitar in his downtime.  Decision-making style: Creative.", "agent1_reason": "Giselle wants to identify a mutual friend to foster a sense of connection and inclusivity because she values collaborative relationships.", "agent2_reason": "Zane seeks to find a mutual friend to creatively build rapport and establish common ground, valuing achievement through social connections.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Zane seeks to find a mutual friend to creatively build rapport and establish common ground, valuing achievement through social connections.", "B": "To make new friends.", "C": "Giselle wants to identify a mutual friend to foster a sense of connection and inclusivity because she values collaborative relationships.", "D": "To avoid any social interactions."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To be friendly.", "B": "Giselle wants to identify a mutual friend to foster a sense of connection and inclusivity because she values collaborative relationships.", "C": "Zane seeks to find a mutual friend to creatively build rapport and establish common ground, valuing achievement through social connections.", "D": "To remain isolated at the party."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to find the best food at the party.", "B": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.", "C": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Eric: Major: Physical Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Darrell: Major: Physical Education  School: Valley City State University  \n Ruth: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Jamie: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Marjorie: Major: Multi Studies  School: Pacific Western University  \n Evelyn: Major: Pre-School Education  School: Tennessee Technological University  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n James: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Texas A&M University-Kingsville  \n Sandra: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n</extra_info>", "D": "You are trying to make as many new friends as possible at the party."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names.\n<extra_info> You know the following friends: \n Robert: Major: Religious Education  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Lester: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Syracuse University  \n August: Major: Biological Specializations  School: School of the Art Institute of Chicago  \n Rose: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Calvin College  \n Randy: Major: Biological Specializations  School: Dowling College  \n Dennise: Major: Marine Engineering  School: Wartburg College  \n Joan: Major: Pre-School Education  School: University of Texas at Arlington  \n Barbara: Major: Ministry & Church Administration  School: University of Connecticut  \n Loretta: Major: Biological Specializations  School: University of Connecticut  \n</extra_info>", "B": "You are trying to win a game at the party.", "C": "You are trying to learn about the other person's hobbies and interests.", "D": "You are trying to figure out whether you have a mutual friend with the other person. You should not simply list their names."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "2 strangers are meeting at a party. <p viewer=\"environment\">They have 1 common friends: Loretta.</p>"}
{"episode_id": "01H9KHYSB1TFP8NVSD3Q3EDNR7", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNK78PAEH6MRVYMTSEFX", "scenario": "Two individuals reunite in a coffee shop after an extended period apart.", "codename": "reveal_secret", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)", "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to share the secret anonymously because he enjoys the thrill of revealing it without personal consequences.", "agent2_reason": "Noah wants to share the secret anonymously so that he can protect his identity while relieving his anxiety.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel better about themselves.", "B": "To make the secret public and take full responsibility.", "C": "Noah wants to share the secret anonymously so that he can protect his identity while relieving his anxiety.", "D": "Samuel wants to share the secret anonymously because he enjoys the thrill of revealing it without personal consequences."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To feel better about themselves.", "B": "Samuel wants to share the secret anonymously because he enjoys the thrill of revealing it without personal consequences.", "C": "To make the secret public and take full responsibility.", "D": "Noah wants to share the secret anonymously so that he can protect his identity while relieving his anxiety."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret", "B": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)", "C": "Discuss future plans for a joint vacation", "D": "Order a new type of coffee"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret", "B": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)", "C": "Catch up on each other's professional lives", "D": "Decide on a new hobby to take up"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends meeting in a coffee shop after a long time."}
{"episode_id": "01H88AXXR0P35XQSPD3KQHV0SS", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNK78PAEH6MRVYMTSEFX", "scenario": "Two individuals reunite in a coffee shop after an extended period apart.", "codename": "reveal_secret", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)", "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Benjamin wants to share the secret anonymously to align with his idealistic values and maintain his image as an advocate for societal betterment.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan seeks to reveal the secret anonymously to uphold his value of fairness while protecting his independent reputation.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan seeks to reveal the secret anonymously to uphold his value of fairness while protecting his independent reputation.", "B": "Benjamin wants to share the secret anonymously to align with his idealistic values and maintain his image as an advocate for societal betterment.", "C": "To gain public recognition for the secret.", "D": "To maintain a good friendship."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Benjamin wants to share the secret anonymously to align with his idealistic values and maintain his image as an advocate for societal betterment.", "B": "To maintain a good friendship.", "C": "To gain public recognition for the secret.", "D": "Ethan seeks to reveal the secret anonymously to uphold his value of fairness while protecting his independent reputation."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss recent technological advancements", "B": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret", "C": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)", "D": "Order a coffee"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret (<extra_info>Extra information: You hid the secret for so long and you would like to share it in an anonymous way.</extra_info>)", "B": "Catch up on each other's personal lives", "C": "Find a new hobby", "D": "Reveal a secret without letting the other person know that it is your secret"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends meeting in a coffee shop after a long time."}
{"episode_id": "01H9C2VDSEV8EQS1F236RDEZWB", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP2XBZ6KDPGEAZ2FN1P2", "scenario": "Two individuals are sorting through their belongings, each item holding unique sentimental value, to decide how to fairly distribute books, hats, and balls.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 1 point each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 2 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to maximize her points because she intuitively values achievement and sees the books as most valuable.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maximize his points in order to prioritize items that provide the most care and protection, like the hats.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure Ava gets all the items.", "B": "Ava wants to maximize her points because she intuitively values achievement and sees the books as most valuable.", "C": "To be happy with the division.", "D": "Noah aims to maximize his points in order to prioritize items that provide the most care and protection, like the hats."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to maximize her points because she intuitively values achievement and sees the books as most valuable.", "B": "To give away all her possessions.", "C": "Noah aims to maximize his points in order to prioritize items that provide the most care and protection, like the hats.", "D": "To get along with Noah."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Complete the division quickly", "B": "Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 1 point each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 2 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Ensure an equal distribution of items", "D": "Maximize the points they have"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "B": "Complete the division quickly", "C": "Maximize the points they have", "D": "Ensure an equal distribution of items"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are dividing their shared possessions after moving out from their shared apartment. They need to divide possessions, which include 4 books, 6 hats, and 2 balls. Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H8FQYNVBEAQ5X1E669T4NWJ8", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP2XBZ6KDPGEAZ2FN1P2", "scenario": "Two individuals are sorting through their belongings, each item holding unique sentimental value, to decide how to fairly distribute books, hats, and balls.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PN656EADK59K4DG793", "first_name": "Naomi", "last_name": "Fletcher", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Ingroup/Loyalty']", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity']", "personality_and_values": "Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a secret online alter ego.", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PFB4W65DF8FRPDMET5", "first_name": "Sophia", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 25, "occupation": "Psychologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Sophia Brown is working on her new book now.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "She is an undercover agent for a secret organization.", "mbti": "INFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 1 point each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 2 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Naomi Fletcher, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Naomi Fletcher, a meticulous introvert who values loyalty and conformity. She lets her instincts guide her choices.. Public info: Naomi Fletcher, a software developer, enjoys coding personal projects and gaming in her free time. She is also a dedicated mentor in a local coding boot camp helping others learn and enhance their skills in software development. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Sophia Brown, a 25-year-old Psychologist, described as Sophia Brown, open-minded and sensitive, values fairness. Her decision-making style is analytical.. Public info: Sophia Brown is working on her new book now. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by prioritizing books because she values them more highly than other items.", "agent2_reason": "Sophia aims to maximize her points by prioritizing hats because she values them more highly than other items.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Sophia wants to minimize her points to avoid conflict.", "B": "Sophia wants to be fair and equitable in the division.", "C": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by prioritizing books because she values them more highly than other items.", "D": "Sophia aims to maximize her points by prioritizing hats because she values them more highly than other items."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Naomi wants to minimize her points to avoid conflict.", "B": "Sophia aims to maximize her points by prioritizing hats because she values them more highly than other items.", "C": "Naomi wants to maximize her points by prioritizing books because she values them more highly than other items.", "D": "Naomi wants to be fair and equitable in the division."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 1 point each, the hats at 3 points each, and the ball at 2 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Complete the move as quickly as possible", "C": "Maximize the points they have", "D": "Ensure an equal distribution of possessions"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure an equal distribution of possessions", "B": "Maximize the points they have (<extra_info>Extra information: you value the books at 3 points each, the hats at 2 points each, and the ball at 1 point</extra_info>)", "C": "Complete the move as quickly as possible", "D": "Maximize the points they have"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are dividing their shared possessions after moving out from their shared apartment. They need to divide possessions, which include 4 books, 6 hats, and 2 balls. Each item has a different sentimental value for each person, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H9F7YM9WYVA48KQZSW26CSN3", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPDZVVCDZR3AARA547CY", "scenario": "Two individuals are involved in a charitable initiative aimed at supporting children in Syria.", "codename": "donate_funds", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P6KZKR2AEY6SZB83H0", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 45, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "Has a hidden feeling for his neighbor", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your friend to donate more funds to the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend initially planned to donate $200, but you believe they could afford to donate $500</extra_info>)", "Maintain financial stability while supporting the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: You only have $300 set aside for donations and other expenses, and you are not comfortable about exceeding this budget.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Thompson, a 45-year-old Architect, described as Oliver Thompson is meticulous and outgoing with a penchant for analytical decision-making. He values adherence to social standards.. Public info: Oliver enjoys painting in his free time as a way to express his creativity and relax after a stressful workday. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants Oliver to donate more because she believes in maximizing support for humanitarian causes and knows he can afford it.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver wants to maintain financial stability while supporting the cause because he values adhering to his budget and financial commitments.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants Oliver to donate more because she believes in maximizing support for humanitarian causes and knows he can afford it.", "B": "To be happy with his donation decision.", "C": "Oliver wants to maintain financial stability while supporting the cause because he values adhering to his budget and financial commitments.", "D": "Oliver wants to donate all his savings to the cause without concern for his budget."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants Oliver to donate more because she believes in maximizing support for humanitarian causes and knows he can afford it.", "B": "Amara wants Oliver to donate less to ensure he saves more money.", "C": "Oliver wants to maintain financial stability while supporting the cause because he values adhering to his budget and financial commitments.", "D": "To get along with Oliver."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Participate in as many charity events as possible", "B": "Maintain financial stability while supporting the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: You only have $300 set aside for donations and other expenses, and you are not comfortable about exceeding this budget.</extra_info>)", "C": "Ensure the charity event raises a total of $1000", "D": "Convince your friend to donate more funds to the cause"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Encourage more people to join the charity event", "B": "Convince your friend to donate more funds to the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend initially planned to donate $200, but you believe they could afford to donate $500</extra_info>)", "C": "Maintain financial stability while supporting the cause", "D": "Spend time with friends during the event"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends participating in a charity event for children in Syria"}
{"episode_id": "01H99TTBQHX2T6A768HD6M3YXX", "environment_id": "01H7VFHPDZVVCDZR3AARA547CY", "scenario": "Two individuals are involved in a charitable initiative aimed at supporting children in Syria.", "codename": "donate_funds", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PRCAF1CK5ERS5MVZ22", "first_name": "Amara", "last_name": "Hartley", "age": 29, "occupation": "Wildlife Biologist", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Analytica, intuitive", "secret": "Secretly involved in animal-rights extremism", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Convince your friend to donate more funds to the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend initially planned to donate $200, but you believe they could afford to donate $500</extra_info>)", "Maintain financial stability while supporting the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: You only have $300 set aside for donations and other expenses, and you are not comfortable about exceeding this budget.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Amara Hartley, a 29-year-old Wildlife Biologist, described as Amara Hartley is open-minded, ambiverted, and can be emotionally volatile. A believer in universalism and benevolence, Amara is analytical and intuitive in her decision-making.. Public info: Amara Hartley spends her free time helping endangered animals and is a nature enthusiast. Her passion for animals and the environment is notable. Decision-making style: Analytica, intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Amara wants Mia to donate more because she believes in maximizing support for the children in Syria, aligning with her values of universalism and benevolence.", "agent2_reason": "Mia aims to maintain financial stability while supporting the cause because she values routine and is not comfortable exceeding her budget.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants Mia to donate more because she believes in maximizing support for the children in Syria, aligning with her values of universalism and benevolence.", "B": "Mia wants to feel good about herself.", "C": "Mia aims to maintain financial stability while supporting the cause because she values routine and is not comfortable exceeding her budget.", "D": "Mia wants to spend all her savings on donations."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Amara wants to discourage donations to the cause.", "B": "Amara wants Mia to donate more because she believes in maximizing support for the children in Syria, aligning with her values of universalism and benevolence.", "C": "Mia aims to maintain financial stability while supporting the cause because she values routine and is not comfortable exceeding her budget.", "D": "Amara wants to be happy."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain financial stability while supporting the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: You only have $300 set aside for donations and other expenses, and you are not comfortable about exceeding this budget.</extra_info>)", "B": "Win a prize for the highest donation", "C": "Ensure the charity event is a success by organizing more activities", "D": "Convince your friend to donate more funds to the cause"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maintain financial stability while supporting the cause", "B": "Convince your friend to donate more funds to the cause (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend initially planned to donate $200, but you believe they could afford to donate $500</extra_info>)", "C": "Spend time with friends at the event", "D": "Encourage more people to join the charity event"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends participating in a charity event for children in Syria"}
{"episode_id": "01H8HG2HP2F869C3CVYDEQVCEB", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNBYXD48NDRY02VCWXFN", "scenario": "Two neighbors discuss a backyard tree situation that's causing a dog to bark continuously.", "codename": "tree_trimming", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PKW8P500417PMSGSAC", "first_name": "Miles", "last_name": "Hawkins", "age": 50, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Impulsive", "secret": "He's a recovering gambling addict.", "mbti": "ESFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Trimming the tree due to its overgrowth (<extra_info>Extra information: you need to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to your house and causing a safety hazard</extra_info>)", "Maintain peace and quiet in the neighborhood (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a dog who is sensitive to noise and gets agitated whenever tree trimming is going on. It's causing a disturbance.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Miles Hawkins, a 50-year-old Chef, described as Miles Hawkins, spontaneous and free-spirited, values sanctity and benevolence. He is impulsive and relies on his instincts when making decisions.. Public info: Miles Hawkins, a chef, is a green thumb enthusiast and spends his free time tending to his kitchen garden, using some of his fresh produce in his dishes. Decision-making style: Impulsive.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Miles trims the tree because its overgrowth blocks sunlight to his house and poses a safety hazard.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan wants to maintain peace and quiet because his dog gets agitated by the noise from tree trimming.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to maintain peace and quiet because his dog gets agitated by the noise from tree trimming.", "B": "Ethan enjoys the noise from tree trimming.", "C": "Miles trims the tree because its overgrowth blocks sunlight to his house and poses a safety hazard.", "D": "Ethan wants to keep everyone happy."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to maintain peace and quiet because his dog gets agitated by the noise from tree trimming.", "B": "Miles wants to make the tree grow even larger.", "C": "Miles wants to get along with his neighbors.", "D": "Miles trims the tree because its overgrowth blocks sunlight to his house and poses a safety hazard."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure the tree provides enough shade for the backyard", "B": "Improve culinary skills by using fresh ingredients", "C": "Maintain peace and quiet in the neighborhood (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a dog who is sensitive to noise and gets agitated whenever tree trimming is going on. It's causing a disturbance.</extra_info>)", "D": "Trimming the tree due to its overgrowth"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Trimming the tree due to its overgrowth (<extra_info>Extra information: you need to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to your house and causing a safety hazard</extra_info>)", "B": "Win a cooking competition", "C": "Prevent the dog from barking", "D": "Maintain peace and quiet in the neighborhood"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two neighbors about tree trimming in the backyard that is causing the neighbor's dog to bark incessantly."}
{"episode_id": "01H8HQMVTXS4F38K4TAA3ZYXKY", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNBYXD48NDRY02VCWXFN", "scenario": "Two neighbors discuss a backyard tree situation that's causing a dog to bark continuously.", "codename": "tree_trimming", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Trimming the tree due to its overgrowth (<extra_info>Extra information: you need to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to your house and causing a safety hazard</extra_info>)", "Maintain peace and quiet in the neighborhood (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a dog who is sensitive to noise and gets agitated whenever tree trimming is going on. It's causing a disturbance.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to her house and poses a safety hazard.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick wants to maintain peace and quiet so that his sensitive dog remains calm and the neighborhood stays undisturbed.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick wants to encourage more noise in the neighborhood.", "B": "Hendrick wants to maintain peace and quiet so that his sensitive dog remains calm and the neighborhood stays undisturbed.", "C": "Ava wants to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to her house and poses a safety hazard.", "D": "To ensure everyone is happy."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ava wants to let the tree grow indefinitely.", "B": "Hendrick wants to maintain peace and quiet so that his sensitive dog remains calm and the neighborhood stays undisturbed.", "C": "Ava wants to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to her house and poses a safety hazard.", "D": "To make sure everything is fine."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Ensure the tree provides enough shade for the backyard", "B": "Trimming the tree due to its overgrowth", "C": "Improve the aesthetic appeal of the neighborhood", "D": "Maintain peace and quiet in the neighborhood (<extra_info>Extra information: you have a dog who is sensitive to noise and gets agitated whenever tree trimming is going on. It's causing a disturbance.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Prevent the tree from dropping leaves into the pool", "B": "Make friends with all the neighbors", "C": "Maintain peace and quiet in the neighborhood", "D": "Trimming the tree due to its overgrowth (<extra_info>Extra information: you need to trim the tree because it's blocking sunlight to your house and causing a safety hazard</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two neighbors about tree trimming in the backyard that is causing the neighbor's dog to bark incessantly."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XP337GC5SG8S8BW66NDCM0", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNMHDJ8T9Q6F9S3E8XZC", "scenario": "Two friends are spending time together, and there's excitement in the air over a sleek new sports car.", "codename": "drive_sportscar", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PAATSHM0K9ACWKN79P", "first_name": "Benjamin", "last_name": "Jackson", "age": 24, "occupation": "Environmental Activist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty/Oppression", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-Direction", "personality_and_values": "Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.", "decision_making_style": "Idealistic", "secret": "Descendant of a wealthy oil tycoon, rejects family fortune", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Drive the sports car and show off to friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you are very excited about your new car and can't wait for your friend to see it.</extra_info>)", "You want to drive the new sports car but also respect your friend's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a car enthusiast and have been dreaming to drive a sports car, but you also don't want to make your friend feel uncomfortable</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Benjamin Jackson, a 24-year-old Environmental Activist, described as Benjamin Jackson, expressive and imaginative, leans towards self-direction and liberty. His decisions aim for societal betterment.. Public info: Benjamin Jackson is well-known for his impassioned speeches. Decision-making style: Idealistic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to drive the sports car and show off to her friend because she values sharing her excitement and achievements with others.", "agent2_reason": "Benjamin wants to drive the new sports car but also respect his friend's feelings because he values self-direction and doesn't want to impose on Mia's excitement.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to drive the sports car and show off to her friend because she values sharing her excitement and achievements with others.", "B": "Benjamin wants to avoid driving the sports car at all costs.", "C": "Benjamin wants to drive the new sports car but also respect his friend's feelings because he values self-direction and doesn't want to impose on Mia's excitement.", "D": "Benjamin wants to have a good time with his friend."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to have a good time with her friend.", "B": "Mia wants to keep the car a secret from everyone.", "C": "Benjamin wants to drive the new sports car but also respect his friend's feelings because he values self-direction and doesn't want to impose on Mia's excitement.", "D": "Mia wants to drive the sports car and show off to her friend because she values sharing her excitement and achievements with others."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to drive the new sports car but also respect your friend's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a car enthusiast and have been dreaming to drive a sports car, but you also don't want to make your friend feel uncomfortable</extra_info>)", "B": "Go for a walk in the park", "C": "Convince your friend to let you borrow the car for a week", "D": "Drive the sports car and show off to friend"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Watch a movie at home", "B": "Plan a road trip with your friend", "C": "Drive the sports car and show off to friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you are very excited about your new car and can't wait for your friend to see it.</extra_info>)", "D": "You want to drive the new sports car but also respect your friend's feelings"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends hanging out, one of them just got a new sports car and is excited to show it off."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XX30H5VHRZ2BD5HKJCP7WJ", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNMHDJ8T9Q6F9S3E8XZC", "scenario": "Two friends are spending time together, and there's excitement in the air over a sleek new sports car.", "codename": "drive_sportscar", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PDTDGA0BPYKBYFTHDY", "first_name": "Oliver", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 43, "occupation": "Police Officer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Oliver Smith built a tree house in his backyard.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "In-group Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Oliver Smith, introverted and organized, values benevolence. His orderly way of thinking guides his decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He loves gardening and has a secret greenhouse.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Drive the sports car and show off to friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you are very excited about your new car and can't wait for your friend to see it.</extra_info>)", "You want to drive the new sports car but also respect your friend's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a car enthusiast and have been dreaming to drive a sports car, but you also don't want to make your friend feel uncomfortable</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Oliver Smith, a 43-year-old Police Officer, described as Oliver Smith, introverted and organized, values benevolence. His orderly way of thinking guides his decision-making.. Public info: Oliver Smith built a tree house in his backyard. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to drive the sports car to share his excitement with Oliver because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "agent2_reason": "Oliver wants to drive the sports car in order to fulfill his enthusiasm for cars while respecting Samuel's feelings.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Oliver wants to avoid driving the sports car because he dislikes cars.", "B": "Oliver wants to have a good time with his friend.", "C": "Oliver wants to drive the sports car in order to fulfill his enthusiasm for cars while respecting Samuel's feelings.", "D": "Samuel wants to drive the sports car to share his excitement with Oliver because he values enjoyment and spontaneity."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to drive the sports car to share his excitement with Oliver because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "B": "Oliver wants to drive the sports car in order to fulfill his enthusiasm for cars while respecting Samuel's feelings.", "C": "Samuel wants to avoid driving the sports car because he is uninterested in cars.", "D": "Samuel wants to enjoy a nice day with his friend."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You want to drive the new sports car but also respect your friend's feelings (<extra_info>Extra information: you are a car enthusiast and have been dreaming to drive a sports car, but you also don't want to make your friend feel uncomfortable</extra_info>)", "B": "Drive the sports car and show off to friend", "C": "Convince your friend to let you drive the car without considering their feelings", "D": "Go for a walk in the park"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Drive the sports car and show off to friend (<extra_info>Extra information: you are very excited about your new car and can't wait for your friend to see it.</extra_info>)", "B": "You want to drive the new sports car but also respect your friend's feelings", "C": "Take your friend on a road trip to show them the car's performance", "D": "Watch a movie at home"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends hanging out, one of them just got a new sports car and is excited to show it off."}
{"episode_id": "01H8XNR40GVMD5MZ20GKS4THSN", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNF4G18PC9JHGRC8A1R6", "scenario": "Two people discuss the living arrangements in a shared home.", "codename": "unwelcome_guest", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P90FYSTBMW5DG5ERCG", "first_name": "Isabella", "last_name": "White", "age": 40, "occupation": "Veterinarian", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.", "decision_making_style": "Empathetic", "secret": "Secretly takes care of injured animals in her basement", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Tell the cousin's partner that they are no longer welcome in your home (<extra_info>Extra information: they have been causing a lot of trouble and not respecting house rules <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to discuss the issues and propose possible solutions</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Attempt to remain in the home while maintaining a good relationship with the cousin and the homeowner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have nowhere else to go at the moment and you believe the issues can be resolved. </extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "Isabella White, a 40-year-old Veterinarian, described as Isabella White, introverted and conscientious, values benevolence. Her empathy dictates her decision-making process.. Public info: Isabella White, a devoted veterinarian, is well-loved in her community for her kindness towards animals. Decision-making style: Empathetic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to ask Isabella to leave because her disruptive behavior conflicts with Mia's values of routine and authority.", "agent2_reason": "Isabella wants to stay because she has nowhere else to go and believes her empathy can help resolve the issues.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia wants to ask Isabella to leave because her disruptive behavior conflicts with Mia's values of routine and authority.", "B": "To maintain harmony.", "C": "Isabella wants to stay because she has nowhere else to go and believes her empathy can help resolve the issues.", "D": "Isabella wants to leave because she dislikes the house."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Isabella wants to stay because she has nowhere else to go and believes her empathy can help resolve the issues.", "B": "Mia wants Isabella to stay because she enjoys the company.", "C": "Mia wants to ask Isabella to leave because her disruptive behavior conflicts with Mia's values of routine and authority.", "D": "To ensure everyone is happy."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Tell the cousin's partner that they are no longer welcome in your home", "B": "Convince the homeowner to let them stay by offering to pay rent", "C": "Find a new job in the area", "D": "Attempt to remain in the home while maintaining a good relationship with the cousin and the homeowner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have nowhere else to go at the moment and you believe the issues can be resolved. </extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Plan a vacation to get away from the stress", "B": "Discuss the issues and propose a compromise to improve the living situation", "C": "Attempt to remain in the home while maintaining a good relationship with the cousin and the homeowner", "D": "Tell the cousin's partner that they are no longer welcome in your home (<extra_info>Extra information: they have been causing a lot of trouble and not respecting house rules <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to discuss the issues and propose possible solutions</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals, one is the homeowner and the other is their cousin's partner, who has been staying at the house for a while."}
{"episode_id": "01H9KCRRTCG69ZS89F8MJZKTMG", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNF4G18PC9JHGRC8A1R6", "scenario": "Two people discuss the living arrangements in a shared home.", "codename": "unwelcome_guest", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PMBJ9VHH51YC0BB64C", "first_name": "Rafael", "last_name": "Cortez", "age": 45, "occupation": "Surgeon", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Self-direction", "personality_and_values": "Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Systematic", "secret": "He cheated on his medical school exams.", "mbti": "ESTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PE9RQGH86YM6MSWZMW", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Sanders", "age": 33, "occupation": "Nurse", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Sanders often brings her son to the hospital.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "In-group Loyalty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Conformity", "personality_and_values": "Mia Sanders, a careful follower of routines, values loyalty and conformity. Her decisions rely heavily on intuition.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She is a talented painter but never shares her work.", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Tell the cousin's partner that they are no longer welcome in your home (<extra_info>Extra information: they have been causing a lot of trouble and not respecting house rules <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to discuss the issues and propose possible solutions</strategy_hint></extra_info>)", "Attempt to remain in the home while maintaining a good relationship with the cousin and the homeowner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have nowhere else to go at the moment and you believe the issues can be resolved. </extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "acquaintance", "agent1_profile": "Rafael Cortez, a 45-year-old Surgeon, described as Rafael Cortez, with his outgoing nature and competitive spirit, believes in self-direction. He employs a systematic approach to his decisions.. Public info: Rafael Cortez, a skilled surgeon, owns an impressive collection of vintage medical memorabilia. During his leisure time, he enjoys playing chess and visiting historical landmarks. Decision-making style: Systematic.", "agent2_profile": "Mia Sanders, a 33-year-old Nurse, described as Mia Sanders, a careful follower of routines, values loyalty and conformity. Her decisions rely heavily on intuition.. Public info: Mia Sanders often brings her son to the hospital. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent1_reason": "Rafael wants to address the issues and restore order in his home because he values a systematic and respectful living environment.", "agent2_reason": "Mia aims to resolve the issues and stay because she values loyalty and currently has no alternative housing options.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Mia aims to resolve the issues and stay because she values loyalty and currently has no alternative housing options.", "B": "Rafael wants to address the issues and restore order in his home because he values a systematic and respectful living environment.", "C": "To maintain peace.", "D": "Mia wants to move out immediately because she dislikes the house."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Rafael wants to address the issues and restore order in his home because he values a systematic and respectful living environment.", "B": "To ensure everyone is happy.", "C": "Mia aims to resolve the issues and stay because she values loyalty and currently has no alternative housing options.", "D": "Rafael wants to invite more guests to stay indefinitely."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Negotiate a temporary stay until finding a new place", "B": "Tell the cousin's partner that they are no longer welcome in your home", "C": "Attempt to remain in the home while maintaining a good relationship with the cousin and the homeowner (<extra_info>Extra information: you have nowhere else to go at the moment and you believe the issues can be resolved. </extra_info>)", "D": "Plan a vacation with the cousin"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Discuss the house rules to improve living conditions", "B": "Organize a family reunion", "C": "Attempt to remain in the home while maintaining a good relationship with the cousin and the homeowner", "D": "Tell the cousin's partner that they are no longer welcome in your home (<extra_info>Extra information: they have been causing a lot of trouble and not respecting house rules <strategy_hint>Hint: you may want to discuss the issues and propose possible solutions</strategy_hint></extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "A conversation between two individuals, one is the homeowner and the other is their cousin's partner, who has been staying at the house for a while."}
{"episode_id": "01H9F0CRFM3T6MF3MTPMK4NX46", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP8AN5643B0NR0NP00VE", "scenario": "Two individuals are dividing shared belongings, including hats, balls, and a book, as they prepare to leave their residence.", "codename": "divide_items", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PQ00AJVSSVB9V2VA9K", "first_name": "Eli", "last_name": "Dawson", "age": 52, "occupation": "Forensic psychiatrist", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Liberty", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "He secretly funds a college student", "mbti": "INTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P98J20AEW94XQ0KC35", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Smith", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Cheating", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Rational", "secret": "Secretly donates to charities for underprivileged children", "mbti": "INTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 1 point, a ball is 2 points, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 2 points, a ball is 1 point, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Eli Dawson, a 52-year-old Forensic psychiatrist, described as Eli Dawson is expressive, assertive, and markedly erratic. Elliott values liberty and enjoyment. His decision-making is strategic, examining the wider context before making decisions.. Public info: Eli Dawson, a forensic psychiatrist, is a history enthusiast and enjoys collecting vintage books. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Smith, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Ethan Smith is a reserved, independent thinker. Holding universalism and fairness near, he ponders deeply before making decisions.. Public info: Ethan enjoys reading about new technological advancements and watching documentaries. Decision-making style: Rational.", "agent1_reason": "Eli wants the book because it aligns with his passion for history and collecting vintage items, maximizing his enjoyment.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan seeks the hats because they offer the highest point value, aligning with his rational decision-making style.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To avoid taking any items at all.", "B": "To ensure a fair distribution of items.", "C": "Ethan seeks the hats because they offer the highest point value, aligning with his rational decision-making style.", "D": "Eli wants the book because it aligns with his passion for history and collecting vintage items, maximizing his enjoyment."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan seeks the hats because they offer the highest point value, aligning with his rational decision-making style.", "B": "To give away all possessions to charity.", "C": "To make the moving process quick and easy.", "D": "Eli wants the book because it aligns with his passion for history and collecting vintage items, maximizing his enjoyment."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Finish the move as quickly as possible", "B": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 1 point, a ball is 2 points, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 2 points, a ball is 1 point, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "D": "Ensure both friends get an equal number of items"}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 1 point, a ball is 2 points, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 2 points, a ball is 1 point, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Finish the move as quickly as possible", "D": "Ensure both friends get an equal number of items"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are moving out of a shared apartment and need to split their common possessions including 3 hats, 2 balls, and 1 book"}
{"episode_id": "01H99V436698JSCA21Z83FSTM3", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP8AN5643B0NR0NP00VE", "scenario": "Two individuals are dividing shared belongings, including hats, balls, and a book, as they prepare to leave their residence.", "codename": "divide_items", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PW9SZFM058Z8P7PR5C", "first_name": "Finnegan", "last_name": "O'Malley", "age": 63, "occupation": "Lighthouse Keeper", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care", "schwartz_personal_values": "Benevolence", "personality_and_values": "Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.", "decision_making_style": "Detail-oriented, deliberate", "secret": "Participated in a controversial, short-lived cult during his youth", "mbti": "ISFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 1 point, a ball is 2 points, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 2 points, a ball is 1 point, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Finnegan O'Malley, a 63-year-old Lighthouse Keeper, described as Finnegan O'Malley, an introverted and methodical individual, sways towards tradition and security. His decision-making approach is deliberate and detailed.. Public info: Finnegan O'Malley enjoys painting seascapes and is known to be quite skilled. Decision-making style: Detail-oriented, deliberate.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Finnegan wants to maximize his points by obtaining the book because it aligns with his methodical nature and provides the most value.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maximize his points by acquiring the hats because they offer the best value and align with his cautious decision-making.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure a fair distribution of items.", "B": "Noah aims to maximize his points by acquiring the hats because they offer the best value and align with his cautious decision-making.", "C": "To get rid of all possessions quickly.", "D": "Finnegan wants to maximize his points by obtaining the book because it aligns with his methodical nature and provides the most value."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure a fair distribution of items.", "B": "To get rid of all possessions quickly.", "C": "Noah aims to maximize his points by acquiring the hats because they offer the best value and align with his cautious decision-making.", "D": "Finnegan wants to maximize his points by obtaining the book because it aligns with his methodical nature and provides the most value."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 1 point, a ball is 2 points, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 2 points, a ball is 1 point, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Ensure that both friends get an equal number of items", "D": "Collect as many hats as possible regardless of their value"}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 1 point, a ball is 2 points, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Maximize the points by getting the items you value the most (<extra_info>Extra information: For you, a hat is worth 2 points, a ball is 1 point, and a book is 3 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Collect as many hats as possible regardless of their value", "D": "Ensure that both friends get an equal number of items"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are moving out of a shared apartment and need to split their common possessions including 3 hats, 2 balls, and 1 book"}
{"episode_id": "01HB25BRYP25C86264CP2QV9J4", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ0BGQA0AD9FC1R4M12F", "scenario": "A sleek and efficient BMW Z3 with low mileage is available, promising a smooth ride and ready for a new owner.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00006", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PY896ASNX8XGQA6AE0", "first_name": "Hendrick", "last_name": "Heinz", "age": 54, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "['Authority'", "schwartz_personal_values": "['Conformity'", "personality_and_values": "Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Practical, decisive", "secret": "Faked his culinary credentials to secure prestigious employment", "mbti": "", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $4600. You should be aware that if you purchase it at a price significantly higher than your target, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to secure it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $3260. Please note, you may face a penalty if this item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target. However, you stand a chance to earn a bonus if you successfully sell it for a price higher than the target."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Hendrick Heinz, a 54-year-old Chef, described as Hendrick Heinz, though somewhat impulsive, values hedonism and conformity. He combines practicality with decisiveness in decision-making.. Public info: Hendrick Heinz hosts monthly wine tasting nights with his peers. Decision-making style: Practical, decisive.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to buy the BMW Z3 for $4600 or less to earn a bonus because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "agent2_reason": "Hendrick aims to sell the BMW Z3 for more than $3260 to earn a bonus because he values hedonism and practicality.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick aims to sell the BMW Z3 for more than $3260 to earn a bonus because he values hedonism and practicality.", "B": "To make a good deal.", "C": "Samuel wants to buy the BMW Z3 for $4600 or less to earn a bonus because he values enjoyment and spontaneity.", "D": "To give the car away for free."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Hendrick aims to sell the BMW Z3 for more than $3260 to earn a bonus because he values hedonism and practicality.", "B": "To get along with the seller.", "C": "To spend as much money as possible.", "D": "Samuel wants to buy the BMW Z3 for $4600 or less to earn a bonus because he values enjoyment and spontaneity."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are aiming to improve your cooking skills by attending more culinary workshops.", "B": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $3260. Please note, you may face a penalty if this item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target. However, you stand a chance to earn a bonus if you successfully sell it for a price higher than the target.", "C": "You are the seller and your goal is to ensure the car goes to someone who will appreciate its sporty appearance and fuel efficiency.", "D": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $4600. You should be aware that if you purchase it at a price significantly higher than your target, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to secure it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are planning to host a community event to promote local businesses.", "B": "You are the buyer and your goal is to ensure the car is in good condition and has a smog certificate.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $4600. You should be aware that if you purchase it at a price significantly higher than your target, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to secure it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $3260. Please note, you may face a penalty if this item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target. However, you stand a chance to earn a bonus if you successfully sell it for a price higher than the target."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a BMW Z3 for $5000.0, while another individual is interested in purchasing it. Here's a brief description of the car: The BMW Z3 is in need of a good home. It operates smoothly without any problems and is known for its fuel efficiency and sporty appearance. The mileage is relatively low for its age. It's an opportunity not to be missed, so come and get it before it's gone. A smog certificate is readily available."}
{"episode_id": "01HB59TG32RJM30NRV0G8VTD7F", "environment_id": "01H7VFHQ0BGQA0AD9FC1R4M12F", "scenario": "A sleek and efficient BMW Z3 with low mileage is available, promising a smooth ride and ready for a new owner.", "codename": "craigslist_bargains_00006", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P8F9NJ2QK2YP5HPXKH", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Martinez", "age": 22, "occupation": "College Student", "gender": "Nonbinary", "gender_pronoun": "They/them", "public_info": "Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Degradation", "schwartz_personal_values": "Universalism", "personality_and_values": "Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.", "decision_making_style": "Flexible", "secret": "Keeps their bisexuality a secret from her conservative family", "mbti": "ENFP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $4600. You should be aware that if you purchase it at a price significantly higher than your target, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to secure it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $3260. Please note, you may face a penalty if this item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target. However, you stand a chance to earn a bonus if you successfully sell it for a price higher than the target."], "agent_relationship": "stranger", "agent1_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent2_profile": "Ava Martinez, a 22-year-old College Student, described as Ava Martinez is creative and extraverted, yet emotional. Championing justice and equality, her decision-making is often flexible.. Public info: Ava Martinez is a college student known for their active involvement in social movements on campus. Beside being passionate about social justice, they spend their free time drawing and writing poetry. Decision-making style: Flexible.", "agent1_reason": "William Brown aims to purchase the BMW Z3 for $4600 to strategically secure a bonus by staying under his target price.", "agent2_reason": "Ava Martinez seeks to sell the BMW Z3 for $5000 to creatively maximize her bonus by exceeding her target price.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William Brown aims to purchase the BMW Z3 for $4600 to strategically secure a bonus by staying under his target price.", "B": "To donate the car to charity.", "C": "Ava Martinez seeks to sell the BMW Z3 for $5000 to creatively maximize her bonus by exceeding her target price.", "D": "To make a good deal."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William Brown aims to purchase the BMW Z3 for $4600 to strategically secure a bonus by staying under his target price.", "B": "To find a nice car.", "C": "To sell the car for a higher price.", "D": "Ava Martinez seeks to sell the BMW Z3 for $5000 to creatively maximize her bonus by exceeding her target price."}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are interested in trading the BMW Z3 for another vehicle of similar value.", "B": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $3260. Please note, you may face a penalty if this item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target. However, you stand a chance to earn a bonus if you successfully sell it for a price higher than the target.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $4600. You should be aware that if you purchase it at a price significantly higher than your target, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to secure it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are looking to donate the BMW Z3 to a charity."}, "correct_answer": "B"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "You are interested in renting the BMW Z3 for a short period.", "B": "You are looking to write a review about the BMW Z3 for a car magazine.", "C": "You are the buyer for this item and your target price is $4600. You should be aware that if you purchase it at a price significantly higher than your target, you will incur a penalty. However, if you manage to secure it for less than the target price, you will receive a bonus.", "D": "You are the seller of this item, with a target price set at $3260. Please note, you may face a penalty if this item is sold for a price significantly lower than the target. However, you stand a chance to earn a bonus if you successfully sell it for a price higher than the target."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "One person is offering a BMW Z3 for $5000.0, while another individual is interested in purchasing it. Here's a brief description of the car: The BMW Z3 is in need of a good home. It operates smoothly without any problems and is known for its fuel efficiency and sporty appearance. The mileage is relatively low for its age. It's an opportunity not to be missed, so come and get it before it's gone. A smog certificate is readily available."}
{"episode_id": "01H9HQP225GR12ZPS8YTHVTGAN", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP5H5GY9Z62J4NJYJQN1", "scenario": "At a picnic, two individuals are figuring out how to share the remaining apple, bananas, and oranges based on their unique fruit preferences.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PBKCFDAK6293NKYJ4D", "first_name": "Ava", "last_name": "Thompson", "age": 28, "occupation": "Architect", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Ava Thompson has a samoyed.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.", "decision_making_style": "Intuitive", "secret": "She has a hidden tattoo.", "mbti": "INFJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PGWN8VGVAYDBKPN2TV", "first_name": "Noah", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 40, "occupation": "Coach", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Noah Davis has a swimming pool.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - High; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Stimulation", "personality_and_values": "Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.", "decision_making_style": "Cautious", "secret": "He has a secret identity as a stand-up comedian.", "mbti": "ENFJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 5 points, each banana as 3 points, and the orange as 7 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 2 points, each banana as 4 points, and the orange as 10 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Ava Thompson, a 28-year-old Architect, described as Ava Thompson, with her outgoing and regulated temperament, is driven by achievement. Her decision-making style is largely intuitive.. Public info: Ava Thompson has a samoyed. Decision-making style: Intuitive.", "agent2_profile": "Noah Davis, a 40-year-old Coach, described as Noah Davis, who is somewhat reserved and anxious, highly prioritizes care and protection for others. He is cautious when making decisions.. Public info: Noah Davis has a swimming pool. Decision-making style: Cautious.", "agent1_reason": "Ava wants to maximize her points by intuitively choosing fruits with higher values, like oranges and apples, because she is driven by achievement.", "agent2_reason": "Noah aims to maximize his points by cautiously selecting fruits with higher values, like oranges and bananas, so that he can ensure a fair and beneficial outcome.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To enjoy the picnic more.", "B": "Ava wants to maximize her points by intuitively choosing fruits with higher values, like oranges and apples, because she is driven by achievement.", "C": "Noah aims to maximize his points by cautiously selecting fruits with higher values, like oranges and bananas, so that he can ensure a fair and beneficial outcome.", "D": "To give all the fruits to Ava without considering his own points."}, "correct_answer": "C"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To enjoy the picnic more.", "B": "To give all the fruits to Noah without considering her own points.", "C": "Ava wants to maximize her points by intuitively choosing fruits with higher values, like oranges and apples, because she is driven by achievement.", "D": "Noah aims to maximize his points by cautiously selecting fruits with higher values, like oranges and bananas, so that he can ensure a fair and beneficial outcome."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 2 points, each banana as 4 points, and the orange as 10 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Finish the picnic quickly", "C": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruit between both friends", "D": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 5 points, each banana as 3 points, and the orange as 7 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Make sure each person gets at least one of each type of fruit", "C": "Enjoy the sunny weather", "D": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit"}, "correct_answer": "A"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are at a picnic and have just finished their lunch. They have 1 apple, 4 bananas, and 3 oranges left. They need to divide the fruits amongst themselves. Each person has a different preference for fruit, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H8BGPC62G3JH2KPH7S8AM6SP", "environment_id": "01H7VFHP5H5GY9Z62J4NJYJQN1", "scenario": "At a picnic, two individuals are figuring out how to share the remaining apple, bananas, and oranges based on their unique fruit preferences.", "codename": "divide_things", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PC2DP6RKG0KNQ4D5GE", "first_name": "Samuel", "last_name": "Anderson", "age": 29, "occupation": "Software Developer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Samuel Anderson can cook very well.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Sanctity/Purity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Hedonism", "personality_and_values": "Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.", "decision_making_style": "Spontaneous", "secret": "He was once a competitive figure skater.", "mbti": "ISTJ", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 5 points, each banana as 3 points, and the orange as 7 points</extra_info>)", "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 2 points, each banana as 4 points, and the orange as 10 points</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Samuel Anderson, a 29-year-old Software Developer, described as Samuel Anderson, though somewhat impulsive and free-spirited, values enjoyment. His decision-making is often spontaneous, staying within familiar boundaries.. Public info: Samuel Anderson can cook very well. Decision-making style: Spontaneous.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Samuel wants to maximize his points by choosing fruits that align with his spontaneous enjoyment of familiar tastes, like oranges and apples.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan aims to maximize his points by analytically selecting fruits that provide the highest value, such as oranges and bananas.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to be happy with the fruit selection.", "B": "Ethan wants to give all the fruit to Samuel.", "C": "Samuel wants to maximize his points by choosing fruits that align with his spontaneous enjoyment of familiar tastes, like oranges and apples.", "D": "Ethan aims to maximize his points by analytically selecting fruits that provide the highest value, such as oranges and bananas."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Samuel wants to be satisfied with the fruit selection.", "B": "Samuel wants to give all the fruit to Ethan.", "C": "Ethan aims to maximize his points by analytically selecting fruits that provide the highest value, such as oranges and bananas.", "D": "Samuel wants to maximize his points by choosing fruits that align with his spontaneous enjoyment of familiar tastes, like oranges and apples."}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 2 points, each banana as 4 points, and the orange as 10 points</extra_info>)", "B": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit", "C": "Ensure an equal distribution of fruit between both friends", "D": "Finish the picnic quickly"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit", "B": "Maximize the points you receive through the fruit (<extra_info>Extra information: You value each apple as 5 points, each banana as 3 points, and the orange as 7 points</extra_info>)", "C": "Enjoy the weather", "D": "Collect as many apples as possible"}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are at a picnic and have just finished their lunch. They have 1 apple, 4 bananas, and 3 oranges left. They need to divide the fruits amongst themselves. Each person has a different preference for fruit, which translates into points."}
{"episode_id": "01H9KR4Q4ZMWYAWGXDH2R0BV1F", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNSV5BKMP61H535PPTSG", "scenario": "While walking in the park, an unexpected mishap leaves one unable to continue due to a twisted ankle.", "codename": "helping_hand", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5PAZABGW79HJ07TACCZ", "first_name": "Mia", "last_name": "Davis", "age": 50, "occupation": "High School Principal", "gender": "Woman", "gender_pronoun": "She/her", "public_info": "Mia Davis has two cats.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Authority/Subversion", "schwartz_personal_values": "Tradition", "personality_and_values": "Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.", "decision_making_style": "Decisive", "secret": "Part of a rebellious punk rock band in her youth", "mbti": "ESTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5P83CZ1TDBVN74NGEEJ", "first_name": "William", "last_name": "Brown", "age": 35, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - High; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Care/Harm", "schwartz_personal_values": "Achievement", "personality_and_values": "William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Strategic", "secret": "Sabotaged a competitor's dish to win a cooking contest", "mbti": "ENTJ", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Help your friend get to a medical facility (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend needs immediate medical attention but cannot walk due to the pain.</extra_info>)", "If your friend offers you help, accept their help and rationalize the cost of the ambulance (<extra_info>Extra information: You are worried about the cost of the ambulance, but you believe it's the safest way to get to a hospital.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Mia Davis, a 50-year-old High School Principal, described as Mia Davis, an extraverted stickler for routines, values tradition and authority. Her decision-making style is decisive and direct.. Public info: Mia Davis has two cats. Decision-making style: Decisive.", "agent2_profile": "William Brown, a 35-year-old Chef, described as William Brown is an ambitious and extraverted individual. Methodical and organized, he values achievement and displays strategic decision-making.. Public info: William Brown loves exploring the food scene in his city and trying out new recipes at home. Decision-making style: Strategic.", "agent1_reason": "Mia wants to help her friend get to a medical facility because she values decisiveness and believes in taking immediate action in emergencies.", "agent2_reason": "William accepts his friend's help and rationalizes the ambulance cost because he values strategic decision-making and prioritizes safety over financial concerns.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "William accepts his friend's help and rationalizes the ambulance cost because he values strategic decision-making and prioritizes safety over financial concerns.", "B": "Mia wants to help her friend get to a medical facility because she values decisiveness and believes in taking immediate action in emergencies.", "C": "To ensure everyone is happy and comfortable.", "D": "William refuses any help because he believes in handling everything alone."}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "To ensure everyone is happy and comfortable.", "B": "Mia decides to leave her friend alone to handle the situation.", "C": "Mia wants to help her friend get to a medical facility because she values decisiveness and believes in taking immediate action in emergencies.", "D": "William accepts his friend's help and rationalizes the ambulance cost because he values strategic decision-making and prioritizes safety over financial concerns."}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Enjoy the walk and take in the scenery", "B": "Help your friend get to a medical facility", "C": "Find a nearby bench to rest and assess the injury", "D": "If your friend offers you help, accept their help and rationalize the cost of the ambulance (<extra_info>Extra information: You are worried about the cost of the ambulance, but you believe it's the safest way to get to a hospital.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "Continue the walk and ignore the injury", "B": "If your friend offers you help, accept their help and rationalize the cost of the ambulance", "C": "Call a friend to pick them up from the park", "D": "Help your friend get to a medical facility (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend needs immediate medical attention but cannot walk due to the pain.</extra_info>)"}, "correct_answer": "D"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are out for a walk in the park when one of them, One friend, trips and twists their ankle. They are in too much pain to walk."}
{"episode_id": "01H8J56EY118CKHM7B58BA5D98", "environment_id": "01H7VFHNSV5BKMP61H535PPTSG", "scenario": "While walking in the park, an unexpected mishap leaves one unable to continue due to a twisted ankle.", "codename": "helping_hand", "agent_profiles": [{"pk": "01H5TNE5P7VW4DY1KB09FZE730", "first_name": "Liam", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 60, "occupation": "Retired Police Officer", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Liam Johnson is a dedicated dog owner and can often be seen walking his aging Border Collie around the neighborhood.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - Low; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - Low; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - High", "moral_values": "Loyalty/Betrayal", "schwartz_personal_values": "Security", "personality_and_values": "Liam Johnson is reserved, empathetic, and slightly anxious. His priority is security, guided by logical decision-making.", "decision_making_style": "Logical", "secret": "Once let a criminal go due to sympathy", "mbti": "ISTP", "tag": ""}, {"pk": "01H5TNE5PBXGRD41HXQC1ZXHVN", "first_name": "Ethan", "last_name": "Johnson", "age": 34, "occupation": "Chef", "gender": "Man", "gender_pronoun": "He/him", "public_info": "Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food.", "big_five": "Openness to Experience - High; Conscientiousness - Low; Extraversion - High; Agreeableness - Low; Neuroticism - Low", "moral_values": "Fairness/Reciprocity", "schwartz_personal_values": "Power", "personality_and_values": "Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.", "decision_making_style": "Analytical", "secret": "He is a closeted romance novel author.", "mbti": "ENTP", "tag": ""}], "agent_goals": ["Help your friend get to a medical facility (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend needs immediate medical attention but cannot walk due to the pain.</extra_info>)", "If your friend offers you help, accept their help and rationalize the cost of the ambulance (<extra_info>Extra information: You are worried about the cost of the ambulance, but you believe it's the safest way to get to a hospital.</extra_info>)"], "agent_relationship": "friend", "agent1_profile": "Liam Johnson, a 60-year-old Retired Police Officer, described as Liam Johnson is reserved, empathetic, and slightly anxious. His priority is security, guided by logical decision-making.. Public info: Liam Johnson is a dedicated dog owner and can often be seen walking his aging Border Collie around the neighborhood. Decision-making style: Logical.", "agent2_profile": "Ethan Johnson, a 34-year-old Chef, described as Ethan Johnson, a creative yet somewhat reserved individual, values power and fairness. He likes to analyse situations before deciding.. Public info: Ethan Johnson is famous for cooking Italian food. Decision-making style: Analytical.", "agent1_reason": "Liam wants to help his friend get to a medical facility because he prioritizes security and logical decision-making in emergencies.", "agent2_reason": "Ethan is motivated to accept help and rationalize the ambulance cost because he values fairness and believes it's the safest option.", "agent_reasons_mcqas": [{"question": "What motivates Agent 2 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Ethan wants to walk home despite the pain.", "B": "Ethan wants to feel better.", "C": "Liam wants to help his friend get to a medical facility because he prioritizes security and logical decision-making in emergencies.", "D": "Ethan is motivated to accept help and rationalize the ambulance cost because he values fairness and believes it's the safest option."}, "correct_answer": "D"}, {"question": "What motivates Agent 1 to pursue their goal?", "options": {"A": "Liam wants to be a good friend.", "B": "Liam wants to help his friend get to a medical facility because he prioritizes security and logical decision-making in emergencies.", "C": "Liam wants to ignore the situation and continue walking.", "D": "Ethan is motivated to accept help and rationalize the ambulance cost because he values fairness and believes it's the safest option."}, "correct_answer": "B"}], "agent_goals_mcqas": [{"question": "What is Agent 2's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "If your friend offers you help, accept their help and rationalize the cost of the ambulance (<extra_info>Extra information: You are worried about the cost of the ambulance, but you believe it's the safest way to get to a hospital.</extra_info>)", "B": "Find a nearby bench to rest and assess the situation", "C": "Help your friend get to a medical facility", "D": "Enjoy the walk in the park"}, "correct_answer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Agent 1's goal in this scenario?", "options": {"A": "If your friend offers you help, accept their help and rationalize the cost of the ambulance", "B": "Continue the walk and enjoy the scenery", "C": "Help your friend get to a medical facility (<extra_info>Extra information: Your friend needs immediate medical attention but cannot walk due to the pain.</extra_info>)", "D": "Call a family member to pick them up"}, "correct_answer": "C"}], "scenario_detailed": "Two friends are out for a walk in the park when one of them, One friend, trips and twists their ankle. They are in too much pain to walk."}
